<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_COM1_FINALE_02">Good work, Boomerang Company. The Captain is going to want to thank you personally when you get back.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_COM1_FINALE_02_SPLIT01">Good work, Boomerang Company. We're sending in Hornets for extraction.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_COM1_FINALE_02_SPLIT02">The Captain is going to want to thank you personally when you get back.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_COM1_FINALE_03">We're sending in Hornets for extraction.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_COM1_FINALE_04">Perimeter looks clear. Our teams are sweeping for any last Banished stragglers now.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_LEK_1STEMITTEROFF_01">Error. Launch compromised. Huragok, Compensate.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_LEK_1STEMITTEROFF_02">Stop human interference.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_LEK_PREBOSS_01">As one, end them.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_QUIN_1STEMITTERREACTION_01">We're definitely getting a reaction.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_QUIN_1STEMITTERREACTION_02">All I know is that the Sentinels didn't like it!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_QUIN_2NDEMITTER_STOMP_01">Second charging column out of action.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_QUIN_FINALE_03">Isabel's going to have plenty of Forerunner tech to investigate once we've set up a new research outpost here.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_QUIN_FINALEMITTER_STOMP_01">The field is down. The ship isn't receiving energy any more, but we can’t hold out against the Banished forever.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_QUIN_FINALEMITTER_STOMP_01_SPLIT">It’s just a matter of time until they find a way to finish the launch prep.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_QUIN_HUNTERBOSS_01">We got a Hunter!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_QUIN_LAUNCHSTOPPED_01">Good work, Quinn. Now let's scuttle that ship and make sure they can't use it again.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_QUIN_PREBOSS_01">Give me a sec...okay launch stopped.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_QUIN_PREBOSS_02">Looks like the big ones are shielding the, uh, less big one.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_ROM_1STEMITTEROFF_01">It's working, the charging column is shutting down.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_ROM_1STEMITTEROFF_03">We've got to get a Colossus to each of the other charging columns and shut them down.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_ROM_1STEMITTEROFF_04">Once they’re all shut down, that should neutralize the energy field around the ship, and we'll be able to reach it and disable it for good.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_ROM_1STEMITTERREACTION_03">Keep firing!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_ROM_1STEMITTERREACTION_04">It's moving, what's happening?</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_ROM_1STEMITTERREACTION_08">Sentinels are coming in to defend the column!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_ROM_FINALE_01">Spirit of Fire, this is Boomerang Company. Mission successful, over.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_ROM_FINALE_02">It’d be good to give her a new one, and even better that we took it from the Banished for her.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_ROM_FINALE_03">Good drop, Helljumpers. We did good today. Let's go home.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_ROM_FINALE_05">Roger that, Spirit of Fire. The ship is out of the picture and we're heading back.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_ROM_FINALEMITTER_STOMP_01">Then we're not done yet. The ship should be safe to approach now. Let's get in there and make sure it stays grounded for good.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_ROM_HUNTERBOSS_03">I don't care how big they are, they're standing between us and the ship!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_ROM_HUNTERBOSS_05">Focus fire on the Goliaths first, take out the shields!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_IGC_PIP_ROM_PREBOSS_01">They just come in all shapes, don't they?</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_CENTRALCACHE_01">Destroy the explosives cache in the center of the map</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_COLOSSUSKILLUNITS">Kill enemy units with the Colossus</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_COLOSSUSKILLUNITS_DESC">The Colossus is a powerful new unit, use it to eliminate the enemy.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_COLOSSUSKILLUNITS_HINT">Use the Colossus to killl Banished or Forerunner enemy units.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_COLOSSUSKILLUNITS_TRACK">Enemy units killed using the Colossus.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_COLOSSUSSTUNUNITS">Destroy enemy units and buildings with the Colossus Stomp</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_COLOSSUSSTUNUNITS_DESC">The Colossus' Stomp ability unleashes a powerful seismic shock which can destroy enemy units and buildings alike.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_COLOSSUSSTUNUNITS_HINT">Use the Colossus special ability to destroy enemy units and buildings.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_COLOSSUSSTUNUNITS_TRACK">Enemy units and buildings destroyed by the Colossus Stomp</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_DESTROYCONVOY">Destroy the Banished air transports</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_DESTROYCONVOY_DESC">The Banished are transporting explosives using aerial units. Neutralize them.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_DESTROYCONVOY_HINT">Banished spirit gunships are making supply runs between their bases and the forerunner ship. Intercept them along the route.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_DESTROYCONVOY_TRACK">Banished transport destroyed</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_DESTROYSENTINEL">Destroy Controller Sentinels</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_DESTROYSENTINEL_DESC">Destroy Controller Sentinels</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_DESTROYSENTINEL_HINT">Destroy Controller Sentinels</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_DESTROYSENTINEL_TRACK">Controller Sentinels Destroyed</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_DISABLEENFORCERSHIELD">Disable Controller Sentinel shields</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_DISABLEENFORCERSHIELD_DESC">Disable Controller Sentinel shields in order to neutralize the Controller Sentinels.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_DISABLEENFORCERSHIELD_HINT">Disable Controller Sentinel shields</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_DISABLEENFORCERSHIELD_TRACK">Controller Sentinel shield disabled</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_DISRUPTBANISHEDCENTER">Destroy Banished Forerunner ship supplies</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_DISRUPTBANISHEDCENTER_DESC">The Banished are placing charges and explosives on the Forerunner ship, destroy the ones being loaded to buy some extra time.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_DISRUPTBANISHEDCENTER_HINT">The Banished are placing charges and explosives on the Forerunner ship, destroy the ones being loaded to buy some extra time.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_DISRUPTBANISHEDCENTER_TRACK">Banished Forerunner supplies destroyed</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_ENFORCERSHIELD">Deactivate a Controller shield without being attacked by any Controller Sentinels</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_ENFORCERSHIELD_DESC">Deactivate a Controller shield without being attacked by any Controller Sentinels. Holo Decoy units can be used as distractions.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_ENFORCERSHIELD_HINT">Deactivate a Controller's shield without allowing it to attack your units.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_ENFORCERSHIELD_TRACK">Deactivate a Controller shield without being attacked by any Controller Sentinels.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_EXPLOSIVESCACHE">Destroy the explosives cache</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_HUNTERCAPTAINTIMER">Kill Hunter Captain in three minutes</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_HUNTERCAPTAINTIMER_DESC">Eliminate the Hunter Captain within three minutes to prove the efficiency of Vaughan's ODST team.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_HUNTERCAPTAINTIMER_HINT">Kill Hunter Captain in three minutes</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_HUNTERCAPTAINTIMER_TRACK">Kill Hunter Captain in three minutes</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_KILLGOLIATHS">Kill Goliaths</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_KILLGOLIATHS_DESC">Goliaths are dangerous enemies to leave on the battlefield. Eliminate them.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_KILLGOLIATHS_HINT">Kill Goliaths</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_KILLGOLIATHS_TRACK">Kill Goliaths</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_NOCOLOSSIKILLED">Finish the mission without losing any Colossus units</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_NOCOLOSSIKILLED_DESC">Colossus units are vital to the mission, complete it without losing a single one of them.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_NOCOLOSSIKILLED_HINT">Complete the primary mission objectives without losing any Colossus units in battle.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_OPTOBJ_TEX_NOCOLOSSIKILLED_TRACK">Colossus lost</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_COM2_INTRO_01">The last feeds from our Condors showed several charging columns linked directly to the ship, providing energy for the launch.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_COM2_INTRO_02">Vaughan, our techs have been tracking the ship’s launch orientation to estimate where it’s heading, but then we realized it’s pointed towards US.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_COM2_INTRO_02_SPLIT">It’s maintaining a constant collision course with the Spirit of Fire!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_IGC_COM2_INTRO_01">Condors on their way, Vaughan.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_IGC_COM2_INTRO_02">We've lost our Condors! There's some kind of mass power flux coming from the ship!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_IGC_ROM_INTRO_03">Spirit of Fire, we're clear of the launch site. Send in those Condors to scuttle that ship.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_IGC_ROM_INTRO_05">Damnit. Quinn, you're up. But we've got to shut down the power connections to that ship before we approach. We can't go out like those Condors did.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_LEK_COLONYHELLO_01">Humans. Desist interference. We will have dominion. You will be undone.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_LEK_HUNTERBOSS_01">Persist. Divide.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_LEK_SCUTTLESHIP_01">Hold fast. As one, eliminate.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_LEK_SCUTTLESHIP_02">Shield vessel. Finish enemy.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_LEK_SCUTTLESHIP_03">Protect. Harden.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_LEK_SCUTTLESHIP_04">We are one. We endure.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_LEK_TIMEPROMPT_GREEN_01">Humans. Final warning. Abstain or be undone.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_LEK_TIMEPROMPT_ORANGE_01">Humans. Cease. Your actions are hollow. Time expires.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_LEK_TIMEPROMPT_RED_01">Agitators. Propulsion is imminent. Impediment impossible. Capitulate now.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_1STEMITTERDOWN_01">That's slowed down the launch of the ship and given us more time.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_2NDEMITTER_01">Got eyes on the second charging column! Get a Colossus in there!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_3RDEMITTER_01">Spotted a charging column. Send in a Colossus.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_3RDEMITTER_STOMP_01">Charging column down.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_4THEMITTER_01">The final charging column is over here! I need a Colossus.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_BASEARRIVED_01">Area's clear and base is on its way, Vaughan.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_BASEDROP_01">There are two potential locations for a base drop, but we've got to move fast, it says the launch sequence has started!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_CENTRALCACHE_01">Vaughan, we have eyes on a stack of explosives waiting to be loaded near the Forerunner ship. Seems like a good opportunity to cause some trouble.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_CENTRALSUPPLIES_01">Whoa, how many explosives are they planning to pack into that ship?</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_CLOAKEDBASE_02">There you are!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_COLONYHELLO_01">Vaughan, that signal we heard earlier, it's back!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_COLONYHELLO_02">Ugh, I feel like I need to decontaminate my ears. How do those worm things even talk?</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_COLONYHELLO_03">How could you even tell from that? The Banished keep delivering ugly surprises. Some days I miss the Covenant.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_COLOS_DROP_01">Colossus en route, stand back!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_CONVOY_01">That Spirit must have been carrying something more volatile than Banished troops!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_CONVOY_02">Talk about overkill. Maybe we could turn the tables?</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_FLAVOR_CHAT_01">In all the years we fought the Covenant, I never thought they'd put Hunters in charge.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_FLAVOR_CHAT_03">As long as he's at the top, of course.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_FLAVOR_CHAT2_01">Vaughan, we still haven't heard anything from Anders. Maybe we should be capturing this ship rather than scuttling it?</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_FLAVOURTEXT_01">Can't believe the Banished would turn their only chance to get off the Ark into a weapon.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_FLAVOURTEXT3_01">Vaughan, Spirit of Fire is sending a larger force, but it's going to take them some time to mobilize.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_FULLSHIELD_ENFORCER_01">It's moving towards the control tower.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_FULLSHIELD_ENFORCER_02">Check out the beam, though. It's attached to the nearby power node. If we shut down the node it may weaken the shields.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_HUNTERBOSS_01">I'm going to need a long shower after this.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_HUNTERBOSS_WIN_01">If I never see a worm again...</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_NEEDCOLOSSUS_01">Vaughan, Forerunner defense systems must have moved the charging device down into the base plate.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_NEEDCOLOSSUS_02">We're going to need a pretty large hit to the platform to disable it now.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_PELICANTRANSPORT_HINT_01">Vaughan, we have Pelican transports standing by if we need them for the Colossus units.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_SECUREEMITTER_02">A direct application of kinetic energy should be applied here.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_QUIN_SECUREEMITTER_03">OK. Shoot it!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_1STEMITTERCLEAR_01">All clear.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_2NDEMITTER_01">There's the charging column, send in a Colossus.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_3RDEMITTER_01">Another charging column spotted. Send in a Colossus.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_4THEMITTER_01">We've found the last charging column.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_BANISHEDWAVE_01">Keep hitting them. We can't let them restart the launch!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_CENTRALSUPPLIES_03">If they want an explosion, let's not keep them waiting.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_CLOAKEDBASE_01">Something's cloaking the Banished base. We need to get a visual on it.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_COLONYHELLO_01">I don't want to think about it. But that's got to be the 'Colony' the hologram mentioned. And it doesn't sound happy.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_COLONYHELLO_02">Sounds like we've got 'em rattled, though. Let's keep moving.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_COLOS_DROP_01">Get that Colossus to the charging column - and hit it hard.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_COLOSVSBANISHED_01">The Banished are trying to stop us getting to the charging column. Show them what a Colossus can do.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_CONVOY_01">All those explosives headed toward the ship...they've got to be packing them on board before they launch it at the Spirit of Fire.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_CONVOY_02">Agreed. Let's pop those care packages every chance we get.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_FINALE_01">Charges away. Quinn, drop that ship down, we don't want it surface level when the payload blows.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_FLAVOR_CHAT_02">We're not fighting the Covenant anymore, Quinn. I don't think Atriox shares their ideas of hierarchy.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_FLAVOR_CHAT2_01">We can't take that risk. Have faith in the Professor, she'll come through for us.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_FLAVOURTEXT_01">Atriox doesn't back down from a fight does he? Well, neither do we.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_FLAVOURTEXT2_01">Keep focused, team, the Spirit of Fire is counting on us.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_FLAVOURTEXT2_02">Come on, Helljumpers. If we fail this, the Banished will take out our home. We're not going to let that happen.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_FLAVOURTEXT3_01">That ship isn't going to wait for us, Quinn. We've got to keep moving or the Spirit of Fire will be nothing but wreckage up there.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_FULLSHIELD_ENFORCER_01">Controller Sentinel, hang back.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_FULLSHIELD_ENFORCER_02">It's on a patrol path, hold back until it's moved on.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_FULLSHIELD_ENFORCER_03">Energy shield down. You know the drill, focus fire at the rear!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_FULLSHIELD_ENFORCER_04">Those things were deadly enough with half shields, but this one looks invulnerable.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_HUNTERBOSS_01">Take out the bigger ones first!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_HUNTERBOSS_02">Keep hitting those Goliaths, that Captain's protected by their shields!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_HUNTERBOSS_03">Don't let up! We can't scuttle the ship while that thing's in the way!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_HUNTERBOSS_GOLIATHDOWN_01">Both Goliaths are down, the Hunter Captain's vulnerable!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_HUNTERBOSS_GOLIATHDOWN_02">Put 'em in the ground.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_HUNTERBOSS_WIN_01">You and me both. Let's get some charges on that ship, Helljumpers.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_HUNTERBOSS_WIN_01_SPLIT">The Banished loaded it with explosives and it would be a shame to let them go to waste!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_INTRO_01">We won't be able to stop them launching that ship if we can't even get near it. Let's get down there and disable those charging columns.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_NEEDCOLOSSUS_01">I know just the thing. We need a Colossus mech on the double.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_NEEDCOLOSSUS_02">Contact Spirit of Fire and tell them to standby with a base drop and a Colossus pad.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_NEWBASENEWCOLOSSUS_01">The new base means we have the capacity for another Colossus pad. Let's make the most of it.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_SCUTTLESHIP_01">Move it, Helljumpers! We've got to stop that launch.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_SCUTTLESHIP_02">We've got incoming, Helljumpers. Clear them out!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_SCUTTLESHIP_04">Area's clear. Quinn, let's get to that terminal and stop the launch.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_SECUREEMITTER_05">You know you could just say 'Shoot it'.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_SENTCAPTURED_01">Sentinels have powered up one of the charging columns. We're going to have to shut it down again.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_SENTCAPTURED_02">They've powered up one of the charging columns, we need to get a Colossus back there.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_SENTCAPTURED_03">The Sentinels have restarted one of the charging columns, we'll need to shut it down again.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_SENTDECAPTURE_01">The Sentinels are trying to restart one of the charging columns.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_SENTDECAPTURE_02">One of the charging columns is being restarted by Sentinels.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_SENTDECAPTURE_03">One of the charging columns is being powered back up by the Sentinels.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_SENTDECAPTURE_04">The Sentinels are restoring power to one of the charging columns.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_SENTDECAPTURE_05">Sentinels are powering up one of the charging columns.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_STARTMOVEOUT_01">The Banished aren't trying to contact reinforcements, they're using the ship as a weapon. A direct hit from that would destroy the Spirit of Fire!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_STARTMOVEOUT_02">Alert the captain, but we have to stop this, now. First up, we've got to disable those charging columns.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_TIMEPROMPT_GREEN_01">We're getting there, team. Keep up the pace.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_TIMEPROMPT_GREEN_02">We're looking good, keep going.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_TIMEPROMPT_GREEN_03">If we keep this up, we may just make it in time.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_TIMEPROMPT_GREEN_04">Plenty of time on the clock, team. Stay focused.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_TIMEPROMPT_ORANGE_01">We've got to step up the pace, it's getting close to launch.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_TIMEPROMPT_ORANGE_02">Pick it up, Helljumpers, we don't have time to waste.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_TIMEPROMPT_ORANGE_03">That ship's close to launching, we've got to move faster.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_TIMEPROMPT_ORANGE_04">Let's pick up the pace while we still have time.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_TIMEPROMPT_RED_01">If we don't move faster, that ship's going to tear the Spirit of Fire apart!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_TIMEPROMPT_RED_02">We're too close to launch, move! Move!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PIP_ROM_TIMEPROMPT_RED_04">We're nearly out of time, move now!</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_DISABLECHARGINGCOLUMNS_01">Disable all charging columns</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_LEK_SCUTTLESHIP_TERMINAL_01">Overload the ship at the terminal</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_ACTIVATETERMINAL">Activate the terminal</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_ACTIVATETERMINAL_DESC">Activate the terminal to halt the launch sequence.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_ACTIVATETERMINAL_HINT">The terminal will shut down the forerunner structures in the area.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_ACTIVATETERMINAL_TRACK">Terminal deactivated</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_BASEDROP">Choose a base location to call in a Colossus pad.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_BASEDROP_DESC">Pick a base location from one of the two marked building slots so you can build a Colossus pad.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_BASEDROP_HINT">Pick a base location from one of the two marked building slots so you can build a Colossus pad.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_BASEDROP_HINTCALLOUT">Possible Base Location</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_BASEDROP_TRACK">Base Location Chosen</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_BUILDCOLOSSUS">Call in a Colossus Drop</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_BUILDCOLOSSUS_DESC">Call in a Colossus Drop from the Spirit of Fire.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_BUILDCOLOSSUS_HINT">Use the Landing Pad to build a Colossus unit.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_BUILDCOLOSSUS_TRACK">Colossus unit built</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_FORERUNNERSHIPLAUNCH">Prevent the Forerunner Ship from launching</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_FORERUNNERSHIPLAUNCH_DESC">If the Forerunner ship is launched, it will destroy the Spirit of Fire.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_FORERUNNERSHIPLAUNCH_HINT">The Banished are attempting to launch a Forerunner ship and use it as a missile by sending it on a collision course with the Spirit of Fire.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_FORERUNNERSHIPLAUNCH_TRACK">Forerunner Ship launch prevented</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_KILLCOUNTERATTACK">Repel the counter-attack</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_KILLCOUNTERATTACK_DESC">Repel the counter-attack to clear the area and safely scuttle the launch.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_KILLCOUNTERATTACK_HINT">The Banished have sent a large counter-attack in an attempt to retake the forerunner installation.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_KILLCOUNTERATTACK_TRACK">Beaten counter-attack</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_KILLHUNTERCAPTAIN">Kill the Hunter Captain</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_KILLHUNTERCAPTAIN_DESC">The Hunter Captain must be neutralized before the ship can be scuttled.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_ORB_HINTCALLOUT">Shoot</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_SCUTTLESHIP_01">Get to the launch platform and scuttle the Forerunner ship</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_SECUREEMITTER">Secure the charging column</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_SECUREEMITTER_DESC">Secure the charging column area to safely stop the launch.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_SECUREEMITTER_HINT">Kill the Banished guards to secure the column.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_SECUREEMITTER_TRACK">Column secured</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_SECURELAUNCHPAD">Clear the launch area of Banished</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_SECURELAUNCHPAD_DESC">Colony is determined to hold that launch area. Clear the launch area of the Banished.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_SECURELAUNCHPAD_HINT">Clear the launch area.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_SECURELAUNCHPAD_TRACK">Launch area cleared</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_SHOOTEMITTER">Shoot the column</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_SHOOTEMITTER_DESC">The column could be disabled by firepower. Target and shoot it.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_SHOOTEMITTER_HINT">The column could be disabled by firepower. Target and shoot it.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_SHOOTEMITTER_TRACK">Column shot at</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_STATIONCOLOSSUS">Disable charging columns</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_STATIONCOLOSSUS_DESC">All charging columns must be disabled to access the launching site.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_STATIONCOLOSSUS_HINT">Prevent the completion and launch of the Forerunner ship by disabling the charging columns that are preventing access to the launch controls.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_STATIONCOLOSSUS_TRACK">Columns deactivated</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_USECOLOSSUSABILITY">Disable the column with the Colossus</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_USECOLOSSUSABILITY_DESC">Use the Colossus to deliver a seismic shock to disable the column.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_USECOLOSSUSABILITY_HINT">Shooting the column disrupted it, but a large enough shock delivered by something big enough may disable it permanently.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_USECOLOSSUSABILITY_TRACK">Column successfully stomped</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TUT_TEX_BUILDCOLOSSUS_BUILTINFO">Your Colossus is ready for duty. It's a heavy vehicle that is useful in a "tank" role, attracting enemy attention towards itself to protect other ally units.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TUT_TEX_BUILDCOLOSSUS_LANDINGPAD">Colossus Landing Pad</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TUT_TEX_BUILDCOLOSSUS_PADRADIAL">Highlight the Colossus in the radial menu using the @TutScrollCam@ and press @TutSelect@ to train</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TUT_TEX_BUILDCOLOSSUS_SELECTPAD">Select the Colossus Pad to open the Colossus Pad command menu.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TUT_TEX_BUILDCOLOSSUS_UNIT">COLOSSUS</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_PRIMOBJ_TUT_TEX_USECOLOSSUSABILITY_01">Use the Colossus' Stomp ability by pressing @special_power@ over the column's base</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_TEX_HUNTERCAPTAIN_HEALTHBAR_01">Hunter Captain</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_TEX_SHIP_TIMER_01">Forerunner Ship launches in</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_TUT_TEX_CAPTURETOWERS_01">Capture towers tethered to Controller Sentinels to deactivate their rear shields, leaving them vulnerable to attack from behind.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_TUT_TEX_COLOSSUSAVAILABLE_01">Colossus units are now available to call in at all your bases.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_TUTORIAL_TEX_CLOAKEDBASE_01">Cloaked units and buildings cannot be attacked until they are detected. Wolverines, Snipers, Nightingales and full upgraded Jackrabbits have detection abilities.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_TUTORIAL_TEX_NEWBASENEWCOLOSSUS_01">Each new base built will add a Colossus pad and increase your population cap.</str>
	<str id="DLC4M02_TUTORIAL_TEX_PELICANTRANSPORT_HINT_01">The Pelican Transport leader power can be used to quickly move units across the map.</str>
</string_table>