<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_ADVANCED_01">In Halo Wars 2, upgrading your base will advance your tech level. Higher tech levels will allow you to purchase more advanced units, upgrades and buildings.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_ADVANCED_03">Upgrade a base by selecting the central building and choosing the base upgrade option at the top of the radial menu.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_ADVANCED_05">If you have multiple bases, your tech level is determined by your most upgraded base.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_ADVANCED_06">Additionally, each building type has its own global upgrades and unit specific upgrades.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_ADVANCED_07">T</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_ADVANCED_08">.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_ADVANCED_09">&amp; a</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_ADVANCED_10">Some units are counter units. They can be used against specific units, even if it breaks the rock, paper, scissor rule.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_ADVANCED_11">If you need more details check the information on the radial menu.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_BASE_01">T</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_BASE_02">&amp; a</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_BASE_03">Y</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_BASE_04">You can build additional buildings at your base to produce infantry units...</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_BASE_05">&amp; v</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_BASE_06">&amp; a</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_BASE_07">I</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_BLITZ_01">In the secoond game mode, you&apos;ll fight conquer as many bases as possible before the time limit expires.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_BLITZ_02">Y</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_BLITZ_03">You just need to focus on capturing mini-bases.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_BLITZ_04">Each mini-base you capture will increase the number of units you can have on the field.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_BLITZ_05">The game is won by having the most mini-bases when the time limit expires or by completely wiping out your enemy.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_BLITZ_06">One final note: in this game mod you&apos;ll start with a limited number of commander points, so spend them wisely.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_CAMERA_01">I</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_CAMERAPC_01">I</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_COMMANDERPOWERS_01">Y</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_COMMANDERPOWERS_02">Commanders can aid you on the battlefield using their Commander Powers. In Halo Wars 2, the commander you have chosen to play with will determine the Commander Powers you have access to.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_COMMANDERPOWERS_02_F">Commanders can aid you on the battlefield using their Commander Powers. In Halo Wars 2, the commander you have chosen to play with will determine the Commander Powers you have access to.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_COMMANDERPOWERS_03">Commander Powers are unlocked by spending Commander Points.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_COMMANDERPOWERS_04">View and unlock your Commander Powers in the Command Tree. You can access the Command Tree by holding the View button at any point during the game.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_COMMANDERPOWERS_06">Any abilities you unlock will be accessible through the Commander Powers menu by pressing the left trigger.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_COMMANDERPOWERS_07">One of the most useful Commander Powers is the ability to heal units. If your units are low on health, target them and use the healing Commander Power to heal all units within the area of effect.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_COMMANDERPOWERS_08">Y</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_COMMANDERPOWERSPC_03">View and unlock your Commander Powers in the Command Tree. You can access the Command Tree by pressing T at any point during the game.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_COMMANDERPOWERSPC_06">Any abilities you unlock will be accessible through the Commander Powers menu by pressing Tab.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_CONTROLGROUP_01">Another way of managing your units is by assigning them to control groups on the D-pad.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_CONTROLGROUPPC_01">Another way of managing your units is by assigning them to control groups on the number keys.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_DOMINATION_01">Welcome  to Domination mode, where teams fight for control of Domination points on the battlefield.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_DOMINATION_02">Capture Domination points with infantry units to seize control.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_DOMINATION_03">A</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_DOMINATION_04">D</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_DOMINATION_05">The winner is the team that forces their enemy to lose all their tickets.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_E3COMMAND_01">You&apos;ll always start a match with a limited number of commander points, so spend them wisely.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_GARRISONEXIT_01">If you wish to take your units out of a garrison, press A to select the garrison and eject them via the radial menu.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_GOODBYE_07">T</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_GOODBYE_07B">G</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_REMINDER_01">If you need a reminder, just refer to your control sheet which also contains details of more advanced controls.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_RESOURCES_01">T</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_RESOURCES_02">Y</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_RESOURCES_03">Supplies and power can be gathered from the battlefield from crates or by capturing and holding Forerunner power nodes.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_SELECTUNITS_01">N</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_SELECTUNITS_02">Units can be selected by moving the cursor over them and pressing the A button. Holding the A button paints a selection area over a group of units. Alternatively, tapping RB will select all units on screen.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_SELECTUNITSPC_02">Units can be selected by left clicking on them. Hold left click and drag to draw a selection box over a group of units. Alternatively, pressing Q will select all units on screen.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_SPECIALUNITS">&amp; o</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_UNITORDERS_01">O</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_UNITORDERS_02">&amp; a</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_UNITORDERS_03">&amp; g</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_UNITORDERS_04">...and capturing tactical points on the map.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_UNITORDERSE3_02">&amp; a</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_UNITORDERSPC_01">O</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_WELCOME_01">Welcome to Halo Wars 2. My name is Captain James Cutter.</str>
    <str id="E3D_PIP_CUT_TUTORIAL_WELCOME_01_F">Welcome to Halo Wars 2. My name is Captain James Cutter.</str>
    <str id="E3D_TEXT_BETAWELCOME_MESSAGE">&lt;font color=&apos;#ffffff&apos;&gt;Thank you for helping us create, test and improve Halo Wars 2. This build is a snapshot of our work in progress and prone to normal game development issues. You will see glitches, hitches and even crashes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Xbox Live features may not work correctly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since this software is pre-release code, we cannot provide customer support in the traditional sense. However, feedback as you play and enjoy the game will help us improve and enhance the final product.&lt;br&gt;Your contributions are an invaluable part of our success.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Visit &lt;font color=&apos;#00d4ff&apos;&gt;http://www.halowaypoint.com/ &lt;/font&gt;&lt;font color=&apos;#ffffff&apos;&gt;to discuss the Beta and provide feedback.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online interactions are not rated.</str>
    <str id="E3D_TEXT_BETAWELCOME_TITLE">THANK YOU FOR YOUR PARTICIPATION IN THIS BETA</str>
</string_table>