<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<str id="EP2MBS_M01_PIP_CORR_01">Pavium, we are ready to move to High Charity. My men are impatient for glory.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M01_PIP_CORR_02">This war has tamed you, brother! Where is your Jiralhanae lust for adventure? That relic is ripe for plunder!</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M01_PIP_CORR_03">Yes, yes. I am well aware of what we face here. Hurry your preparations, old one, I already have troops on the ground! Voridus, out.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M01_PIP_UNBREA_01">Put a leash on them, Voridus! The terrain here is unsuitable for our power extractors. I am still working on a solution!</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M01_PIP_UNBREA_02">And your men would do well to remember that whatever we find here belongs to Atriox.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M01_PIP_UNBREA_03">This war has taught me, Voridus. Stay your hand. Once we reach High Charity we need to move quickly to avoid the wrath of the Sentinels defending it.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M01_TEX_INTELREPORT_01">Field anti-air units to combat the heavy Sentinel threat.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M01_TEX_MISSIONSUMMARY_01">Join and support Voridus' assault on High Charity.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M02_PIP_BRUTE_01">Pavium, our troops are en route to perform salvage extraction from the nearby ships.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M02_PIP_BRUTE_02">No, no further communications since he and his Brutes approached High Charity.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M02_PIP_UNBREA_01">Good. If Voridus has listened to me, he'll be doing the same from outside of High Charity. Have you had word from him?</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M02_PIP_UNBREA_02">Unsurprising. No doubt he's picked a fight with some Sentinels there, but he should have reported in. No matter.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M02_TEX_INTELREPORT_01">Valuable resources can be found amongst the wreckage from the crash site.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M02_TEX_MISSIONSUMMARY_01">Clear a path for the salvage operation</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M03_PIP_CORR_01">Some kind of Flood forms block the entrance to the station, it's as if they understand it's a threat to them.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M03_PIP_CORR_02">We haven't the numbers, Pavium. Each time we kill one, another appears. The Flood is everywhere, scattered across every surface, every crack and fissure!</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M03_PIP_CORR_03">We barely even had time to establish a base before they besieged us!</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M03_PIP_CORR_04">I will start our extractors up immediately to start stockpiling power.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M03_PIP_UNBREA_01">Voridus, my troops and I are nearly at your position at the salvage drills. Have you reached the Forerunner defense station?</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M03_PIP_UNBREA_02">We MUST reach that station, if we can't reactivate the Forerunner defenses we will have no chance against the parasite!</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M03_PIP_UNBREA_03">The fissures! That whole area is honeycombed with explosive power.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M03_PIP_UNBREA_04">If we can start the salvage drills, we can use them to cause a chain reaction and burn the parasite away!</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M03_TEX_INTELREPORT_01">Multiple Flood bursters have been detected in the area</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M03_TEX_MISSIONSUMMARY_01">Gather power to start up the salvage drills</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M04_PIP_CORR_01">Pavium, how far down is this facility? The lift still hasn't reached the bottom, it is endless!</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M04_PIP_CORR_02">I told you I will fix this, Pavium. The means to reactivate the Sentinel Flood defenses should lie below.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M04_PIP_CORR_04">The lift slows, it seems I have arrived. Hold the line up there, I’ll be back soon.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M04_PIP_UNBREA_01">If you had followed orders, you wouldn’t have to be down there, and I wouldn’t have to be up here watching more of our troops fall to the infection!</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M04_PIP_UNBREA_02">As does the Flood. Tread carefully. This area will be rotten with Flood forms.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M04_PIP_UNBREA_03">Be sure to make use of your incendiary gels, the enclosed spaces will work to your advantage.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M04_TEX_INTELREPORT_01">Jump Pack Brutes are vital to navigating the Archive.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M04_TEX_MISSIONSUMMARY_01">Find and reactivate the Sentinel defenses</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M05_PIP_ATR_01">Voridus, Pavium! Do you know what your actions have cost me?</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M05_PIP_ATR_02">You "thought it wise"? The Flood is the very thing this installation was created to destroy! You have no idea what you’ve unleashed!</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M05_PIP_ATR_03">I have spent months fortifying positions to continue the fight against the humans. Now I have to abandon them because of you!</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M05_PIP_ATR_04">If we don’t send every soldier we have right now to stop its spread, everything we’ve worked for will be consumed.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M05_PIP_ATR_05">I want actions, not words. I'm on my way.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M05_PIP_CORR_01">We’ve already reactivated the Sentinels, we will help them fix this! You have our word!</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M05_PIP_UNBREA_01">We will fix this, Atriox. We only thought it wise to inform you of the threat.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M05_TEX_INTELREPORT_01">Pavium's Mega Turrets are critical to defeating the menace.</str>
	<str id="EP2MBS_M05_TEX_MISSIONSUMMARY_01">Repel the final Flood threat before it's too late.</str>
</string_table>