<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
    <str id="EP2M03_BONUS_REPEL10TENTACLES_01">Fight back Flood tentacles</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_BONUS_REPEL10TENTACLES_01_SHORTDESCR">The Flood will use tentacles to attack your units. Attack them to force them back into the ground.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_DESTROY_50FLOODMEGATURRET_01">Destroy Flood forms with the Mega Turret</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_DESTROY_50FLOODMEGATURRET_01_SHORTDESCR">The Mega Turret is one of Pavium&apos;s greatest weapons against the Flood and will target enemies automatically.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_OPTOBJ_DESTROYFLOODBASES_01">Destroy the Flood bases</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_OPTOBJ_DESTROYFLOODBASES_01_SHORTDESCR">The Flood have started infecting Banished bases. Cleanse them.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_OPTOBJ_GATHERPOWERMEGARUPTURE_01">Discover each Giant Burster</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_OPTOBJ_GATHERPOWERMEGARUPTURE_01_SHORTDESCR">Crystallized power is forced up through the ground near Giant Bursters. Find each one to maximise your power collection.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_OPTOBJ_SPEEDRUN_01">Ignite the fissures within 40 minutes</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_OPTOBJ_SPEEDRUN_01_SHORTDESCR">The salvage drills will cause a chain reaction in the fissures, eradicating the Flood threat.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_OPTOBJ_STOPHIVECOMM_01">Prevent any Abominations from reaching the salvage drills</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_OPTOBJ_STOPHIVECOMM_01_SHORTDESCR">Abominations coordinate and enhance other Flood forms. Do not let them reach the salvage drills.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_ACCELERATION_01">Pavium! The Flood reinforcements are accelerating! They must recognize the threat those drills pose to them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_ALLQUIET_01">Pavium, it&apos;s grown quiet. Could we have finally pushed them back?</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_BANISHEDTURRETS_01">Pavium, we could use more defenses. It may be worth using some of our power to build turrets and upgrade them to counter the Flood!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_BLISTERBACKINFECTED_01">Pavium! The parasite has taken over some of our Blisterbacks! They&apos;re bombarding your base!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_ENCOURAGE_01">Our resources are growing, Pavium. Forge ahead!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_ENCOURAGE_02">We are gathering resources quickly! We may survive this yet!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_ENCOURAGE_03">We are getting closer, Pavium! I was wrong to doubt you.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_ENCOURAGE_04">We almost have enough power! Just a bit more.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_ERUPTURE_WARNING_02">Pavium, it&apos;s about to release more Flood! Get clear!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_POWERPROGRESS_01">Don&apos;t worry about me, brother, I consider this a challenge!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_PRESSURE_WARNING_01">Pavium, the pressure&apos;s begun building up again.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_PRESSURE_WARNING_02">Pavium, the pressure is at mid-point. Soon the bursters will loose more Flood!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_PRESSURE_WARNING_03">Pavium, the pressure is reaching critical state! The Flood bursters will erupt soon!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_PRESSURE_WARNING01_02">Pavium, pressure escalating now.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_PRESSURE_WARNING01_03">Brother, the pressure has started building.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_PRESSURE_WARNING02_02">Brother, the pressure is at half!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_PRESSURE_WARNING02_03">Pavium, the pressure is halfway to full release!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_PRESSURE_WARNING03_02">Brother, the pressure is close to releasing the Flood bursters!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_PRESSURE_WARNING03_03">The pressure will soon force the Flood bursters out, brother!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_REVISITRUPTURES_01">The underground power constantly flows, Pavium. Look for newer sources breaking up through the ground.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_RUPTUREBADNEWS_01">Brother, I witnessed one of those things decimate a squad of my troops earlier! They are everywhere here. They seem to occur on a cycle.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_TIMEWARNINGS_01">Y</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_TIMEWARNINGS_02">Pavium, you must take more power. The Flood multiply at a greater rate than our resources!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_CORR_TIMEWARNINGS_03">Our power is too low, Pavium!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_IGC_CORR_LASERDRILLFINALE_01">It&apos;s working, Pavium!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_IGC_CORR_LASERDRILLFINALE_02">Pavium, the way is clear! I can reach the Forerunner station!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_IGC_CORR_LASERDRILLFINALE_03">I will not return until I have, brother. Good luck.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_IGC_CORR_STARTEXTRACTORS_01">Start the extractors! We&apos;ll need all the power we can to start the salvage drills up!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_IGC_CORR_STARTEXTRACTORS_02">Pavium, the power is too unstable for our extractors.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_IGC_CORR_STARTEXTRACTORS_04">However, there are many small eruptions where the power has crystallized. If we collect them in that state, we can break them down for use in the drills.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_DRILLSWORKING_01">Voridus, the salvage drills have begun blasting through. We just need to protect them until they&apos;ve breached the surface and ignited the liquids beneath.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_HIVECOMMANDER_01">Their forms are endless! This thing seems to be leading the others, enhancing their strength! Focus fire on it!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_LASERDRILLFINALE_01">I would have preferred a cleaner solution, but it is clearly effective.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_LASERDRILLFINALE_02">I will stay here with the rest of our troops to guard your exit. Find a way to reactivate the Sentinel defenses down below, Voridus. Redeem yourself.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_LASERDRILLFINALE_04">And to you. Now go. I will inform Atriox of what has taken place here.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_RUPTUREWARNING_02">They breed faster than Grunts! We must end this quickly, they&apos;re heading for our base!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_STARTEXTRACTORS_02">Very well, Voridus. I&apos;ve set up my own operation, we&apos;ll start gathering the power we need for the salvage drills.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_ACTIVATEFIRSTLASERDRILL_01">The first drill has been activated.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_ACTIVATESECONDLASERDRILL_01">The second drill is working.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_ACTIVATETHIRDLASERDRILL_01">We&apos;ve activated the third drill.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_AIRINFECTORS_01">Stay alert, the Flood infection forms have taken to the air. Keep our aerial units away from them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_ALLQUIET_01">You know better than that, brother. Be ready.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_BLISTERBACKINFECTED_02">We must neutralize them quickly! If we lose our base, we&apos;ll lose the battle!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_BLISTERBURSTS_01">One of the vile things has burst! Deal with the mess it has released and try to keep your distance in the future!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_CLEANANDCOLLECT_01">Wipe out the vermin before we collect the rest of the power!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_DESTROYFLOODCOLLECTGOODS_02">We have exhausted the power from this area. We must find more!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_DESTROYFLOODCOLLECTGOODS_03">Stay vigilant for more bursters and secure the power near them! Time grows short!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_ERUPTRUPTURE_WARNING_01">That thing, something&apos;s happening!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_ERUPTRUPTURE_WARNING_03">Ready yourselves, it&apos;s about to erupt!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_ERUPTRUPTURE_WARNING_04">Move! It&apos;s about to set loose more Flood!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_ERUPTRUPTURE_WARNING_05">Ready your weapons, here they come!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_FIRSTMEGARUPTER_01">What is that monstrosity?</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_FIRSTMEGARUPTER_02">Save your weapons, they&apos;re doing nothing! We&apos;ll have to rely on the salvage drills to burn them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODBASE_01">The Flood has started overtaking our bases! The speed with which they&apos;re spreading is incredible!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODCOMMENTS_01">Is there no end to the horrors they can twist themselves into?</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODCOMMENTS_02">They are a mockery of all that lives!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODCOMMENTS_03">Force them back, the Banished did not defy the Covenant to be laid low by these wretched things!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODCOMMENTS_04">They&apos;re never-ending! Where are they coming from?</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODSPORES_WARNING_02">So many ways this sickness spreads itself! Keep your distance from those blisters, they seem to know when we are close!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_FULLBANK_01">We have enough power for all the drills. We must restart them now!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_KILLFLOODRUPTURE_WARNING_01">Cleanse this place!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_KILLFLOODRUPTURE_WARNING_02">Destroy the Flood so we can safely collect the rest of the power here!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_KILLFLOODRUPTURE_WARNING_03">Collect the power but be ready!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_KILLFLOODRUPTURE_WARNING_04">Clear the infected before we continue!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_LETSGO_01">With me! The liquid form of that energy has crystallized where it has broken through the surface. We can use those crystals to start the drills again.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_LOSINGDRILLS1_01">We&apos;ve lost one of the salvage drills to the Flood! Its going to take longer to trigger the chain reaction!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_LOSINGDRILLS1_02">Protect the other two!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_LOSINGDRILLS2_01">Those cursed things have destroyed another drill! We&apos;re going to have to hold out even longer now!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_LOSINGDRILLS2_02">We can&apos;t afford to lose that final drill. If we do, we&apos;ll never be able to reactivate the Sentinel defenses.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_LOSINGDRILLS3_01">They&apos;ve destroyed all our drills!  We&apos;ll never reach the Sentinel defenses now!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_NEEDALLTHREEDRILLS_01">We have to get all three drills running if we want to create a strong enough chain reaction!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_NEEDALLTHREEDRILLS_02">We still need to power up that last drill. We&apos;ll need all three to trigger the reaction!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_NEEDMOREPOWER_01">We&apos;ve used too much power elsewhere, we need to restock!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_NEEDMOREPOWER_02">We need to grab more power, we&apos;ve used too much on the battle!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_POWERPICKUPS_01">There is crystallized power breaking through the ground around that thing. Take it for the drills, we must seize all we can.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_POWERPROGRESS_01">We have enough to power a drill, but we&apos;re not finished yet!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_POWERPROGRESS_02">We&apos;ve gathered enough power for a drill. Keep going.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_POWERPROGRESS_03">This is enough power for a drill. We can start one up!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_POWERPROGRESS_04">Voridus, we have enough power for two of the drills now. Hold fast!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_POWERRUPTURE_WARNING_01">That&apos;s all the power, onto the next one!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_POWERRUPTURE_WARNING_02">We&apos;ve secured all the power here, move on.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_POWERRUPTURE_WARNING_03">We&apos;ve taken everything we can here. Onwards.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_POWERRUPTURE_WARNING_04">We&apos;ve picked this place clean of power, let&apos;s move on.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_PRESSURESPIKING_01">The underground pressure is spiking! It&apos;s working!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTDRILLS_01">Keep them away from the drills! The longer they take to work the more troops we&apos;ll lose to the Flood!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTDRILLS_02">They&apos;re attacking the drills! Keep the Flood away from them! We must keep them going!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTDRILLS_03">Stop the Flood from interrupting the salvage drills! They&apos;re our best hope.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTDRILLS_04">There must be something guiding the Flood, they understand the threat from the salvage drills!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTDRILLS_05">Hold them off a bit longer! We&apos;re close to triggering the chain reaction!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTDRILLS_06">The drills are close to starting the chain reaction! Keep the Flood away from them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTDRILLS_DESTROY_01">Keep The Flood from our drills! Without them we&apos;re lost.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTDRILLS_DESTROY_02">We can&apos;t lose those drills!  Protect them from the Flood!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTDRILLS_DESTROY_03">Do not let the Flood destroy our salvage drills!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTDRILLS_DESTROY_04">There must be something guiding the Flood, they&apos;re trying to destroy the drills!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_REVISITRUPTURES_01">Voridus, we&apos;ve picked the battlefield clean, but we still lack the power needed for the drills!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_RUPTUREBADNEWS_01">Monitor them as best you can. I&apos;ll need to know when they&apos;re about to burst.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_SPAWNERINTRO_01">What now? How many forms can these things take?</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_SPAWNERINTRO_02">That thing appears to react to our units and spawns opposing forms! It&apos;s too dangerous to ignore, take it out!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_SPOTRUPTURE_WARNING_01">Another burster! Grab the power before it erupts!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_SPOTRUPTURE_WARNING_02">There&apos;s a burster here, collect the power!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_SPOTRUPTURE_WARNING_03">Another of those foul things! Take the power from around it.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_SPOTRUPTURE_WARNING_05">Gather the power from around that growth.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_SURFACEBREACH_01">The drills have broken the surface and will soon start the chain reaction!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_THARSHEBLOWS_01">It&apos;s getting ready to spew more of its filth! Move!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_THARSHEBLOWS_02">The burster is about to erupt, fall back!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PIP_UNBREA_WAVESTILLACTIVE_01">Stand fast! We need to give the drills time to calibrate!</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PRIMOBJ_DEFENDDRILLS_01">Defend the salvage drills</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PRIMOBJ_DEFENDDRILLS_01_SHORTDESCR">Defend the drills from the Flood until the drills have breached the surface.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PRIMOBJ_POWERUPLASERDRILLS_01">Gather power to charge the salvage drills</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PRIMOBJ_POWERUPLASERDRILLS_01_SHORTDESCR">The power here is too unstable to extract using Power Extractors, so it will need to be gathered locally.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PRIMOBJ_POWERUPLASERDRILLS_02">Activate the salvage drills</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PRIMOBJ_POWERUPLASERDRILLS_02_SHORTDESCR">When all 3 salvage drills are charged and calibrated, they will burn through the surface.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PRIMOBJ_WAITFORCALIBRATION_01">Stand by as the salvage drills calibrate</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_PRIMOBJ_WAITFORCALIBRATION_01_SHORTDESCR">The salvage drills need time to calibrate. Cleanse the area and prepare for activation.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_TEX_ACTIVATE_DRILL_01">ACTIVATE DRILL</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_TEX_CALLOUT_DESTROYCRYSTALS_01">Destroy crystals to gather power</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_TEX_CALLOUT_DRILLPROGRESSBAR_01">DRILL PROGRESS</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_TEX_CALLOUT_POWERNEEDEDFORDRILLS_01">Press @TutSelect@ to access Salvage Drills</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_TEX_CALLOUT_PRESSUREBAR_01">RUPTURE PRESSURE</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_TEX_CALLOUT_WAITFORCALIBRATION_01">DRILLS CALIBRATED IN</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_TEX_DRILL_ACTIVATED_01">DRILL ACTIVATED</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_TEX_HINT_DEFENDBASE_01">Fall back and defend the base</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_TEX_HINT_PAVIUM_01">Armed with a long range Mortar Cannon, Pavium is a formidable force in any battle against ground based units.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_TEX_HINT_PAVIUM_ABILITY_01">Press @special_power@ to use Pavium&apos;s Target Designator.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_TEX_POWERBAR_PROGRESS_01">POWER RESERVES</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_TEX_TUT_AIRINFECTORS_01">Flood Seeder Infectors attack and infect air units. Counter them with anti-air units.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_TEX_TUT_BANISHEDTURRETS_01">Banished turrets can be upgraded to add anti-infantry, anti-air and anti-vehicle weapons. Unlike the UNSC&apos;s turrets, the Banished&apos;s turrets do not need to specialize.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_TEX_TUT_DESTROYCRYSTALS_01">The power beneath the surface has crystallized. Destroy the crystals to break them down and collect the power.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_TEX_TUT_FLOODSPORES_WARNING_01">Flood blisters will explode if you get too near them.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_TEX_TUT_HIVECOMMANDER_01">Abominations are huge, monstrous Flood units that strengthen surrounding flood units.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_TEX_TUT_MANAGEECONOMY_01">Balance spending your power resources between combat units and the salvage drills.</str>
    <str id="EP2M03_TEX_TUT_SPAWNERS_01">Spawners produce Flood forms to directly counter your units. Take them out to stop them producing counters.</str>
</string_table>