<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
    <str id="EP2M02_BRUTE_FLOODARRIVE_01">They were right, the Flood still lives!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_BRUTE_FLOODARRIVE_02">Don&apos;t let them touch you!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_GRUNT_FLOODARRIVE_01">What...what are they?</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_GRUNT_FLOODARRIVE_02">Run, run!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_BONUS_01">Build defenses</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_BONUS_01_SHORTDESCR">Build defenses to help you hold the line against the Flood.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_BONUS_01_UPDATED">Defenses built</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_BONUS_02">Kill Flood Pod Infectors</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_BONUS_02_SHORTDESCR">Pod Infectors are the Flood equivalent of anti-infantry units. Kill them to protect your infantry better.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_BONUS_02_UPDATED">Flood Pod Infectors killed</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_01">Recover the Blisterback crews</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_01_SHORTDESCR">Recover the Blisterback crews to add them to your army.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_01_UPDATED">Blisterback crew recovered</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_02">Recover resources</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_02_SHORTDESCR">Recover resources on the battlefield to aid you in the fight against the Flood.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_02_UPDATED">Resources recovered</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_03">Rescue the salvage teams</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_03_SHORTDESCR">Rescue the salvage teams to add them to your army.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_03_UPDATED">Salvage team rescued</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_00">Keep Pavium alive</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_00_SHORTDESCR">Pavium must be kept alive, his experience in battle is invaluable.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_01">Hold the line</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_01_SHORTDESCR">Pavium has ordered a staggered retreat to give Voridus time to respond. Hold off the Flood until the lightbridge is activated and you can fall back.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_02">Fall back to the first defensive line</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_02_SHORTDESCR">Fall back to the first defensive line and hold there to give Voridus time to respond.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_03">Prepare for the Flood attack</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_03_SHORTDESCR">Prepare defenses, heal and manage your army before the next Flood attack.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_04">Hold the first defensive line</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_04_SHORTDESCR">Hold the first defensive line while the Goliaths clear the wreckage.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_05">Fall back to the second defensive line</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_05_SHORTDESCR">The Goliaths have cleared the wreckage, fall back to the second defensive line.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_06">Hold the second defensive line</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_06_SHORTDESCR">Hold the second defensive line while the Goliaths clear the wreckage.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_07">Clear out the Flood from the Banished base</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_07_SHORTDESCR">The Flood are already at the Banished base. Clear them out to create an effective defensive position.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_08">Defend the main base against the Flood</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_08_SHORTDESCR">Defend the main base against the Flood and hold for word from Voridus.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_09">Retreat</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_OBJ_PRIMARY_09_SHORTDESCR">The Flood threat has become too great, retreat from the areas.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_BRUTE_EXTRAMEN1_01">Pavium. We&apos;ve been separated from the main force. We need help to rejoin you.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_BRUTE_EXTRAMEN1_02">Pavium, our pack is still awaiting assistance. Do you hear us?</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_BRUTE_EXTRAMEN2_01">Pavium, we are here to reinforce you but we are under attack by the Flood!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_BRUTE_EXTRAMEN3_01">Pavium, our reinforcement team has been ambushed by the Flood! We can&apos;t get to you!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_BRUTE_FIRSTFALLBACK_01">Pavium, we must go! They will infect us all!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_BRUTE_FIRSTRUPTURE_02">They&apos;re behind us now!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_BRUTE2_EXTRAMEN2_01">Pavium! We can&apos;t break through the Flood here, we need assistance!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_CORR_PHONEHOME_01">Pavium, this is Voridus! My pack and I barely escaped High Charity!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_CORR_PHONEHOME_02">I did not believe the tales! They appeared from nowhere and forced us back!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_CORR_PHONEHOME_03">During our retreat we discovered an entrance to a Forerunner structure below ground. My Engineers believe it is connected to the defenses I shut down earlier.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_CORR_PHONEHOME_04">We cannot break through the Flood to reach it! We are at the power support site you established earlier, but have already lost many to the parasite!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_GRUN2_FIRSTRUPTURE_02">This isn&apos;t happening!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_GRUNT_BURSTERPARTY_01">Where are they all coming from?!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_GRUNT_DEFENSIVEADVICE_1">They&apos;re coming from everywhere!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_BRUTE_CLEARWRECKAGE_01">Pavium! Movement! From High Charity!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_BRUTE_FIRSTRUPTURE_01">P</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_CORR_CLEARWRECKAGE_01">.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_CORR_EXITBLOCKED_01">Be quick, Pavium. The Flood are rapidly taking over this sector as well!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_CALLINMEGATURRET_01">We did not defy the Covenant to be twisted into such foul creatures! The Banished forge our own path!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_CALLINMEGATURRET_02">Send in a barrage from our turrets on the perimeter!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_CLEARWRECKAGE_01">Keep moving, I want us to be ready for extraction as soon as possible.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_CLEARWRECKAGE_02">Let&apos;s get to work. We need those barriers down so I can clear a path for the salvage route.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_CLEARWRECKAGE_03">Voridus, this is Pavium. Have you found anything outside the shell?</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_CLEARWRECKAGE_05">Voridus? Respond! Engineers, get his comms feed back, now!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_EMERGENCYSUPPLIES_01">Search for supplies! We will not be able to hold without support!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_EMERGENCYSUPPLIES_02">Grab those supplies!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_EXITBLOCKED_01">What?! The size of that thing, its...</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_EXITBLOCKED_02">...Voridus! Our way has been blocked, we cannot reach you directly! We will have to find another route!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_FINALESCAPE_01">I will not fall to these monstrosities!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_FINALESCAPE_02">That will hold them long enough, let&apos;s move out! Voridus, we have made it out. Hold on.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_FINALSTAND_01">Attention, pack brothers! We make our final stand here!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_FINALSTAND_02">I left too many Jiralhanae on the battlefield during the Covenant war. I will not abandon Voridus!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_FINALSTAND_03">If Voridus or one of his pack contact us I want to know of it immediately!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_FINALSTAND_04">Recover those Blisterbacks, we will need their power if we are to hold, even briefly!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_FINALSTANDALT_02">I will not abandon my brother!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_FIRSTRUPTURE_01">They are spreading beneath the substructures! We must stop this, but first we need to find a safe hold!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_FIRSTRUPTURE_02">Fight on! They must not overrun us!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_FLOODINFECT_02">Destroy those who turn, they are no longer your allies!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_MOREDEMCREW_01">We need more demolition crews! Send them in now!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_MORELOCUSTS_01">We need more Goliaths! Send them in now!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_SECONDLINE_01">We have little time to prepare before they return! Fall back to the next line and ready the defenses!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_ABANDONBASE_01">We cannot hold this sector any longer. Abandon the base!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_ALLQUIET_02">See to the injured while we can! Make sure none are infected!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_ALLQUIET_03">Shore up those defenses!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_ALLQUIET_05">We need more resources for the defense! Gather supplies while we can!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_BASEUNDERATTACK_01">We must not lose our base to the infection! Destroy the Flood!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_BRIEFPAUSE_01">They&apos;ve stopped. Stay alert, it may not be over yet.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_BRIEFPAUSE_02">Do not let your guard down, they will return.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_BRIEFPAUSE_03">They&apos;re back! Take them out before they destroy our base!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_BUILDDEFENSES_01">Get the defenses up! We need to stagger the Flood&apos;s assault with barricades!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_BURSTERPARTY_01">Dig in deep and show them the might of the Banished!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_BURSTERPARTY_02">We shall not fall to the parasite! Rally!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_CALLINGCORR1_01">Voridus? Are you there? I&apos;m holding the line as long as I can, but I won&apos;t be able to wait forever!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_CALLINGCORR1_02">Still nothing? Damn him!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_CALLINGCORR2_02">Voridus, this is Pavium. Are you alive, brother? We are holding as long as we can!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_CALLINLOCUSTS_01">The Flood are as inexorable as the stories said.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_CALLINLOCUSTS_02">Bring in the Goliaths to clear a path back to our base! We must hold the line for Voridus there, it&apos;s our best chance!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEFENDDEMCREW_01">Defend the demolition crew, they must clear both routes or we&apos;ll have nowhere to fall back to!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEFENDDEMCREW_02">Do not allow the demolition crew to be compromised! Keep the Flood off of them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEFENDDEMCREW_03">Defend the demolition crew or we will be overrun by the Flood!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEFENDLOCUSTS_01">Defend the Goliaths, they must clear both routes or we&apos;ll have nowhere to fall back to!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEFENDLOCUSTS_02">Do not allow those Goliaths to be compromised! Keep the Flood off of them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEFENDLOCUSTS_03">Defend the Goliaths or we will be overrun by the Flood!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEFENDLOCUSTS_04">We must have a staggered retreat, If Voridus is still alive he will need us!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEFENSIVEADVICE_01">Into garrisons! Defend yourselves!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEFENSIVEADVICE_02">Keep them back, do not let them overrun the area!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEFENSIVEADVICE_03">Do not let them touch you, it is said they will consume your body and mind!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEFENSIVEADVICE_04">Fight back! The Banished have not come so far to be devoured by monstrosities!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEFENSIVEADVICE_05">Hold the line!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEFENSIVEADVICE_06">Keep fighting, we shall not lose this place to these aberrations!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEFENSIVEADVICE_07">Stand fast! Atriox is who you should fear, not them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEFENSIVEADVICE_08">We cannot leave until we hear from Voridus! Stem the tide!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEFENSIVEADVICE_09">Push them back! Use all means at your disposal!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEFENSIVEADVICE_10">If your brother falls to one of them, he is your brother no longer!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEFENSIVEADVICE_11">Kill the infected where they fall, we cannot risk an acceleration in their numbers!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEFENSIVEADVICE_12">If you see your brother turn, kill him quickly and put him out of his misery!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEMCREW1_01">Bring the demolition crew in to clear a path back to our base! We must hold the line for Voridus there, it&apos;s our best chance!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEMCREW50DAMAGE_01">Our demolition crew is taking damage!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEMCREW50DAMAGE_02">Our demolition crew is still taking damage from the Flood! Defend them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEMCREW50DAMAGE_03">Stop the Flood from killing our demolition crew!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEMCREW75DAMAGE_01">Our demolition crew is taking heavy damage! Defend them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEMCREWDAMAGE_03">The Flood are trying to destroy our demolition crew! They&apos;ve taken heavy damage!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEMCREWDYING_01">We&apos;ve nearly lost one of our demolition crew! Quickly, we cannot lose them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEMCREWDYING_02">Stop the Flood attacking our demolition crew! They are close to dying!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEMCREWDYING_03">One of our demolition crew is about to be killed! Save it, quickly!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEMCREWSCOVERUS1_01">Demolition crew! Cover us as we fall back!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEMCREWUNDERATTACK_01">The demolition crew is under attack! Protect them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEMCREWUNDERATTACK_02">Protect our demolition crew, fools!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_DEMCREWUNDERATTACK_03">Keep the Flood off our demolition crew!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_EXITSTAGERIGHT_04">We&apos;re almost there, we must reach Voridus! I better have some answers, or I will kill him long before the Flood has a chance!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_EXITSTAGERIGHT_05">Push through them! Do not let them stop you!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_EXITSTAGERIGHT_06">Keep moving! If we slow down, we will be overwhelmed!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_EXITSTAGERIGHT_07">Use everything you have! They must not stop us!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_EXITSTAGERIGHT_08">Show them the Banished will not be stopped!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_EXTRAMEN_SUCCESS_01">Now, with us!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_EXTRAMEN_SUCCESS_02">Come with us, the fight is not over.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_EXTRAMEN_SUCCESS_03">Add your might to ours and help us repel the Flood!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_EXTRAMEN_SUCCESS_04">Hurry, we need you at the base.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FALLBACK1_01">We must retreat, the area is lost to the Flood. All units, fall back to the first position!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODARRIVE_01">The rumors were true! What has that fool done?</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODARRIVE_02">Coward! We will hold the line until I hear from Voridus and his troops. I will not abandon them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODATTACKINGBASE_01">The Flood are already at the base! Clear them out!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_01">More Flood incoming!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_02">Brace yourselves, they&apos;re coming back!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_03">The Flood have returned! Stand fast!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_04">They&apos;re coming! Engage and destroy!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_05">The Flood are back! Destroy them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_06">Here they come again, be ready!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_07">Incoming!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_08">The Flood are on the way, cut through them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_09">The Flood are here! Pick your targets!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_10">Flood incoming! Destroy them before they reach you!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_EAST_01">Flood threat from the east!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_EAST_02">Flood incoming from the east!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_EAST_03">The Flood are coming from the east!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_EAST_04">Flood coming from the east! Watch out!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_EAST_05">We have Flood to the east!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_NORTH_01">Flood from the north, cut them down!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_NORTH_02">Flood incoming from the north!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_NORTH_03">Flood forms attacking from the north!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_NORTH_04">Flood are attacking from the north!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_NORTH_05">We have Flood forms coming from the north!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_SOUTH_01">Flood incoming from the south!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_SOUTH_02">Flood forms attacking from the south!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_SOUTH_03">The Flood are coming from the south, beware!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_SOUTH_04">We have Flood coming from the south!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_SOUTH_05">Flood threat coming from the south!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_WEST_01">Flood incoming from the west!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_WEST_02">Eyes to the west, the Flood are coming!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_WEST_03">Flood threat coming from the west!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_WEST_04">We have Flood forms incoming from the west!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_FLOODWARNINGS_WEST_05">Flood threat to the west!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_GETOFFTHELIGHTBRIDGE_01">Get off that bridge! We need to shut it down and get it secured!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_GETREADY1_01">See to the wounded and prepare the defenses for the next attack! They are not finished with us yet!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_GETREADY1_02">My Orbital Designator shows a massive wave of Flood coming soon, gather supplies and build defenses to be ready for them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_GETREADY2_01">Keep your eyes out for movement, we must be ready when they attack again!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_GETREADY2_02">Repair and heal what&apos;s needed while we have the time. We must be at full strength.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_GETREADY2_03">Here they come again!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_GETREADY3_01">The Flood renew their assault! Steel yourselves!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_GOLIATHSCOVERUS1_01">Goliaths! Cover us as we fall back!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_GRABSUPPLIES_01">Break open those cases! Use everything we have to strengthen our defenses!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_HOLDTHELINE_01">We must hold the line here to give Voridus and his troops time to join us! Dig in!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_INFECTEDWAVECOMING_01">The Flood turn our own pack brothers against us! Put them out of their misery!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_INFECTINGOURTROOPS_01">Those things are infecting our troops, turning them against us!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_LOCUST50DAMAGE_01">Our Goliaths are taking damage!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_LOCUST50DAMAGE_02">Our Goliaths are still taking damage from the Flood! Defend them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_LOCUST50DAMAGE_03">Stop the Flood from killing our Goliaths!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_LOCUST75DAMAGE_01">Our Goliaths are taking heavy damage! Defend them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_LOCUST75DAMAGE_02">Our Goliaths are heavily damaged! Protect them before we lose them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_LOCUST75DAMAGE_03">The Flood are trying to destroy our Goliaths!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_LOCUSTDYING_01">We&apos;ve nearly lost one of our Goliaths! Quickly, we cannot lose it!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_LOCUSTDYING_02">Stop the Flood attacking our Goliaths! We cannot lose either of them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_LOCUSTDYING_03">One of our Goliaths is about to be destroyed! Protect it!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_LOCUSTUNDERATTACK_01">The Goliaths are under attack! Protect them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_LOCUSTUNDERATTACK_02">Protect our Goliaths, fools!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_LOCUSTUNDERATTACK_03">Keep the Flood off those Goliaths!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_MOREDEMCREW_03">And keep those demolition crews alive!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_MORELOCUSTS_01">Smash through those barriers, we need an exit route!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_MORELOCUSTS_02">Keep them back! We&apos;ll hold until the next barriers have been breached!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_MORELOCUSTS_03">And keep those Goliaths alive!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_ORBITALDESIGNATOR_01">The Orbital Designator shows we have a little time before the next Flood surge. Start preparing our defenses!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_PHONEHOME_01">You live! What madness has been released upon us? Is this your doing?</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_PHONEHOME_02">Then get in there and start them up again!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_PHONEHOME_03">Stand fast, we are on our way to help you break the lines.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTARTILLERY_01">They&apos;re creeping up on the Blisterbacks! Support that artillery!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTARTILLERY_02">The Flood are attacking our Blisterbacks, protect them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTARTILLERY_03">Our Blisterbacks are under attack from the Flood! Support them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTARTILLERY_04">Our Blisterbacks are being attacked by the Flood! We need that artillery!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTARTILLERY_05">It looks like the Flood are approaching our Blisterbacks! Do not let them reach them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTARTILLERY_06">The Flood are threatening our Blisterbacks!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTARTILLERY_07">Our Blisterbacks are under threat from the Flood! Keep those monsters away from our artillery!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTARTILLERY_08">The Flood are close to our Blisterbacks! Don&apos;t let them launch an attack!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_RETREATAGAIN_01">The Goliaths have broken through! Retreat back to our base and fortify it!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_RETREATAGAIN_02">Goliaths, cover us!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_RETREATAGAINDEMCREW_01">The demolition crews have broken through! Retreat to our base and fortify it!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_RETREATAGAINDEMCREW_02">Demolition crew, cover us!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_RUPTUREATTACKINGDEMCREW_01">The Flood now threaten our demolition crews! Protect them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_RUPTUREATTACKINGGOLIATH_01">The Flood now threaten our Goliaths! Protect them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_RUPTUREPROMPT_01">Flood spews from those eruptions! Destroy the filth pouring from it!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_RUPTUREPROMPT_02">We have a Flood burst in our territory! End the threat now!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_RUPTUREPROMPT_03">Flood burster! Destroy them before the Flood reaches our defenses!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_RUPTUREXPLANATION_01">Now the infection travels beneath us! Destroy those eruptions before they spread parasites behind our lines!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_SALVAGECREWS_01">Salvage teams! Keep gathering supplies, we&apos;re going to need them to hold against the Flood! The rest of you - FIGHT!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_SNEAKYFLOOD_01">They&apos;re attacking from behind us!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_SNEAKYFLOOD_02">Watch out! They&apos;re launching a rear assault!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_SNEAKYFLOOD_03">They&apos;re trying to surround us! Watch your backs!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_TENTACLESATTACK_01">Watch out, tentacles are bursting from the ground! Cut them down!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_VEHHICLEINFECTORS_01">Infected troops are using our vehicles against us! The Flood are adapting new forms to combat us! We must act quickly!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PIP_UNBREA_VEHICLEWAVE_01">The Flood are sending in infected vehicles now!</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PRIMOBJ_BASEUNDERATTACK_01">Clear out the Flood from the Banished base</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PRIMOBJ_BASEUNDERATTACK_01_SHORTDESCR">The Flood have already reached the base. Clear them out to create an effective defensive position.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_DEFENDLOCUST_01">Protect the Goliaths, all wreckage must be cleared</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_PRIMOBJ_TEX_DEFENDLOCUST_01_SHORTDESCR">Protect the Goliaths as they clear the wreckage. All wreckage must be cleared to ensure a successful staggered retreat.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_DEFEND_SALVAGE">Defend the salvage team from the Flood attack.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_HINT_BAN_TURRETS">Banished turrets can be upgraded to add anti-infantry, anti-air and anti-vehicle weapons. Unlike the UNSC&apos;s turrets, the Banished&apos;s turrets do not need to specialize.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_HINT_BARRICADE">Barricade build slot</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_HINT_BARRICADE_DESC">Barricades can be used to block, slow or damage enemies.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_HINT_BASE_FLOOD_TIMER">Hold the line</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_HINT_BLISTERBACKS">Recover the Blisterbacks to add them to your army.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_HINT_ESCAPE">ESCAPE THE FLOOD</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_HINT_GARRISON">Garrisons are effective cover against the Flood, use them to hold the line more effectively.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_HINT_HEROPOWER">Leader powers are available to help you slow the Flood attacks, access leader powers by pressing @TutPwrRadial@ to open the radial.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_HINT_INF_FLOOD">Keep your distance from Flood infector forms. They will infect and turn your own squads against you.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_HINT_PAVIUM">Armed with a long range Mortar Cannon, Pavium is a formidable force in any battle against ground based units.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_HINT_PAVIUM_ABILITY">Press @special_power@ to use Pavium&apos;s Target Designator.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_HINT_PREPARE">Prepare your defenses</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_HINT_RETREAT">RETREAT</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_HINT_VEHICLE_INFECTOR">Flood Infesters infect your own vehicles and turn them against you.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_HINT_WALL">Wreckage cleared in</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_TUT_BUILDDEFENSES_02">Construct defenses at the marked building slots to hold back the Flood.</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_WALL_A">Wreckage A</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_WALL_B">Wreckage B</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_WALL_C">Wreckage C</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_WALL_TEAM_A">Goliath Team A</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_WALL_TEAM_B">Goliath Team B</str>
    <str id="EP2M02_TEX_WALL_TEAM_C">Goliath Team C</str>
</string_table>