<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
    <str id="EP2M01_UNBREA_LENDYOUMYEYES_01">Voridus, my Orbital Designator is yours upon request. It will help you spot those launching bays.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TUT_TEX_UPGRADEBASETURRETS_02">Upgrade the turrets by selecting them and choosing the anti-air upgrade from the radial.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TUT_TEX_UPGRADEBASETURRETS_01">Upgrade the Stronghold to a Citadel to unlock and then build defense turrets.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TUT_TEX_SCARABGROUP_01">Keep track of the Scarab&apos;s progress by cycling through unit types using @TutCyclSquds@. The Scarab&apos;s health is displayed on the health bar.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TUT_TEX_LENDYOUMYEYES_02">To use the Orbital Designator, select it in the leader radial and press @A_LMB@ over a hidden area to activate it.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TUT_TEX_LENDYOUMYEYES_01">Pavium&apos;s Orbital Designator can be used to briefly probe through the fog of war and reveal hidden units.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TUT_TEX_EMPNEEDSREPLACING_01">The effects of the Disruption Emitter only last a short time and will need to be refreshed by firing a new charge.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TUT_TEX_DISRUPTIONSHELLINTRO_04">The launching bays will continually release Sentinels, so disrupt the flow of them with Disruption Emitters.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TUT_TEX_DISRUPTIONSHELLINTRO_03">Move the Disruption Emitter target over the Sentinel launching bay and press @A_LMB@ to fire a shell.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TUT_TEX_DISRUPTIONSHELLINTRO_02">Disruption Emitters fire a large EMP field upon impact which stuns all Forerunner units in the AOE.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TUT_TEX_DISRUPTIONSHELLINTRO_01">Open up the leader radial with @TutPwrRadial@ and use @TutScrollCam@ to select the Disruption Emitter from the menu.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TUT_TEX_BARRICADEHEALTH">Barricade Health</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TEX_TUTORIAL_ONLYSCARAB_01">Only the Scarab has the power to destroy the wreckage blocking the path. Use your units to protect the Scarab as it does so.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TEX_TUT_UPGRADEBASE_01">Upgrade the Stronghold to a Citadel to unlock then build defense turrets.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TEX_TUT_TUTORIAL_DISRUPTIONSHELL_01">When dropped from orbit, the Disruption Shell emits a large EMP radial field which stuns and damages Sentinels.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TEX_TUT_REAVERS_SPECABILITY_01">Press @special_power@ to use the Reavers&apos; leaping ability to cross the chasm and activate the lightbridge.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TEX_TUT_BUILDSUPPLY_01">Build Harvesters to gain a steady supply of supply resources.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TEX_TUT_BUILDRAID_01">Build a Foundry, Apex or Raid Camp to recruit more units.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TEX_TUT_BUILDPOWER_01">Build Power Extractors to gain a steady supply of power resources.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TEX_TUT_ANTIAIRDEFENCES_01">Upgrade the turrets by selecting them and choosing the anti-air upgrade from the radial.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TEX_HINT_PREPARETIMER">Time to prepare</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TEX_HINT_KEEPSCARABALIVE">Keep the Scarab alive</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TEX_HINT_DOUBLETAP">Double tap @TutSelect@ on one of your units to select all units of that type on-screen.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TEX_CALLOUT_SCARABHEALTH_01">SCARAB HEALTH</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TEX_CALLOUT_PLACEDISRUPTIONEMITTER_01">Place Disruption Emitter here</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_TEX_CALLOUT_GATHERRESOURCES_01">Gather resources</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_TEX_SOLVETHEPUZZLE_03_SHORTDESCR">Solve the final part of the Forerunner interface puzzle to deactivate the Sentinel defenses around the High Charity crash site.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_TEX_SOLVETHEPUZZLE_03_COMPLETE">Solved the Forerunner interface puzzle</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_TEX_SOLVETHEPUZZLE_03">Solve the final part of the Forerunner interface puzzle</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_TEX_SOLVETHEPUZZLE_01_SHORTDESCR">Protect the Scarab from Sentinel threats while Voridus tries to deactivate the defenses.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_TEX_SOLVETHEPUZZLE_01_COMPLETE">Scarab protected</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_TEX_SOLVETHEPUZZLE_01">Protect the Scarab</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_MEETRECONTEAMS_01_SHORTDESCR">Meet with recon teams on the way back to base to learn more about Voridus&apos; orders regarding the High Charity salvage operation.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_MEETRECONTEAMS_01_COMPLETE">Recon teams met</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_MEETRECONTEAMS_01">Meet with the recon teams for further orders</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_FINALESCORT_01_SHORTDESCR">Voridus has his own plans for High Charity and plans to use his Volatile Scarab to complete them. Safely escort the Scarab to High Charity.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_FINALESCORT_01_COMPLETE">Escorted the Scarab to High Charity</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_FINALESCORT_01">Safely escort the Scarab to High Charity</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_ESTABLISHMAINBASE_01_UPDATED">Building constructed</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_ESTABLISHMAINBASE_01_SHORTDESCR">Start preparing the base. You can choose to build turrets, resource buildings unit buildings.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_ESTABLISHMAINBASE_01">Prepare the base</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_DISRUPTIONSHELLINTRO_01_SHORTDESCR">There is a heavy Forerunner Sentinel presence guarding the High Charity crash site. Use Disruption Emitters to stun them as you progress through.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_DISRUPTIONSHELLINTRO_01_COMPLETE">Emitter used to locked down launching bay</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_DISRUPTIONSHELLINTRO_01">Use a Disruption Emitter to stun Forerunner and Sentinel threats.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_DESTROYUNSCBASE_UPDATED">UNSC presence destroyed</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_DESTROYUNSCBASE_SHORTDESCR">The UNSC have set up a base near the High Charity crash site. Destroy them to prevent interference.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PRIMOBJ_DESTROYUNSCBASE">Destroy the UNSC presence</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_WASTINGTROOPS_02">We still don&apos;t know how to bypass The Ark&apos;s defenses.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_WASTINGTROOPS_01">Voridus, I hope you are being cautious. I keep seeing Spirit transports over your position. You can&apos;t simply throw troops at the problem!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_TEMPUNSCBASE_01">What? If they crept beneath our scans their forces must be small. Simply a reconnaissance mission.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_SENTINELTURRETS_02">Atriox used cunning as well as strength. A wise warrior does not pick a fight with an unknown foe.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_SENTINELTURRETS_01">The area around High Charity is more fortified than anywhere else. It is clear we are treading where we should not.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_SENTINELSWARNING_01">Voridus, there are many Sentinels amassing here near the salvage site. They may be guarding, rather than protecting something within High Charity.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_SATELLITEATTACK_INTRO_01">Be careful, Voridus. There is still much we don&apos;t understand about the Forerunners and their machines. You may make things worse.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_PUZZLE03_01">Stay alert, you fool. There is a massive Sentinel wave flying in your direction!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_PUZZLE02_01">V</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_PUZZLE01_01">Hold, Voridus. We should send in Engineers first to examine the controls. You don&apos;t know what using them may do!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_ORBITALEYE_02">Voridus! The Orbital Designator shows they&apos;re coming from a nearby launching bay.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_MESSINGWITHMYSTUFF_02">Your &apos;improvements&apos; have shortened the duration of the EMP field. You will need to replace it soon!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_HISTORYLESSONS3_02">Atriox warned us not to enter High Charity, Voridus. Focus on salvaging what remains around it.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_HISTORYLESSONS3_01">Voridus, from the size of the shell, it appears large portions of High Charity remain intact.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_HISTORYLESSONS2_ALT_01">You know the tales of the Gravemind and the corruption it spread inside High Charity.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_HISTORYLESSONS2_02">If true, then it could be a greater threat than even the Covenant were.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_HISTORYLESSONS2_01">We should proceed with caution, Voridus. There are strange readings from inside the wreckage.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_HISTORYLESSONS1_01">High Charity. It gives me great pleasure to see the heart of the Covenant torn apart before us.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_FUELWELLS_02">I&apos;m not sure if our extractors could handle it in it&apos;s unrefined form.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_FUELWELLS_01">Voridus, I have run into problems with the salvage drills. The power that runs under the surface here is surprisingly unstable.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_FINALWARNING_01">Remember, brother, our orders are to leave the shell of High Charity intact. There should be enough pickings for us around the perimeter.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_EMPNEEDSREPLACING_01">Voridus, the EMP field from that emitter is fluctuating.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_UNBREA_DOYOUHAVEAPLAN_01">Voridus, you&apos;re going to be facing more Sentinels than we ever have before. Tell me you have a plan.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_SENTINELESCALATION_03">The Sentinels are sending even more against us!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_SENTINELESCALATION_02">Voridus, the Sentinels&apos; numbers have increased again!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_SENTINELESCALATION_01">Voridus! The Sentinel attacks have increased in ferocity!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_RETREIVER_PROMPTS_03">We need those defenses shut down, Voridus! These Retrievers are unstoppable!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_RETREIVER_PROMPTS_02">Voridus, the Retrievers still attack us! You must deactivate the defenses soon!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_RETREIVER_PROMPTS_01">Voridus, we can&apos;t defeat these Retrievers! We need you to shut down the defenses!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_RETREIVER_02">Voridus! We&apos;re not doing any damage against those Retrievers! How will we stop them?</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_RETREIVER_01">Voridus! The Ark has sent Retrievers to stop us!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_PUZZLE03_01">We are approaching High Charity now, Voridus.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_BARRICADE_MOVINGOUT_03">We&apos;ve cleared the path, Voridus. Moving out now.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_BARRICADE_MOVINGOUT_02">Path clear! Moving out!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_BARRICADE_MOVINGOUT_01">Wreckage destroyed! Moving out!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_BARRICADE_LOWHEALTH_03">We&apos;ve almost cleared the path.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_BARRICADE_LOWHEALTH_02">We&apos;re nearly through, Voridus.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_BARRICADE_LOWHEALTH_01">We&apos;ve almost blasted through!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_BARRICADE_HALFHEALTH_03">We&apos;ve blasted through half the wreckage, Voridus. Staying the course.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_BARRICADE_HALFHEALTH_02">Halfway through!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_BARRICADE_HALFHEALTH_01">Wreckage at fifty-percent integrity!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_BARRICADE_ATTACKING_03">Clearing the path!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_BARRICADE_ATTACKING_02">Wipe out that wreckage!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_SCARA_BARRICADE_ATTACKING_01">Clearing wreckage!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_REAV_HUMANSCOUTING_03">Voridus, the scouting party was too small to be out this far without a base. They must have one close by.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_REAV_HUMANSCOUTING_01">Voridus! We&apos;ve run into a human scouting party!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_CHECKOUTMYRIDE_01">Very subtle.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_IGC_CORR_ENTERHIGHCHARITY_03">G</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_IGC_CORR_ENTERHIGHCHARITY_02_SPLIT02">It&apos;s time we got inside to take what&apos;s ours!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_IGC_CORR_ENTERHIGHCHARITY_02_SPLIT01">Focus the plasma emitter. Maximum cutting strength.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_IGC_CORR_ENTERHIGHCHARITY_02">Focus the plasma emitter. Maximum cutting strength. It&apos;s time we got inside to take what&apos;s ours!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_IGC_CORR_CHECKOUTMYRIDE_01">Subtlety is not needed, Pavium. Besides, it has been too long since I commanded a Scarab!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_IGC_BRUTE_CHECKOUTMYRIDE_01">Voridus, we have placed the markers to show the route for your Scarab!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_DABAB_GARRISONS_01">Me first, me first!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CRET_WHOTURNEDITOFF_01">Gah! What fool turned off the lightbridge?</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CRET_TUTORIALRESOURCES_02">You will carry what I tell you to carry if you value your worthless hides. This way.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CRET_TUTORIALRESOURCES_01">Stop gawking and grab them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CRET_SENTINELS_01">Sentinels! Reavers, destroy them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CRET_REAVERJUMPPROMPT_01">Reavers, activate the lightbridge so we can cross!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CRET_POWERNODESOPTIONAL_01">A power node! Seize it!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CRET_JOINUS_01">They&apos;re down. Now, let&apos;s get moving, our orders await!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CRET_INTROTUTORIAL_02">Silence! Those Covenant lies do not concern me and that means they do not concern you!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CRET_INTROTUTORIAL_01">This way, whelps, there&apos;s weapons to be salvaged from High Charity and Voridus commands us to return to base for new orders.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CRET_INTOGARRISON_01">More of those cursed machines!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CRET_HIGHCHARITYWRECKAGE_02">See how easy that was? Now come with us!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CRET_HIGHCHARITYWRECKAGE_01">Then don&apos;t waste time with your scanning toys! Smash it open!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CRET_DEACTIVATEDLIGHTBRIDGE_01">Cowards! I shall punt you into the void! Reavers, re-activate the lightbridge!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CRET_COVENANTWRECKAGE_01">You can return with salvaged goods, or on a platter as meat for the real soldiers. Your choice.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CRET_CALLINNEWBASE_01">Stop yapping about fake history and focus on your task!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CRET_BEHINDUS_01">They&apos;re behind us now! Stay alert!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_WASTINGTROOPS_02">You worry too much about old tales and strange machines, Pavium!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UPGRADEBASE_01">Get that base upgraded, we&apos;re going to need to build defenses!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNSCORBITALDROP_01">The humans are sending in support! Make them regret it!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_FIRSTATTACKS_06">Try harder! Hahah!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_FIRSTATTACKS_05">Was that supposed to stop me?</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_FIRSTATTACKS_04">Petty gnats!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_FIRSTATTACKS_03">Send something bigger next time!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_FIRSTATTACKS_02">Is that the best you can do?</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_FIRSTATTACKS_01">Bah! Barely a scratch!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_ALMOSTDEAD_06">Send Engineers! I will not lose this Scarab!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_ALMOSTDEAD_05">I will not be laid low by those things! Fix me!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_ALMOSTDEAD_04">Fix the Scarab! Before it&apos;s too late!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_ALMOSTDEAD_03">I cannot lose this Scarab! REPAIRS! NOW!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_ALMOSTDEAD_02">I can&apos;t take much more of this! Where are the Engineers?</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_ALMOSTDEAD_01">Impossible! They&apos;ve nearly destroyed my Scarab! Repair me!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_75PERCENT_06">I&apos;m taking fire! Stop them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_75PERCENT_05">Argh! I HATE THESE THINGS!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_75PERCENT_04">Stop those pests before I lose the Scarab!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_75PERCENT_03">I smell burning! What&apos;s going on?</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_75PERCENT_02">I need repairs, NOW!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_75PERCENT_01">I am badly damaged! Where are those cursed Engineers?</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_50PERCENT_06">If I lose this Scarab, I will raze the ground and salt the earth!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_50PERCENT_05">Don&apos;t make me come out there!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_50PERCENT_04">You will pay for that insult!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_50PERCENT_03">I will burn you all for this!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_50PERCENT_02">ARGH! I just got this thing!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_50PERCENT_01">This will NOT STAND!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_25PERCENT_06">If you damage this thing, you will pay!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_25PERCENT_05">Do you know who you&apos;re messing with?</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_25PERCENT_04">You are playing a dangerous game!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_25PERCENT_03">Try that one more time!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_25PERCENT_02">Very well, NOW you have my attention!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_UNDERATTACK_ATTACK_25PERCENT_01">You&apos;re beginning to annoy me.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_TUTORIAL_DISRUPTIONSHELL_01">Fire a Disruption Emitter at the launching bay. Its EMP field will stun those Sentinels!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_TEMPUNSCBASE_03">Then I&apos;ll make sure they don&apos;t report anything back.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_TEMPUNSCBASE_02">Pavium, the humans are here!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_TEMPUNSCBASE_01">The humans are here! They will not stop us from taking what we want! Wipe them out!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SENTSMESSINGWITHUS_02">Hah! The Sentinels will soon learn that the Banished are not as easy to stop as the Covenant!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SENTSMESSINGWITHUS_01">The Sentinels are trying to stop us reaching High Charity. The riches inside must be invaluable!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SENTLAUNCHBAY_05">That launching bay threatens my Scarab! Shut it down!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SENTLAUNCHBAY_04">There&apos;s a launching bay close by! We must stun it!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SENTLAUNCHBAY_03">We&apos;re nearing another launching bay! Shut it down quickly!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SENTLAUNCHBAY_02">What are you waiting for? Use a Disruption Emitter to stun any Sentinels launching from it!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SENTLAUNCHBAY_01">There&apos;s a Sentinel launching bay nearby!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SENTINELTURRETS_03">Bah!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SENTINELTURRETS_02">The Banished go where they want and destroy any who oppose! Is Atriox&apos;s rise not proof of this?</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SENTINELTURRETS_01">Pavium, we have encountered a new Forerunner defense system - turrets!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SENTINELSWARNING_02">Y</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SENTINELSWARNING_01">The old stories of the parasite? Nothing but Covenant propaganda, old friend.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SENTINELESCALATION_04">Then deal with them! Use everything you have!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SENTINELESCALATION_03">Use the Disruption Emitters, use everything we have - just keep them off that Scarab!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SENTINELESCALATION_02">They&apos;re getting desperate! I must be close to completely shutting them down!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SENTDEFENSESDEACTIVATED_01">The Sentinel defenses have been deactivated! They will interfere no longer!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SENTATTACKINGBASE_01">The Sentinels are attacking our base!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SCARABAMBUSH_01">We&apos;re being ambushed! Disrupt that launching bay!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SATELLITEATTACK_INTRO_03">This must be part of their defenses, I may be able to clear the skies if I can figure out how it works.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SATELLITEATTACK_INTRO_02">Don&apos;t fret, brother. I can handle it. I&apos;m going to investigate. Scarab commander, continue smashing through that wreckage.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_SATELLITEATTACK_INTRO_01">Pavium, I&apos;ve found some kind of Forerunner interface and there are more Sentinels nearby.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_REPAIRBASE_01">The base will continue to be a target for the Sentinels. Get it repaired now!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_REMEMBERTOACTIVATEBRIDGE_01">Once we&apos;ve bolstered our forces, we&apos;ll need to activate the lightbridge to advance.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLING4_01">It seems like I&apos;m on the last security level now.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLING3_05">Yes, I&apos;ve got it!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLING3_04">Every time I think I&apos;ve solved it...wait, this looks promising.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLING3_03">I&apos;ve breached the third level. It&apos;s only a matter of shutting it down now.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLING3_02">Gah! I will solve this if I have to press every button I see!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLING3_01">This looks more complex than the last one.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLING2_03">Almost there. Yes, this should be it.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLING2_02">I think I&apos;ve got it. Gah, that didn&apos;t work!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLING2_01">This level is more complicated than the first one. Make sure our Scarab is protected while I delve deeper.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLING1_SOLVED_01">It worked! That&apos;s the first level deactivated.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLING1_03">Aha! It seems to have several security levels and the first one should be broken when I do...this!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLING1_02">Could this be...no, that&apos;s not working either. Perhaps if I hit it hard enough...</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLING1_01">Hmm, perhaps if I rotate like this...no, that&apos;s not right.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLE2_USEEMITTERS_01">Use the Disruption Emitters! Nothing must stop our Scarab!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLE2_KEEPMOVING_01">Keep that Scarab moving. I&apos;ve breached the second security level. I just need some time to deactivate it.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLE03_02">I tire of their interference! I&apos;ll use this thing to deactivate the Sentinel defenses once and for all!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLE03_01">At last Pavium! I hope your pack is ready to transport the riches we find nearby!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLE02_04">You relics of the past need to make way for the Banished! This is OUR home now!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLE02_03">Come to see who&apos;s undoing your work, eh? Destroy them! I&apos;m not finished here yet!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLE02_01">Mysteries are what kept the Covenant blinkered and weak, we will smash through them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLE01_04">Protect the Scarab while I try and deactivate the Sentinel defenses!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLE01_03">Where is your sense of adventure? I&apos;m going to line up the plates and see what happens, we may need it soon!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PUZZLE01_01">It looks like this structure controls the plates outside, Pavium. There are, uh, many buttons.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PROTECTSCARABPOSTLASERS_03">Keep them away from the Scarab! We cannot afford to lose it now!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PROTECTSCARABPOSTLASERS_02">Don&apos;t let them harm the Scarab! We are so close !</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PROTECTSCARABPOSTLASERS_01">Blast them out of the sky!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PROTECTSCARABPOSTBASE_03">The Scarab can&apos;t take such a prolonged assault! DO YOUR JOB and protect me!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PROTECTSCARABPOSTBASE_02">Protect the Scarab! If I lose this, I will have your hides!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_PROTECTSCARABPOSTBASE_01">Get these pests off me! Hurry, fools!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_ORBITALEYE_01">Fear not, Pavium. One of my new toys should handle them.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_MESSINGWITHMYSTUFF_01">I made a few improvements and now it affects a much larger area.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_LETSGO_02">Keep up, we cannot risk being pinned by the Sentinels.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_INTERCEPTSENTS_02">Be watchful of the launching bays! We cannot let the Sentinels overrun us!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_INTERCEPTSENTS_01">Build turrets near the launching bays so we can intercept the Sentinels as they emerge!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_HUMANSCOUTING_02">Humans? Why are they here? I have bigger matters to attend to, but I may be able to spare another unit.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_HISTORYLESSONS3_01">Which means there are more weapons for us to plunder!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_HISTORYLESSONS2_01">M</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_HISTORYLESSONS1_01">And ripe for plundering, abandoned by the Prophets and their pets. Atriox was wise to lead us in revolt against such proud fools.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_HIGHERDIFFICULTY_SENTPATROL_04">We&apos;ve detected a Sentinel patrol nearby. It could be targeting our base and Emitters. Guard them well.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_HIGHERDIFFICULTY_SENTPATROL_03">The Ark has released a Sentinel into the area. Keep it away from our base and Emitters.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_HIGHERDIFFICULTY_SENTPATROL_02">Monitor our base and Emitters. There&apos;s a Sentinel patrol close by.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_HIGHERDIFFICULTY_SENTPATROL_01">There&apos;s a Sentinel patrol in the area. Keep a watch on our base and Emitters.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_HIGHERDIFFICULTY_SENTATTACKS_05">One of our Emitters is under fire from a Sentinel! Stop it!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_HIGHERDIFFICULTY_SENTATTACKS_04">A Sentinel has targeted one of our Emitters! Blast it out of the sky!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_HIGHERDIFFICULTY_SENTATTACKS_03">One of our Emitters is being attacked by a Sentinel! Destroy it, quickly!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_HIGHERDIFFICULTY_SENTATTACKS_02">Our base is being targeted by a Sentinel! End that thing!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_HIGHERDIFFICULTY_SENTATTACKS_01">The Ark is targeting our base and Emitters with Sentinels! Fend them off!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_HIGHCHARITYHISTORY_01">Pavium, our air forces are engaging Sentinels near High Charity.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_HATETHOSESENTS_02">Damn these infernal things!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_HATETHOSESENTS_01">I hate these things! Why must they plague me?</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_FUELWELLS_02">I</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_FUELWELLS_01">W</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_FLANKINGTURRETS_02">Forerunner turrets! Destroy them!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_FLANKINGTURRETS_01">The launching bay is flanked by Forerunner turrets! Take them out!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_FIRSTSENTINELSPAWNSWATTED_02">Now, hit them while they are defenseless!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_FINALWARNING_01">So you&apos;ve said many times. I can handle myself, brother. Voridus, out.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_FINALESCORT_WARNINGS_03">Swat those insects! We&apos;re nearly there!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_FINALESCORT_WARNINGS_02">Keep them off the Scarab!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_FINALESCORT_WARNINGS_01">Hold them off, I&apos;m making progress!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_EXPANSIONBASE_02">Take the base so we can divide the Sentinels&apos; focus and stagger their attacks! My Scarab must make it to High Charity in one piece!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_EXPANSIONBASE_01">There&apos;s a prime location for a base expansion near that launching bay!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_ESCORTWARNINGS_06">Do I have to tell you again? Protect your leader!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_ESCORTWARNINGS_05">I&apos;m under fire! Take care of it, NOW!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_ESCORTWARNINGS_04">I am under attack! Act quickly!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_ESCORTWARNINGS_03">If I lose this Scarab, I will build a new one starting with your bones!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_ESCORTWARNINGS_02">Protect your Scarab! Do your duty!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_ESCORTWARNINGS_01">Are you blind? The Scarab is under attack!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_EMPTYTURRETSLOT_01">Use those empty plots to build turrets of our own!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_EMITTEREXPIREDPROMPT_10">We&apos;ve used up another emitter, get a replacement out there.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_EMITTEREXPIREDPROMPT_09">Get another emitter ready, we need to replace the one that&apos;s burnt out!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_EMITTEREXPIREDPROMPT_08">One of our emitters is used up, replace it.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_EMITTEREXPIREDPROMPT_07">Keep replacing the emitters when they expire, we need to lock those sentinels down!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_EMITTEREXPIREDPROMPT_06">We&apos;ve used up one of our emitters, get another one ready.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_EMITTEREXPIREDPROMPT_05">One of our emitters has expired, prepare another!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_EMITTEREXPIREDPROMPT_04">We need another emitter, get one ready!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_EMITTEREXPIREDPROMPT_03">Prepare another emitter, we&apos;ve used one up!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_EMITTEREXPIREDPROMPT_02">We&apos;ve used up one of our emitters, replace it!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_EMITTEREXPIREDPROMPT_01">One of our emitters has expired, get another one out there!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_DOYOUHAVEAPLAN_01">I&apos;m putting it into action right now!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_DESTROYSIEGETURRETS_01">Disable those turrets!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_DESTROYEDUNSCBASE_01">Haha! I never tire of that sight!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_DEFENDWHILEIBURN_02">Keep them off my back!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_DEFENDWHILEIBURN_01">Defend me while I burn through this wreckage!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_COVENANTWRECKAGE_01">Troops, I&apos;m sending a Locust in to clear the path.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_CONTROLLERPATH_03">What are you waiting for? Use a Disruption Emitter!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_CONTROLLERPATH_02">There&apos;s a Sentinel launching bay nearby!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_CALLINNEWBASE_01">Clear that debris out and call in a new base! We&apos;ll need more troops to make sure this Scarab reaches High Charity.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BUILDTURRETS_01">The more turrets we have near those launching bays, the better we can control the flow of Sentinel attackers!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BUILDREAVERS_01">Make sure we have Reavers on the ground as well.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BUILDFEEDBACK_TURRETS_01">Good, we&apos;ve built turrets. Those will help protect our base as we make our way to High Charity.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BUILDFEEDBACK_RESOURCES_01">I see we have extra resources. They will help us build for the battle ahead.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BUILDFEEDBACK_NOTHING_01">We&apos;ve built nothing out of the base? That will have to do, we have no more time to wait.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BUILDFEEDBACK_FOUNDRY_01">Ah, I see the Foundry is up and running. We can start recruiting Reavers!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BLASTINGSTINGSTUFF_15">Hahahaha!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BLASTINGSTINGSTUFF_14">Grah!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BLASTINGSTINGSTUFF_13">Is this the extent of their defenses? Pah!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BLASTINGSTINGSTUFF_12">Disappointing! I thought the explosion would be bigger!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BLASTINGSTINGSTUFF_11">Build a better one next time!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BLASTINGSTINGSTUFF_10">A little heat for you!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BLASTINGSTINGSTUFF_09">Enjoy my plasma beam!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BLASTINGSTINGSTUFF_08">Voridus finds you wanting!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BLASTINGSTINGSTUFF_07">One side, insects!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BLASTINGSTINGSTUFF_06">See them burn! Hahah!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BLASTINGSTINGSTUFF_05">I was expecting more of a fight!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BLASTINGSTINGSTUFF_04">Where is the challenge?</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BLASTINGSTINGSTUFF_03">Fall before me! Hahah!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BLASTINGSTINGSTUFF_02">HA! I hope you didn&apos;t need that!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BLASTINGSTINGSTUFF_01">Out of my way!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BASEDESTROYEDMOVEOUT_01">Enough fun. Back to the mission!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BARRICADE_MOVINGOUT_03">The wreckage has been removed! Move out on me!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BARRICADE_MOVINGOUT_02">Wreckage clear! Let&apos;s get going!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BARRICADE_MOVINGOUT_01">Wreckage destroyed! Move out!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BARRICADE_LOWHEALTH_03">We&apos;ve nearly blasted through. Be ready to go.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BARRICADE_LOWHEALTH_02">The wreckage is nearly destroyed! Get ready to move!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BARRICADE_LOWHEALTH_01">Almost there! Keep going!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BARRICADE_HALFHEALTH_03">We&apos;re halfway through the wreckage. Keep going!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BARRICADE_HALFHEALTH_02">Structural integrity at fifty-percent!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BARRICADE_HALFHEALTH_01">Halfway there! Keep firing!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BARRICADE_ATTACKING_03">Fire! I want that junk out of my way!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BARRICADE_ATTACKING_02">Clear the path of that wreckage!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_BARRICADE_ATTACKING_01">Take out that wreckage!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_ATTACKUNSCBASE_02">Fire! Let the humans&apos; bases join the rest of the wreckage here!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_ATTACKUNSCBASE_01">You shouldn&apos;t have got in my way, humans!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_ANTIAIRDEFENCES_01">We will need anti-air defenses to deal with the Sentinels! Upgrade the turrets!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_ALMOSTTHERE_01">We&apos;re almost at High Charity. There may be more resistance, bolster our forces!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_1STWRECKAGECOMMENT_02">Next time the Covenant lose a war, I hope they clean up after themselves!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_CORR_1STWRECKAGECOMMENT_01">There&apos;s still so much wreckage lying around High Charity, it&apos;s going to take me a while to carve through it.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_BRUTE2_SCANFORWEAPONS_02">Brothers! We found these Covenant supply cases on our way to the base.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_BRUTE2_SCANFORWEAPONS_01">Scan that supply case! There may still be Covenant weapons inside!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_BRUTE2_FINDANOTHERROUTENOW_01">The path is marked, Voridus!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_BRUTE2_BASETHISWAY_01">This way, brothers! Our base is up ahead!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_BRUTE_NEUTRALIZESPAWNS_03">We need more Disruption Emitters!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_BRUTE_NEUTRALIZESPAWNS_02">The Sentinel launching bay is operational again!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_BRUTE_NEUTRALIZESPAWNS_01">Voridus, we need to disrupt the Sentinel launching bays.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_PIP_BABAB_GARRISONS_01">Outta my way!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_OPTOBJ_TEX_EXPANSIONBASES_01_SHORTDESCR">Expand to all base plots to stagger the focus of the Sentinel attacks.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_OPTOBJ_TEX_EXPANSIONBASES_01_COMPLETE">Expansion base captured</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_OPTOBJ_TEX_EXPANSIONBASES_01">Expand to all base plots</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_OPTOBJ_RESCUEREAVERS_01_SHORTDESCR">A Reaver patrol have encountered UNSC troops. Rescue them to add them to your army.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_OPTOBJ_RESCUEREAVERS_01_COMPLETE">Reavers rescued</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_OPTOBJ_RESCUEREAVERS_01">Rescue the Reavers</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_OPTOBJ_POWERNODESOPTIONAL_01_SHORTDESCR">Capture all power nodes around the High Charity crash site to gain a reliable flow of resources to help build your army.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_OPTOBJ_POWERNODESOPTIONAL_01_COMPLETE">Power node captured</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_OPTOBJ_POWERNODESOPTIONAL_01">Capture all power nodes</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_OPTOBJ_DESTROYWRECKAGE_01_SHORTDESCR">Covenant supply cases are scattered around the High Charity crash site. Break them open to salvage resources.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_OPTOBJ_DESTROYWRECKAGE_01_COMPLETE">Covenant supply case salvaged</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_OPTOBJ_DESTROYWRECKAGE_01">Salvage all Covenant resources</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_OPTOBJ_BUILDTURRETS_01_SHORTDESCR">Some Sentinel launching bays are protected by Forerunner turrets. Destroy them and build your own turrets to slow the flow of Sentinels from the bays.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_OPTOBJ_BUILDTURRETS_01_COMPLETE">Launching bay fortified</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_OPTOBJ_BUILDTURRETS_01">Build on all turret slots near the launching bays</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_OBJ_PRIMAIRY_07_UPDATED">Activate Lightbridge</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_OBJ_PRIMAIRY_07_SHORTDESCR">Activate the lightbridge to gain access to the next area.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_DABAB_TUTORIALRESOURCES_02">He sure is testy today. That was YOUR fault.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_DABAB_TUTORIALRESOURCES_01">Hey, look! Shiny!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_DABAB_LOTTASENTINELS_01">Whoa, that&apos;s a lotta Sentinels!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_DABAB_INTROTUTORIAL_01">Whoa, man. Back off the gas.</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_DABAB_COVENANTWRECKAGE_02">Choice made! Let&apos;s blast it!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_DABAB_COVENANTWRECKAGE_01">We turn back?</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_DABAB_CALLINNEWBASE_01">Wasn&apos;t that the Demon? Or was it a Flood demon?</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_BVOBANSH_CALLOUT_SENTINELS_ON_GUARD_02">Sentinels in the area!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_BABAB_TUTORIALRESOURCES_01">I think that&apos;s all I can carry, these things are heavier than they look!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_BABAB_SENTINELS_01">Agh! Robot things!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_BABAB_POWERNODESOPTIONAL_01">Hey, one of those big pointy things over there!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_BABAB_INTROTUTORIAL_01">Did you say High Charity? The Covenant capital-place? I heard it was haunted! Scary monsters everywhere!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_BABAB_DEACTIVATEDLIGHTBRIDGE_01">Aw, too bad. Guess someone else will have to deal with those Sentinels!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_BABAB_COVENANTWRECKAGE_01">Ooh, Covenant stuff! Retro!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_BABAB_CALLINNEWBASE_02">Hmmm, it&apos;s hard to keep track of this stuff. Too scary!</str>
    <str id="EP2M01_BABAB_CALLINNEWBASE_01">Didn&apos;t High Charity get destroyed by the Flood?</str>
</string_table>