<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<str id="EP2M05_BONUSOBJ_KEEPMEGATURRETALIVE_01">Do not lose any Mega Turrets during the mission</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_BONUSOBJ_KEEPMEGATURRETALIVE_01_SHORTDESCR">Pavium's Mega Turrets are a key to defeating the Proto-Gravemind. Destroy the Proto-Gravemind without ever losing a single one of them.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_BONUSOBJ_LICHKILLS_01">Kill Flood units with the Lich Vanguard</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_BONUSOBJ_LICHKILLS_01_SHORTDESCR">The Lich Vanguard leader power calls in a Lich which can not only produce units, but will attack nearby enemies.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_BONUSOBJ_LICHKILLS_UPDATE_01">Flood killed with Lich Vanguard</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_FIRETURRET_FOURTHCYCLE_01">Fire!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_FIRETURRET_SECONDCYCLE_01">Target acquired. Firing.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_FIRETURRET_THIRDCYCLE_01">Locked on and firing.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_HITTURRET_FOURTHCYCLE_01">Pavium! We're blasting it, but it's resisting!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_MEGATURRET_01">Pavium, the turret is ready to fire.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_MEGATURRET_02">Firing!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_MEGATURRET_AIMING_01">Locked on target.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_MEGATURRET_LOS_01">Pavium, I need a visual on the tentacle before I can fire.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_MEGATURRET_LOS_02">Pavium, what are my firing co-ordinates? We need eyes on that tentacle.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_MEGATURRET_LOS_03">Ready to fire, Pavium. Just give me eyes on my target.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_MEGATURRET_TARGETHIT_01">Target hit!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_MEGATURRET2_HIT_01">Confirmed hit!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_MEGATURRET2_TARGET_01">Targeting Proto-Gravemind.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_READYTURRET_FOURTHCYCLE_01">Pavium, all turrets are ready, do we have a visual?</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_TARGETHITTURRET_SECONDCYCLE_01">Target hit!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_TARGETHITTURRET_THIRDCYCLE_01">Confirmed hits from all turrets!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_TARGETTURRET_FOURTHCYCLE_01">We have it in our sights.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_TARGETTURRET_SECONDCYCLE_01">Turret ready, where is my target?</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_TARGETTURRET_THIRDCYCLE_01">Turret ready, I need eyes on the target.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_TURRETREADY_01">Mega Turret ready to fire.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_TURRETREADY_02">Next charge ready, give me a target.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_TURRETREADY_03">Ready for a new firing solution.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_TURRETREADY_04">Mega Turret waiting for orders.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_BRUTE_TURRETREADY_05">Mega Turret charged and ready.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_ARMOR_01">Pavium! There seems to be some kind of armor shielding the thing's hide!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_ATTACKCENTER_01">Aim at that thing in the center! It must fall!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_ATTACKCENTER_03">It is working! We're killing it!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_BASEUNDERATTACK_01">The Flood is trying to destroy our base! Stop them!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_BASEUNDERATTACK_02">Our base is under attack!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_BASEUNDERATTACK_03">Keep the Flood from our base, or we'll have no way to defend ourselves!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_BLOCKEDTENTACLE_01">Argh! How are we going to find the source of this outbreak thing with all these tentacles in our way?</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_BLOCKEDTENTACLE_02">Once we destroy it we can join the Sentinels in pushing the rest of the Flood back!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_BUILDTURRET2_01">Hurry, get that turret ready!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_CAVALRYRETRIEVER_01">Haha! Burn!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_CLEANSELOCK_01">Get to it, troops! Cleanse that lock while we still can!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_CLEANSELOCK_02">The lock is clear, Pavium. Has it worked?</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_CLEANSELOCK_03">A Retriever! You do not disappoint me, Pavium!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_FINALBATTLEAIR_01">Send in aerial units! Finish it!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_FINALSHOWDOWN_01">Let's show this thing Jiralhanae rage, brother!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_FINDSOURCE_01">Their numbers are infinite!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_FOURTHCYCLE_FLOODRELEASE_01">Another Flood wave! Stand fast!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_FOURTHCYCLE_INTROCHAT_01">We must be close now, how much more punishment can that thing take?</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_FOURTHCYCLE_TARGETCARAPACE_01">Blast through that armor!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_FOURTHCYCLE_TENTACLES_01">Keep out of range of those tentacles!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_FREETOROAM_01">At least with its tentacles retracted we can move about more freely!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_GRAVEY_GROWING_01">Pavium! Our sensors indicate the Proto-Gravemind is growing!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_HUNKERDOWN_SECONDCYCLE_01">Fall back, it has retreated again! Pavium, each time we injure it, it seems to come back stronger!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_HUNKERDOWN_THIRDCYCLE_01">It cowers in its hole! Prepare another turret to force it back out!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_HUNKERDOWN_VARIATIONS_01">We can't reach that thing while it's in that hole, Pavium!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_KILLEDIT_01">Haha! I told you not to worry so much, brother! A fitting victory to add to our past glories!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_LEGENDS_01">This could be our greatest battle, Pavium. We will be legends!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_MEGATURRET_01">But to where? We didn’t destroy it, so it must be connected to something!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_MEGATURRET2_TARGET_01">Fire! Drive it out!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_NEEDHELP_01">Pavium, that thing has grown too strong. Our turrets aren't enough anymore, we need more firepower!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_OPT_TENTACLE_01">More of those wretched tentacles!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_OPT_TENTACLE_02">We must act fast, if it reaches full Gravemind the Ark will be lost to us, and there's still so much to loot from it!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_PROTECTTURRET_01">The Flood is attacking the turret!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_PROTECTTURRET_02">The Flood is after one of our turrets! We cannot lose it!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_PROTECTTURRET_03">One of our turrets is under attack! Fend them off!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_PROTECTTURRET_04">One of our turrets is under attack from the Flood! Clear them out before they damage it!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_PROTECTTURRET_05">Keep the Flood from the turret!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_PROTECTTURRET_FOURTHCYCLE_01">You heard Pavium! This may be our last chance to kill that thing!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_PROTECTTURRET_SECONDCYCLE_01">Stop the Flood from destroying our turrets!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_PROTECTTURRET_THIRDCYCLE_01">Protect our turrets, fools! If we lose them we'll never force that thing out!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_PROTECTTURRETPROMPT_01">Here they come! Don't let them reach the turret!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_PROTECTTURRETPROMPT_02">Keep that filth from the turret!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_PROTECTTURRETPROMPT_03">They're attacking our turret! Fend them off!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_PROTECTTURRETPROMPT_04">Keep the Flood from the turret!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_PROTOGRAVEMIND_CHAT_01">Desperation, brother! It is finally beginning to know fear!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_RELEASEFLOODWARNING_01">It's releasing Flood forms! Ready yourselves!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_SACSEXPOSED_FOURTHCYCLE_01">Destroy those sacs! Spare nothing!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_SACSEXPOSED_SECONDCYCLE_01">We've broken through its armor! Shoot the sacs and make it bleed!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_SACSEXPOSED_THIRDCYCLE_01">Destroy those sacs! Teach it what happens when it crosses the Banished!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_SECONDCYCLE_FLOODRELEASE_01">It's releasing more Flood forms! Fight them back!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_SECONDCYCLE_INTROCHAT_01">What does it take to kill this thing?</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_SECONDCYCLE_INTROCHAT_02">Time to show the mettle of the Banished, troops! Put that monstrosity down!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_SECONDCYCLE_TARGETCARAPACE_01">Hit the armored carapace! Crack it wide open!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_SECONDCYCLE_TARGETCARAPACE_02">All units fire on its armor!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_SENTCAVALRY_01">Face us, monster! Attack while it's open, troops!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_SENTINELDEFENSES_01">We can't let them have all the fun! Let's get to work!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_SENTINELDEFENSES_02">Perhaps I misjudged these Sentinels, Pavium. If we could harness their power, perhaps we could crush the humans!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_SPOREMOUND_02">Then what are we waiting for? Attack!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_TENTACLE_VARIATIONS_01">Attack the tentacles!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_TENTATTACK_01">Be ready!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_TENTATTACK_02">It's going to strike! Pull back the ground troops!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_TENTATTACK_03">We must be doing something right for it to fight with such ferocity!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_TENTATTACK_04">Get rid of those distracting tentacles! They're protecting the beast!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_TENTATTACK_INFECT_01">It's trying to infect our aircraft and vehicles! Send in ground troops to stop it!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_THIRDCYCLE_FLOODRELEASE_01">Send all you can, monster! We will cut them all down!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_THIRDCYCLE_MORECHAT_01">Atriox will be impressed with our prowess if we survive this, Pavium!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_THIRDCYCLE_TARGETCARAPACE_01">Target the armor! I want to hear it crack!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_THIRDCYCLE_TENTACLES_01">Cut those tentacles down!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_WEAKPOINTS_KILLED_01">Ha, I think it's flinching!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_WEAKPOINTS_VARIATIONS_01">Destroy those sacs! We will see this thing fall today or we'll die trying!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_CORR_WEAKPOINTS_VARIATIONS_02">I think it's having an effect!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_ATR_REPORT_01">What is the situation?</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_ATR_REPORT_02">It was that very arrogance that caused this mess, Voridus! I'm on my way now. You will have this fixed by the time I arrive!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_CORR_BOSSBEATEN_01">We did it! We've beaten it back, brother. Atriox will be pleased!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_CORR_DEATHTHROES_01">Finally! We've hurt it!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_CORR_DEATHTHROES_02">That thing is no animal. But you're right, we must increase our assault!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_CORR_DESTROYEDARMOR_01">Then why does it not fall?</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_CORR_HUNKERDOWN_01">It has retreated!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_CORR_PROTOGRAVEMIND_01">That tentacle was just an extension of this...thing.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_CORR_PROTOGRAVEMIND_02">If the stories are true...it would be unstoppable.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_CORR_REPORT_01">Do not fear, Atriox. With the Sentinel defenses up and running, we will crush the Flood threat!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_CORR_TENTRETRACT_01">The tentacles have retracted!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_ATTACKGRAVEY_01">Hit it with everything! We must find a weakness!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_BOSSBEATEN_01">I don't think pleased is the right word, brother. Atriox will arrive soon. He may not be as merciful as the Flood.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_DEATHTHROES_01">An animal is at its most dangerous when cornered, Voridus.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_DEATHTHROES_02">Attack its crown, it seems to be the most vulnerable point!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_DESTROYEDARMOR_01">We have broken through part of its armor!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_DESTROYEDARMOR_02">The armor must have been to protect those strange sacs! Our work is not over yet, brother!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_FIGHTBACK_01">Fight back! Do not let them destroy our base!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_HUNKERDOWN_01">But it's not finished yet. Look, it's releasing more Flood!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_PROTOGRAVEMIND_01">We must focus all our efforts on it. If I'm right and it continues to grow it could become a Gravemind - the ultimate stage of the Flood life cycle.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_PROTOGRAVEMIND_02">We must test its defenses to find a way to destroy it! Attack!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_PROTOGRAVEMINDALT_01">We must focus all our efforts on it.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_REPORT_01">I've lost over forty percent of our troops, Atriox. The Flood has spread quickly in the area near High Charity.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_AIRINFECT_01">Look! The Flood has already started adapting to counter the Sentinels!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_ARMOR_01">Then it must be protecting something vital! Target the carapace!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_ARMOR_02">Hit it with our heaviest troops! We must break through its armor!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_ARMOR_03">Keep pounding it, don't let up!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_ATTACKCENTER_01">I want every unit focused on destroying that vile thing!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_ATTACKCENTER_02">We were right! They must sense where that thing can be hurt!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_ATTACKCENTER_03">At last! I began to fear it was unstoppable!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_ATTACKCENTER_04">Voridus! The Sentinels you released earlier! They're joining in the attack!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_BLOCKEDTENTACLE_01">Have faith, brother. My siege turret will carve this thing up. There's a point nearby that will provide the necessary firing position.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_BUILDTURRET_01">We need more firepower. I've located several sites where we can build another turret. Get to it!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_BUILDTURRET_02">We're nearing a turret site! Get one constructed, quickly!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_BUILDTURRET_03">A turret site! We must take advantage of it and build one now!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_BUILDTURRET_04">We're close to a turret site. Prepare it, quickly!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_BUILDTURRETPROMPT_01">We need more firepower. I've located several sites where we can build another turret. Get to it!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_BUILDTURRETPROMPT_02">I've marked new potential locations for an extra turret. Get one constructed now!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_BUILDTURRETPROMPT_03">We need another turret. There are several sites that will serve our purpose.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_BUILDTURRETPROMPT_04">It's time we increased the firepower. Build another turret at one of the other locations!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_CARAPACE_VARIATIONS_01">Target the carapace sections! We must find a vulnerability!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_CARAPACE_VARIATIONS_04">Crack the shell of that thing! Tear it apart!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_CAVALRYRETRIEVER_01">It's working!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_CLEANSELOCK_01">I'm detecting something very powerful on the way now, brother!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_CLEANSELOCK_02">Now we shall see how strong that thing is!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_FAILSTATE_01">It's too late! We have failed!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_FINALBATTLEAIR_01">We must strike from the air!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_FINALBATTLEAIR_02">Strike with all we have!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_FINALSHOWDOWN_01">It has increased its attacks! It's getting desperate!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_FINDSOURCE_01">Come, brother, we must find the source of this new Flood outbreak!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_FOURTHCYCLE_FLOODRELEASE_01">Stay alert! The thing is releasing more Flood!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_FOURTHCYCLE_INTROCHAT_01">As much as we can deal out it seems. We may need to hit it with something even more powerful!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_FOURTHCYCLE_TARGETCARAPACE_01">Aim at the armor to expose the sacs! No armor exists that Pavium has not broken!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_FOURTHCYCLE_TENTACLES_01">Will someone take out those annoying tentacles!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_FREETOROAM_01">Which gives us more sites on which to build a turret. Quickly, troops!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_GRAVEY_GROWING_01">It must be while its protected! We cannot let it reach full Gravemind!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_GRAVEY_GROWING_02">Get a turret built quickly, before its too late!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_HUNKERDOWN_FOURTHCYCLE_01">See to the injured and replace any lost troops while that turret is being built!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_HUNKERDOWN_FOURTHCYCLE_02">Cease, we are wasting firepower! While it recovers, regroup and get ready for another assault!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_HUNKERDOWN_FOURTHCYCLE_03">Fall back and get another turret built! It must be close to reaching Gravemind state now and this may be our last chance!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_HUNKERDOWN_SECONDCYCLE_01">We will need another turret! Get one built at one of the sites I've marked!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_HUNKERDOWN_THIRDCYCLE_01">It retreats! Take the time to heal wounds and build another turret! We will need all the firepower we can get!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_HUNKERDOWN_VARIATIONS_01">Fall back! We must not waste troops battling those Flood forms.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_HUNKERDOWN_VARIATIONS_02">Then we must encourage it back out again! I've found several locations where we can build a turret to force out!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_INFECTEDVEHICLE_01">The Flood have infected Wraiths! They'll destroy our infantry!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_KILLEDIT_01">Finally! It falls!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_LEGENDS_01">Legends?! If we fail, there will be nobody left to recount our folly! Do not underestimate the graveness of this situation, Voridus.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_MEGATURRET_01">Prepare the turret, we'll soon rid ourselves of those tentacles!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_MEGATURRET_02">It's retreating!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_MEGATURRET_03">Fire at will, commander.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_MEGATURRETLOS_01">Make sure we have vision on the tentacles, my turrets need to know where to aim!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_NEEDHELP_01">I was afraid of this, but I think I have the answer.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_NEEDHELP_02">I've detected a damaged Sentinel lock nearby. If we cleanse it of the Flood filth, it should call in Sentinel reinforcements.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTTURRET_01">Their intelligence is growing! Something must be guiding them!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTTURRET_02">They're attacking one of our turrets! Protect it with your lives!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTTURRET_03">The Flood is attacking one of our turrets! Wipe them out before they destroy it!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTTURRET_FOURTHCYCLE_01">Flood incoming! Protect our turrets, we must not lose them!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTTURRET_SECONDCYCLE_01">Flood incoming! Protect our turrets, we must not lose them!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTTURRET_THIRDCYCLE_01">Don't let the Flood destroy a single turret, we need every one of them to hurt that thing!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_PROTECTTURRET2_01">That thing suspects what we're doing! It's trying to destroy the turret! Protect it!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_PROTOGRAVEMIND_CHAT_01">How can it produce endless numbers of those vile things?</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_PROTOGRAVEMIND_CHAT_02">I don't believe that thing can feel fear, but perhaps it can feel pain!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_RELEASEFLOODWARNING_01">It's trying to protect itself! Carve through those wretched creatures!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_SACSEXPOSED_FOURTHCYCLE_01">Its armor has fallen! Target the sacs underneath!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_SACSEXPOSED_SECONDCYCLE_01">The carapace is destroyed! Now's our chance!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_SACSEXPOSED_SECONDCYCLE_02">Target those sacs!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_SACSEXPOSED_THIRDCYCLE_01">Its sacs are exposed! Target them!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_SECONDCYCLE_FLOODRELEASE_01">It's trying to stop us with more of it's vile offspring!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_SECONDCYCLE_INTROCHAT_01">Stay strong, brother. We know how to wound it now, we must keep going!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_SECONDCYCLE_TARGETCARAPACE_01">Send in our heavy units to break its shell! It must fall!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_SECONDCYCLE_TARGETCARAPACE_02">Target its armor! Break it open!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_SENTCAVALRY_02">It's working! It rises!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_SENTINELDEFENSES_01">Voridus, the Sentinel defenses you activated are here! They're attacking the Flood!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_SENTINELDEFENSES_02">The humans are not the one we should be worried about now. We must survive the Flood first!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_SPOREMOUND_01">That monstrosity is sitting right where I need to build the turret!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_TARGETSACS_01">Now those tentacles are out of the way, we can hit it where it hurts the most!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_TENTACLE_VARIATIONS_01">Don't let those tentacles hit you!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_TENTATTACK_01">What is it doing?</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_TENTATTACK_02">We must destroy those tentacles! Target them!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_TENTRETRACT_01">Keep those ground troops moving, they'll be crushed by the tentacles!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_TENTRETRACT_02">Target the tentacles! Keep out of their reach!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_THIRDCYCLE_FLOODRELEASE_01">Watch out! More Flood incoming!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_THIRDCYCLE_INTROCHAT_01">The Flood are relentless! Next time remind me to bring more troops!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_THIRDCYCLE_INTROCHAT_02">Next time listen to my warnings and we won't have to!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_THIRDCYCLE_MORECHAT_01">Then we'll just need to survive Atriox!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_THIRDCYCLE_TARGETCARAPACE_01">Break through its armor! We will end that monster if we have to pry it out of its shell!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_THIRDCYCLE_TENTACLES_01">Attack the tentacles so it can't defend itself!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_WEAKPOINTS_KILLED_01">Be on guard! We must be prepared for anything!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_WEAKPOINTS_VARIATIONS_01">Focus all firepower on those sacs, make it pay for our losses!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNBREA_WEAKPOINTS_VARIATIONS_02">Don't take any chances, keep hitting it!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PIP_UNRBEA_OPT_TENTACLE_01">If the Flood can form such things, it must be close to becoming a Gravemind!</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_BUILDMEGATURRET_01">Build another Mega Turret</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_BUILDMEGATURRET_01_SHORTDESCR">The Proto-Gravemind has retreated into its hole for cover. Build another Mega Turret to force it out.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_BUILDMEGATURRET_01_UPDATE">Mega Turret sites secured</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_CAVALRYRETRIEVER_01">Use the Retriever to attack the Proto-Gravemind</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_CAVALRYRETRIEVER_01_SHORTDESCR">The Proto-Gravemind has grown too strong for the Mega Turrets alone. Use the Retriever to attack it.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_CLEANSELOCK_01">Cleanse the lock to call in reinforcements</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_CLEANSELOCK_01_SHORTDESCR">Pavium believes that cleansing the Sentinel lock of Flood will enable it to call in reinforcements.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_DESTROY_GRAVEMIND_01">Destroy the Proto-Gravemind</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_DESTROY_GRAVEMIND_01_SHORTDESCR">The Proto-Gravemind is the source of the increased Flood threat, and if allowed to live will develop into a full Gravemind.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_FINDSOURCE_01">Discover the source of the increased Flood threat</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_FINDSOURCE_01_SHORTDESCR">The Flood threat has dramatically increased. Find the source of the increase to destroy it.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_MEGATURRET_01">Set up a Mega Turret at the minibase location</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_MEGATURRET_01_SHORTDESCR">Build a Mega Turret at the minibase location to destroy the tentacles blocking further exploration.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_PROTECTTURRET_01">Protect the Mega Turret</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_PROTECTTURRET_01_SHORTDESCR">Protect the Mega Turret from Flood attacks while it's being built.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_SECUREFOURTURRETSITES_01">Secure four Mega Turret sites</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_SECUREFOURTURRETSITES_SHORTDESCR_01">Extra firepower is needed to force the Proto-Gravemind out of its defensive hole. Find and secure four more sites to build Mega Turrets on.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_SECURETHREETURRETSITES_01">Secure three Mega Turret sites</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_SECURETHREETURRETSITES_SHORTDESCR_01">Extra firepower is needed to force the Proto-Gravemind out of its defensive hole. Find and secure three more sites to build Mega Turrets on.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_SECURETURRETSITES_01">Secure Mega Turret sites</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_SECURETURRETSITES_SHORTDESCR_01">Extra firepower is needed to force the Proto-Gravemind out of its defensive hole. Find and secure more sites to build Mega Turrets on.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_SECURETWOTURRETSITES_01">Secure two Mega Turret sites</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_SECURETWOTURRETSITES_SHORTDESCR_01">Extra firepower is needed to force the Proto-Gravemind out of its defensive hole. Find and secure two more sites to build Mega Turrets on.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_TARGETCARAPACE_01">Attack the carapace sections</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_TARGETCARAPACE_SHORTDESCR_01">The Proto-Gravemind has armored carapace sections which must be protecting a weak spot. Target and attack them.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_TARGETCENTER_01">Attack the center of the Proto-Gravemind</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_TARGETCENTER_SHORTDESCR_01">The center part of the Proto-Gravemind is the most vulnerable area. Target and attack it.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_TARGETSACS_01">Attack the sacs</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_TARGETSACS_SHORTDESCR_01">The sacs revealed by the carapace sections seem to be a weak spot. Target and attack them.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_PRIMOBJ_TEX_HINTATTACK">ATTACK</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_TEX_CRITICALMASSTIMER_TITLE">PROTO-GRAVEMIND CRITICAL MASS</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_TEX_PROTOGRAVEMINDHEALTH_01">Proto-Gravemind Health</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_TEX_PROTOGRAVEMINDWEAKPOINT_01">Weakpoint</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_TEX_TUT_ATTACKCENTER_01">The attacks have forced the Proto-Gravemind to expose its vulnerable area. Target the center of the Proto-Gravemind to hurt it.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_TEX_TUT_CATACLYSM_01">Voridus' Catacyclsm leader power ignites all incendiary gel pools on the battefield to flare up, increasing their damage.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_TEX_TUT_CRITICALMASSTIMER_01">Force the Proto-Gravemind from its hole using Mega Turrets before it reaches critical mass and full Gravemind form.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_TEX_TUT_MEGATURRET2_01">Build another Mega Turret to force the Proto-Gravemind from its hole.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_TEX_TUT_RETRIEVER_01">Use the Retriever's special abiltiy with @special_power@ to finish off the Proto-Gravemind.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_TEX_TUT_TARGETCARAPACE_01">The Proto-Gravemind's carapace sections are protecting something underneath, destroy them to reveal its weakness.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_TEX_TUT_TARGETSACS_01">The Proto-Gravemind's sacs seem to be a vulnerable point. Target and destroy them.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_TUT_TEX_INFECTEDVEHICLE_01">Infesters are the equivalent of Flood vehicles and are effective against infantry units. Counter them with anti-vehicle units such as Hunters and Banshees.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_TUT_TEX_MEGATURRET_01">Mega Turrets will automatically fire on targets within your units' line of sight.</str>
	<str id="EP2M05_TUT_TEX_MEGATURRET_02">Mega Turrets need line of sight on the Proto-Gravemind to fire.</str>
</string_table>