<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<str id="EP2M04_CORR_CALLOUT_KILL_SUCCESS_GENERIC_02">Is there no-one that can challenge me?</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_CORR_INCIDENTAL_SUCCESS_CHEERS_01">Voridus triumphs again!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_CORR_LEADER_DOMINATION_POINT_WON_GAME_NORMAL_01">Victory was ours, well fought, pack.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_OPTOBJ_CLEARQUARANTINE_01">Clear all the Flood within the time limit</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_OPTOBJ_CLEARQUARANTINE_01_SHORTDESCR">Clear all the Flood within the quarantine time limit to deactivate the shield dome and reveal a secret.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_OPTOBJ_CORRUPTION_01">Kill units with any source of incendiary gel</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_OPTOBJ_CORRUPTION_01_SHORTDESCR">Kill units using any weapons, special abilites or leader powers associated with incendiary gel.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_OPTOBJ_KEEPEVERYTHINGCLEAN_01">Keep all locks clean of the Flood</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_OPTOBJ_KEEPEVERYTHINGCLEAN_01_SHORTDESCR">Do not let any of the locks become blocked by the Flood at any time.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_OPTOBJ_NOUNITSLOSTTOBEAMS_01">Don't lose any units to the Forerunner beams</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_OPTOBJ_NOUNITSLOSTTOBEAMS_01_SHORTDESCR">The Forerunner Beams are incredibly deadly, and you'll need all your units against the Flood.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_OPTOBJ_USEFORERUNNER_01">Use Forerunner terminals to combat the Flood</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_OPTOBJ_USEFORERUNNER_01_SHORTDDESCR">Use Forerunner terminals to temporarily call in Sentinel drones to combat the Flood.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_BRUTE_JUMPBRUTESLIGHTBRIDGE1_01">Lightbridge activated, Voridus!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_BRUTE_JUMPBRUTESLIGHTBRIDGE1_02">What's that sound?</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_BRUTE_SCOUTINGINFO_01">Voridus, we see a Forerunner structure ahead in a large chamber. But it is surrounded by Flood sacs.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_BRUTE_THIRDLIGHTBRIDGE_01">Voridus, the lightbridge controls aren’t working!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_BRUTE_THIRDLIGHTBRIDGE_02">Voridus! They come!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_BRUTE_THIRDLIGHTBRIDGE_03">They are endless!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_BEWAREOFSACS_01">Keep your distance from the blisters.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_CHEEZEIT_01">Move, before we are caught in the middle! Let the Sentinels take care of them!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_CLEANLOCKS_01">They've covered one of the locks! Cleanse it!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_CLEANLOCKS_02">The lock has been compromised! Clean it!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_CLEANLOCKS_03">The Flood have covered one of the locks! Free it up!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_CLEANNODES_01">Blast away the Flood matter! Pavium, there is another teleporter down here.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_CLEANNODES_02">Blast away that filth! We need it clear so I can reactivate the defense system!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_CLEANNODES_03">It's working, Pavium. The power is increasing. Once this device is at full power I should be able to reenable the defenses.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_CLEANNODES_04">Keep blasting, we're nearly done!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_CLEANNODES_05">Cleanse the area! The locks must be freed!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_CLEANNODES_06">Hold fast, brother, just a little longer.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_CLIFFSPAWNER_01">Wait. I hear something.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_CLIFFSPAWNER_02">I could smell the trap… The Flood were waiting to ambush us!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_CLIFFSPAWNER_03">I should have trusted my instincts! That infester was part of an ambush! Destroy those spawners!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_CORRSPECABILITY_01">I'll start spreading my incendiary gel to head them off. Stand back!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_CORRSPECABILITY_02">Vile things! You won't get past me!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_CORRVSFLOOD_01">Come and burn, filth! A special mix of my own, just for you!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_CORRVSFLOOD_02">Pavium, my modified incendiary gel works wonders against the Flood!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_CORRVSFLOOD_03">And where would we be without it now? You must learn to break a few rules, brother!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_DEACTIVATE_BEAMS_01">The path is clear, continue on.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_DEFENSETERMINAL_01">That Forerunner structure may help our efforts to reactivate the defenses.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FACILITYDEFENSES_01">Pavium, the way forward is not clear. We have many Forerunner beam defenses and retracted lightbridges.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FINALHIVECOMMANDERS_01">Abominations! Concentrate fire on them!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FINALHIVECOMMANDERS_02">More abominations on the way!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FINALHIVECOMMANDERS_03">They're sending in more of those abominations!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FINALHIVECOMMANDERS_04">They must be desperate! They're sending in their abominations!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FINALSENTINELBEAMS_01">Pavium, the Forerunner defenses are stronger here. We must be getting close to the core.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FINALTELEPORTER_02">And you, brother. I will see this done.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FLOODCARRIER_KILLED_01">Come, let us move fast before the Flood completely engulfs this place!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FLOODONBRIDGE_01">Here they come now, wipe them out before they reach us!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FLOODTHREAT_01">Here they come, raze them!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FLOODTHREAT_02">Infectors! Wipe them out before they reach us!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FLOODTHREAT_03">Keep them away from the locks!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FLOODWARNINGS_01">Here they come, cut them down!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FLOODWARNINGS_02">Don't let them touch you!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FLOODWARNINGS_03">Wipe them out!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FLOODWARNINGS_04">Listen! I hear the foul sounds of Flood up ahead!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FLOODWEB_01">The Flood is making itself at home here. Destroy that filth so we can reach those resources!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FLOODWEB_02">Crush them!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FORERUNNERBEAMS_01">Forerunner beams ahead.  It seems some defenses remain active.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FORERUNNERBEAMS_02">The terminals are on a failsafe. They must be activated at the same time.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FORERUNNERBEAMS_TERMINAL_01">Check the nearby terminal to see if can turn off these beams.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FORERUNNERFIELD_01">We're blocked by Forerunner beams! Turn them off! We have to get inside!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FORERUNNERFIELD_02">What now?</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_FORERUNNERSTRUCTURE_01">Get ready, we need to investigate.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_GELPROMPT_01">My incendiary gel will make short work of these monstrosities.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_GELPROMPT_02">Come, filth. My gel awaits you! I have enough for every one of you!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_GELPROMPT_03">My gel has recharged and is ready for deployment.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_GELPROMPT_04">Stay vigilant, my gel awaits victims to burn!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_GRENADIERHINT_01">Grenadiers! Attack at range!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_HEADSUPSENT_PROMPT_01">There's a Forerunner terminal ahead in a large chamber, but it's surrounded by blisters. We should investigate it.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_HEALPROMPTS_01">We've sustained some injuries. Take a moment to heal!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_HEALPROMPTS_02">We've injured troops. We should heal while we can.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_HEALPROMPTS_03">Assess your injuries and heal them if needed!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_HIVECOMMANDATTACKING_01">Here it comes!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_HIVECOMMANDATTACKING_02">Keep clear of the blisters or the Abomination will rally the forms they release!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_HIVECOMMANDERCLOSE_01">Careful. It's close.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_HIVECOMMANDERWARNING_01">Wait!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_HIVECOMMANDERWARNING_02">There's another of those abominations. Be careful, those things seem to make any nearby Flood forms more aggressive!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_HIVECOMMANDERWARNING_03">Be sure not to break any blisters or the abomination will have more Flood to rally against us!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_HIVECOMMANDSNEAK_01">We haven't been spotted yet, keep going.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_HIVECOMMANDSPOTTED_01">We've been seen! Attack!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_HONORGUARD_01">An Honor Guard's cloaking ability could prove useful to us. Get ready to earn your keep, mercenary!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_HONORGUARD_02">Honor Guard, now is the time to use your cloak!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_IDISTURBEDEGGS_01">We've disturbed the Flood blisters! Destroy them all!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_INCOMINGFLOOD_01">The Flood is coming in from the corridor!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_INCOMINGFLOOD_02">Incoming at the corridor!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_INCOMINGFLOOD_03">More Flood from the vents!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_INCOMINGFLOOD_04">The Flood is pouring through the vents!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_INCOMINGFLOOD_05">Check the vents, the Flood is coming through there!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_INCOMINGFLOOD_06">More Flood incoming!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_INCUBATION_01">Tread carefully, if we disturb the sacs, they may release Flood. Although it is tempting to burn them all now...</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_INFECTEDUNSC_01">They're sending more infected forms now!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_INFECTEDUNSC_02">Watch out, infected forms!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_INFECTEDUNSC_03">More of their twisted forms!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_INFECTEDUNSC_04">Put those wretches out of their misery!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_INFECTEDUNSC_05">Enemy or no, no soldier should deserve that fate! Kill them quickly!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_ISITATRAP_01">Something's not right here. Tread carefully.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_JUMPBRUTE_01">Which way now?</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_JUMPBRUTE_HINT_01">Welcome to my pack, Jump Brutes. Your role is vital to this mission.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_JUMPBRUTE_SEARCH_01">Jump Brutes, there is another path ahead. We may need your unique skills.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_JUMPBRUTECOLLECT_01">Gather what resources you can. We'll need them to power up any more teleporters we find down here.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_JUMPBRUTEPROMPT_DAMAGE_01">Jump Brutes! Protect yourselves!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_JUMPBRUTEPROMPT_DAMAGE_02">Defend yourselves, Jump Brutes! I still have need of you!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_JUMPBRUTEPROMPT_DAMAGE_03">Jump Brutes! I have no use for you if you are dead!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_JUMPBRUTEPROMPT_LOSTONE_01">We've lost a Jump Brute! Careful, we will not be able to complete our mission without them!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_JUMPBRUTEPROMPT_LOSTONE_02">A Jump Brute has fallen! Be sure the rest of you don't fail me!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_JUMPBRUTEPROMPT_LOSTONE_03">We've lost a Jump Brute! This will make things more difficult.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_JUMPBRUTEPROMPT_LOSTONE_04">Die on your own time, Jump Brutes! We need you now!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_JUMPBRUTEPROMPT_ONELEFT_01">Only one Jump Brute remains! Protect him at all costs, he is vital to our mission!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_JUMPBRUTEPROMPT_ONELEFTINJURED_01">Our last Jump Brute is injured. Keep him alive, or we must abandon the mission!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_JUMPBRUTESCAREFUL_01">Be careful, I will have need of your mobility as we work our way through this place.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_JUMPBRUTESLIGHTBRIDGE1_01">Jump Brutes, investigate the console on that pillar. We need to find a way forward.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_JUMPBRUTESLIGHTBRIDGE1_02">Ready your hammers, Jump Brutes! The Flood is climbing up towards your position!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_LIGHTBRIDGEKEEPFIGHTING_01">Hold your tongue and fight, fool!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_LOSEJUMP_FAIL_01">Pavium, we have no way of continuing. We are returning to you for reinforcements.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_NEARLYDONE_01">They've nearly taken all the locks! Push them back or the power will stop coming!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_NEARLYDONE_02">We must not let them take all the locks! We need that power!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_NEARLYDONE_03">They've nearly taken all the locks! Force them back or we'll never get the power running!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_PROTECTLOCKS_01">The Flood are trying to block one of the locks!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_PROTECTLOCKS_02">The locks! They're under assault from the Flood!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_PROTECTLOCKS_03">Keep them away from the locks!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_PROTECTLOCKS_04">Stop them! They must not reach the locks!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_QUARANTINE_01">We've triggered a quarantine!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_QUARANTINE_02">We must clear the area of Flood or the automatic defenses will attack us as well!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_QUARANTINE_03">We were too late! The defenses are being activated!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_QUARANTINE_04">Keep away from the beams until the quarantine is lifted!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_QUARANTINE_05">This is the power we need. Let’s hope it doesn’t kill us before we can use it against the Flood.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_QUARANTINE_06">The quarantine has lifted and the field is down, let's move!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_RESOURCES_01">All of them? But what of you?</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_SECONDFORERUNNERBEAMS_01">Hold, I smell burning. There are Forerunner beams up ahead.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_SECONDFORERUNNERBEAMS_02">Honor Guard, you're fast on your feet. Prove your usefulness!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_SECONDFORERUNNERSTRUCTURE_01">Another of those Forerunner terminals.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_SENTINELBEAMS_04">Ha, challenge accepted, brother!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_SENTINELSWARM_01">Pavium, we've activated a minor defense system. It seems to be a localized patrol, we still need to activate the global system.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_SENTINELSWARM_02">A minor victory. I hope the main defense system proves just as effective.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_SENTINELTERMAHEAD_01">There's another Sentinel terminal up ahead.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_SPECSPREAD_01">I need to create a large pool to burn those foul things! I won't leave any space for them to get through!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_SUGGESTHONGUARD_01">You have reinforcements ready for me then?</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_TELEPORTER_01">Pavium, we've found a teleporter down here. It appears to be connected to the one near you. I need reinforcements.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_TENTACLES_01">Pavium! The Flood's tentacles have reached down here now! Have any more appeared up there?</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_THIRDLIGHTBRIDGE_01">Another chasm! Jump Brutes, get across and activate the lightbridge!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_THIRDLIGHTBRIDGE_02">The Flood is corrupting everything! We must move fast before the whole facility is a lost cause!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_THIRDLIGHTBRIDGE_03">Then destroy them! I will not fall to these aberrations!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_THIRDLIGHTBRIDGE_04">Keep fighting until that lightbridge starts working! The Flood infection must have compromised the facilities' systems.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_THIRDLIGHTBRIDGE_05">Cross quickly, the systems are unstable and I do not relish a plunge into the depths below!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_THIRDLIGHTBRIDGE_06">That looked like the last chasm, Jump Brutes. You will have to measure your worth in kills now!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_THIRDLIGHTBRIDGE_07">The lightbridge is working again!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_THIRDLIGHTBRIDGE_08">Hurry! That lightbridge will not remain on forever!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_THIRDLIGHTBRIDGE_09">It's shut down behind us. At least it should buy us some time.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_TURNONDEFENSES_01">Pavium! The system is at full power! I’m reactivating it now!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_TURNONDEFENSES_02">Yes, this is familiar. Time to fight, Sentinels.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_USEFORERUNNERBEAMS_01">We're going to need more firepower! That Forerunner terminal may aid us.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_USEFORERUNNERBEAMS_02">It's working, but it's draining power from the main defense system. We must use it sparingly!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_CORR_USEJUMPBRUTES_01">This facility is pitted with many chasms. Jump Brutes, be ready.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_BRUTE_MOPROBLEMS_01">Voridus, Pavium! We are being overrun, some kind of giant Flood form has appeared and...</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_CORR_ARRIVAL_01">I have arrived, Pavium. It stinks of death down here. The enemy is everywhere.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_CORR_CLIFFSPAWNER_01">Wait, something's not right here.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_CORR_CORRVSFLOOD_01">Steel yourselves! Infection forms! I'll cut them off before they overrun us.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_CORR_FINALROOMARRIVE_01">Pavium, I think we've found it. It resembles the system I shut down before.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_CORR_FINALROOMARRIVE_02">Strange, it's almost as if the Flood understands its importance. The locks are blocked with their filth.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_CORR_FLOODCARRIER_01">The Flood has already started to choke this place. Watch your step.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_CORR_HOLDTHELINE_01">Pavium, the defense system is back on! The Sentinel cleansing operation should commence soon.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_CORR_HOLDTHELINE_02">It seems the Flood are aware of the threat, they rush to stop us!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_CORR_HOLDTHELINE_03">It is done! The defense system is working again!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_CORR_MOPROBLEMS_01">What was that?</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_CORR_MOPROBLEMS_02">We must act fast!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_CORR_SENTINELBEAMS_01">Impressive! Pavium, the Forerunner beams make swift work of the Flood here!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_CORR_SENTINELBEAMS_02">We are more agile than those shuffling monstrosities! I'll send one of my squad through to deactivate them from the other side!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_ARRIVAL_01">We will stop the Flood together, Voridus. My troops and I will guard the entrance up here, but you must reactivate those defenses quickly.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_FINALROOMARRIVE_01">There is cunning in their chaos, Voridus. The Flood seems to be growing in intelligence. You must clean those locks and reactivate the defenses, now!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_HOLDTHELINE_01">Sentinels are appearing up here as well, brother! We must help them battle the Flood and...</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_MOPROBLEMS_01">That was from one of our bases. It seems our work is not yet finished.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_MOPROBLEMS_02">Atriox is sending support as we speak. We are going to need all the help we can get.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_SENTINELBEAMS_01">As they will you, Voridus. Can you get past them?</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_IGC_UNBREA_SENTINELBEAMS_02">You surprise me, Voridus. I thought you would want to test your mighty reflexes against the beams.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_UNBREA_CLEANNODES_01">Hurry, Voridus. The Flood is amassing here.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_UNBREA_CLIFFSPAWNER_01">Voridus, two more bases have fallen silent. Hurry, the Flood is getting closer.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_UNBREA_CORRVSFLOOD_01">At least there's finally a use for it. Colony was not pleased to learn you had been tinkering with his weapons.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_UNBREA_FACILITYDEFENSES_01">A good sign. It means the facility is still partly functional. We may still be able to restore the defenses.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_UNBREA_FINALSENTINELBEAMS_01">Make haste, Voridus. We're falling back to the entrance for a final defensive position.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_UNBREA_FINALTELEPORTER_02">I am sending my finest warriors for you, Voridus. I have also outfitted some Brutes with new equipment, inspired by your 'experiments'. Fight well.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_UNBREA_FINALTELEPORTER_03">You must not fail, Voridus. Fight well.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_UNBREA_RESOURCES_01">Voridus, I'm sending you all my reserves. Make good use of them.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_UNBREA_RESOURCES_02">If you fail, we will quickly fall next. You must be our shield now.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_UNBREA_SENTINELSWARM_01">Keep searching, Voridus. We've just lost contact with another base, you must act quickly.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_UNBREA_SUGGESTHONGUARD_01">Then I suggest using an Honor Guard. Their cloaking abilities will enable them to reach the terminal undetected.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_UNBREA_SUGGESTHONGUARD_02">Yes, the teleporter's working, but I can't spare many fighters.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_UNBREA_SUGGESTHONGUARD_03">If the Flood return here, I will need every one to hold them back.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_UNBREA_TELEPORTER_02">Scout ahead while I get it working.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_UNBREA_TENTACLES_01">Many more. Hurry, Voridus. You must move quickly down there.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PIP_UNBREA_TURNONDEFENSES_01">Then reactivate the defenses! The Flood is almost here!</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PRIMOBJ_CLEANNODES_01">Destroy the Flood covering the locks</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PRIMOBJ_CLEANNODES_01_SHORTDESCR">The Flood are preventing the locks from functioning. Cleanse the locks of Flood.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PRIMOBJ_COMPLETEPUZZLE_01">Solve the Forerunner interface puzzle</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PRIMOBJ_COMPLETEPUZZLE_01_SHORTDESCR">Solve the Forerunner interface puzzle to reactivate the Sentinel defenses.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PRIMOBJ_DEFENDLOCKS_01">Defend the locks</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PRIMOBJ_DEFENDLOCKS_01_SHORTDESCR">Defend the locks from the Flood while the power comes back online.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PRIMOBJ_FINDSOURCE_01">Locate the central Forerunner defense system</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PRIMOBJ_FINDSOURCE_01_SHORTDESCR">Explore the Forerunner facility to find and reactivate the central Sentinel Flood defenses.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PRIMOBJ_FORERUNNERBEAMS_01">Turn off the beams using the terminal</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PRIMOBJ_FORERUNNERBEAMS_01_SHORTDESCR">Some Forerunner defenses are still active. Look for terminals to turn off beam defenses.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PRIMOBJ_FORERUNNERBEAMS_03">Deactivate the Forerunner beams at the terminal</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PRIMOBJ_FORERUNNERBEAMS_03_SHORTDESCR">Some Forerunner defenses are still active. Look for terminals to turn off beam defenses.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PRIMOBJ_JUMPBRUTES_01">Keep your Jump Pack Brutes alive</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PRIMOBJ_JUMPBRUTES_01_SHORTDESCR">The Jump Pack Brutes are vital for navigating this facility. Keep them alive or you will have to abandon the mission.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PRIMOBJ_TURNONDEFENSES_01">Reactivate the Sentinel defenses with Voridus</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_PRIMOBJ_TURNONDEFENSES_01_SHORTDESCR">Use Voridus to reactivate the Sentinel defenses so they can help push back the Flood threat.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TITLE_FACILITY_POWER_01">FACILITY POWER</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TITLE_JPBS_REMAINING_01">JUMP BRUTES REMAINING</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TITLE_LIGHTBRIDGE_TIMER_01">LIGHTBRIDGE DEACTIVATES IN:</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TITLE_POWER_NODE_01">LOCK A HEALTH</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TITLE_POWER_NODE_02">LOCK B HEALTH</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TITLE_POWER_NODE_03">LOCK C HEALTH</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TITLE_QUARANTINE_TIMER_01">QUARANTINE TRIGGERS IN:</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_CATACLYSM_01">Voridus' Catacyclsm leader power ignites all incendiary gel pools on the battlefield to flare up, increasing their damage.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_CODEX_01">Clear all of the flood within the time limit to deactivate the shield dome and uncover a secret.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_CORRPOWERS_01">Leader Powers are powerful against mass Flood attacks.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_CORRSPECABILITY_01">Use @special_power@ to activate Voridus' Salt the Earth special ability, then move him to spread pools of damaging gel.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_CORRSPECABILITY_02">Move Voridus around when using his Salt the Earth special ability to leave behind large pools of damaging gel.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_CORRVSFLOOD_01">Use Voridus' Salt the Earth special ability to destroy the approaching Flood</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_CORRVSFLOOD_01_SHORTDESCR">Voridus' Salt the Earth special ability leaves pools of damaging incendiary gel on the ground. Use it to destroy and lay traps for the Flood.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_CORVORTEX_01">Infusion Wake spreads incendiary gel as you guide it around the map.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_EXPLOSIVES_01">Explosive Power Cores</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_FINALTELEPORTERS_01">Teleporters can be used multiple times</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_FINALTELEPORTERS_02">Reinforce your army using the teleporters</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_FORERUNNERDEFENCE_01">Forerunner defense system</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_GRENADIERS_01">Grenadiers can absorb Voridus' gel to temporarily increase their speed, armor and damage. Press @special_power@ to activate their special ability</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_HEAL_01">You can heal your Jump Brutes with Atriox's Bulwark.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_HIVECOMMANDERS_01">Abominations increase the speed and armor of other Flood forms and have a devastating slam attack.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_HONORGUARDCLOAK_01">Honor Guards can cloak themselves to prevent detection by other units. Press @special_power@ to activate their special ability.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_JUMPBRUTES_01">Jump Brutes can leap across large chasms. Press @special_power@ to activate their special ability.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_LASERS_01">Send one unit through to deactivate the beams at the terminal ahead.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_SPREADCORR_01">Move Voridus to spread his Infusion Gel.</str>
	<str id="EP2M04_TEX_TUT_TELEPORTERREINFORCE_01">Move within range of the teleporter and press 
@A_LMB@ to teleport in units from above.</str>
</string_table>