<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
    <str id="M01_BRU2_CAMP_ATTACK_02">The humans return for another beating!</str>
    <str id="M01_BRUTE_CAMP_ATTACK_01">We&apos;re under attack!</str>
    <str id="M01_BRUTE_CAMP_ATTACK_03">Protect our supplies! Push them back!</str>
    <str id="M01_BRUTE_CAMP_ATTACK_04">Decimus will have our hides if they get damaged!</str>
    <str id="M01_COMMS_HORNETS_SUPPRESSION_01">Lay down suppressing fire, squadron!</str>
    <str id="M01_COMMS_MARSQ_CAMP_ATTACK_02">Not so tough in a fair fight, are you?</str>
    <str id="M01_COMMS_SPAJ_HUNTERS_INTRO_01">Fire on the move, their cannons will tear right through our armor!</str>
    <str id="M01_FLAVOUR_MAR02_COVWRECKAGE_01">Did you hear that? The Master Chief was here!</str>
    <str id="M01_HORN_COMMS_FIRSTSUPPORT_01">Hornet squadron here, laying down suppressing fire.</str>
    <str id="M01_HORN_COMMS_SECONDSUPPORT_01">Light them up, Hornets.</str>
    <str id="M01_IGC_BRUTE_WRECKAGE_01">Humans! Stop them or Decimus will have our heads!</str>
    <str id="M01_KODIA_DEPLOY_01">Kodiak deploying. Standing by for orders.</str>
    <str id="M01_KODIA_FIRING_01">Tracking hostiles.</str>
    <str id="M01_MAR02_CAMP_ATTACK_01">Keep up the pressure!</str>
    <str id="M01_MAR02_CAMP_COMPLETE_01">That&apos;s one for the outpost!</str>
    <str id="M01_MAR03_CAMP_COMPLETE_01">Did you see the surprise on their faces? Oh man!</str>
    <str id="M01_MAR03_HUNTERS_DEAD_01">Phew, I&apos;ve seen a pair of those things take out a whole tank crew before.</str>
    <str id="M01_MAR03_HUNTERS_INTRO_01">T</str>
    <str id="M01_MAR03_HUNTERS_INTRO_RESPONSE_01">Not exactly top of my list!</str>
    <str id="M01_MAR04_CAMP_ATTACK_01">Yeah! I lost some good buddies at that base!</str>
    <str id="M01_MAR04_CAMP_COMPLETE_01">It was over too quickly for them if you ask me.</str>
    <str id="M01_MAR04_HUNTERS_INTRO_CALL_01">Don&apos;t let their blasts hit you!</str>
    <str id="M01_MARSQ_CAMP_ATTACK_01">Now! Move, move!</str>
    <str id="M01_MARSQ_HUNTERS_INTRO_01">Keep moving, marines!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_AND_DAMAGEDVEHICLE_01">J</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_AND_LIGHTBRIDGE_01">That Forerunner tower up ahead is generating an incredible energy signature. If you can secure it, we might be able to tap into that power.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CHAT_DEC_BASEOPENTAUNT_01">You leave your base wide open for my forces? Ha! How did you ever win the war?</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CHAT_DEC_BASEOPENTAUNT_02">If you value your base so little, I will gladly take it from you!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CHAT_DEC_TAUNT_01">I will hollow out your skulls and let the short one use them as toys!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CHAT_DEC_TAUNT_02">This is futile! The Ark is ours now - and you will not take it from us!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CHAT_DEC_TAUNT_04">The Ark is ours, humans, and no one will stand before the might of the Banished!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CHAT_IGC_DEC_BOSSBATTLE_01">Why not flee? You demonstrated great skill in that before!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CHAT_IGC_ISA_END_01">Oh, this isn&apos;t good. I&apos;m only recovering bits and pieces of data, but it all points to a Cartographer.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CHAT_IGC_ISA_END_02">N</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CHAT_IGC_SPAJ_END_01">We&apos;ve found something, Captain. Uploading now. Isabel, can you decrypt this for us?</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CHAT_IGC_SPAJ_END_02">T</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_BARRACKS_PROMPT_01">Jerome, build that Barracks so we can get more infantry on the field.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_BARRACKS_PROMPT_02">You&apos;re going to need advanced infantry squads. Build a Barracks on one of the empty base sockets.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_BASETUTORIAL_01">This is a good location to establish a base of our own. It&apos;s the heart of your operation and once it&apos;s constructed you can call in more structures to build an army.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_BASETUTORIAL_02">Now that the base is constructed, Supply Pads are online. Build one now.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_BASETUTORIAL_03">Supply Pads will bring in a steady stream of supplies to help you build your army.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_BASETUTORIAL_04">Now call in a Generator so you can start producing power.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_BASETUTORIAL_05">You&apos;ll need power as well as supplies to build more specialized units.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_BASETUTORIAL_06">Now that we&apos;ve got resources coming in, build a Barracks to field advanced infantry squads.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_BASETUTORIAL_07">Infantry are your frontline in battle and one of your most adaptable units on the field.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_BASETUTORIAL_08">You&apos;ve got a good baseline now, Jerome. Bring in more resources, Barracks or set up some automated turrets to help protect your base as you see fit.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_BASETUTORIAL_10">You can also build a Garage to reinforce your Warthogs.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_BASETUTORIAL_PROMPT_01">Jerome, start building a base at that empty base plot.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_BASETUTORIAL_PROMPT_02">We need to establish a base to build more troops, Jerome. Start building one on the empty base plot.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_CAPTUREPOWER_PROMPT_01">Jerome, we&apos;re going to need all the power we can get. You should secure that power node.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_CAPTUREPOWER_PROMPT_02">That power node isn&apos;t going to help us unless we capture it, Jerome.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_DECORDERSSTRIKE_01">Decimus is ordering a bombardment on his own position from the carrier! Fall back!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_DECUSFIRSTEAVESDROP_01">Can you intercept, Isabel?</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_DECUSFIRSTEAVESDROP_02">W</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_FIRSTBASE_01">Remember your marines are equipped with grenades, use them to destroy that base.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_FIRSTOPTIONALPOWER_02">Not to mention bolstering our own income. Secure as many as you can find.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_HELLBRINGERSVBASE_01">Jerome, use your Hellbringers&apos; flamethrowers to burn down that base.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_MARINES_ENEMYCAMPFOUND01">Roger that, Strike One. Take them out.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_MOVEINTOGARRISON_10">Move some troops into those empty garrisons, Jerome. They&apos;ll be better protected against the Banished base there.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_POSTBOMB_01">Jerome, use the Restoration Drones to fix the damage to the base.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_POWERPROMPT_01">Your base needs to start producing power. Build a Generator now.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_POWERPROMPT_02">It&apos;s vital you build a Generator, Jerome. Build one on an empty base socket.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_REINFORCE_01">Jerome, the enemy has troops garrisoned up ahead. I&apos;m dropping in support to help you clear them out.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_REINFORCE_ADD01">We&apos;re hitting the Banished hard across the ops area, keep an eye out for opportunities to coordinate fire.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_SALVAGEOPERATION_01">S</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_SILOS_02">Collect what you can, we&apos;re going to need all the help we can get.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_SUPPLYPROMPT_01">We need that Supply Pad, Jerome. Call one in on one of the empty base sockets.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_SUPPLYPROMPT_02">We won&apos;t be able to build an army without supplies. We need a Supply Pad.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_WARTHOGDROP_01">Strike One, you&apos;re closing in on Decimus&apos; salvage operation, so I&apos;m sending in some Warthogs to help you scout ahead.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_CUT_WRECKWARNING_01">Jerome, we&apos;re detecting a high number of hostiles beyond that wreck. Use your Warthogs to scout out a flanking path.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_DEC_BOMBTAUNT_01">Run as you did before!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_DEC_BOMBTAUNT_02">You will burn like all we killed here!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_DEC_BOMBTAUNT_03">Burn, fools!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_DEC_DECUSFIRSTEAVESDROP_01">Salvage teams, this is Decimus! Why have you ceased production? Explain yourselves!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_DEC_ENGINEERSATTACKED_01">I will break you!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_DEC_MOREENGINEERS_01">Enginners! Now!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_DEC_ORBSTRIKECALL_01">Shipmaster! Keep firing! Incinerate them!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_DEC_ORBSTRIKECALL_02">Now, Shipmaster! Raze them!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_DEC_ORBSTRIKECALL_03">Orbital strike on my mark!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_DEC_POWERNODE_01">Do NOT let the humans interfere with our power supply! Get down there and END THEM!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_DEC_POWERNODE_02">If we lose our supplies to the humans, I will see to it that everyone responsible is skinned! Crush them!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_DEC_POWERNODE_03">Why are you letting them take our power? Wipe them out!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_DEC_RESPONDSTOCAPTURES_01">Atriox shouldn&apos;t have let you escape at the human base! He may have thought it enough to toy with you, but I won&apos;t be so kind!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_DEC_RESPONDSTOCAPTURES_03">Damaged? BAH! I am Jiralhanae! I have been killing your kind for years!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_DEC_USESGRAVITYHAMMER_01">Come to me, worms!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_DEC_WARLORD_TAUNT_01">You have cost me greatly today, humans! Warlord! Bring me their heads!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_IGC_AND_LIGHTBRIDGEON_01">Looks like the Banished are using those nodes to pull power from the Ark - but now I can reconfigure them to supply our bases on the ground.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_IGC_CUT_END_01">Watch out, you&apos;ve got incoming!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_IGC_CUT_END_02">Decimus must be trying to hide something. Search what&apos;s left.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_IGC_CUT_GHOSTSCOUT_02">Plasma bombardment on the way! Take cover, Strike One!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_IGC_CUT_INTRO_01">Listen up, team. The Banished are dug in deep and dead set on controlling this installation, and we cannot allow that to happen.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_IGC_CUT_INTRO_02">Strike One, your job is to establish a forward base. Expect resistance.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_IGC_CUT_INTRO_SPLIT_01">One of Atriox&apos;s generals, Decimus, led the attack on the UNSC outpost, so it&apos;s time for payback.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_IGC_DEC_END_01">I</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_IGC_DEC_GHOSTSCOUT_01">So, you&apos;ve crawled out your hiding places for another battering? I thought we bloodied you enough last time.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_IGC_DEC_GHOSTSCOUT_02">That was a taste of our power, humans. If you want more, I&apos;ll be waiting.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_IGC_DEC_ORBSTRIKE_FIRST_01">Shipmaster! Put an end to these creatures!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_IGC_ISA_BOSSBATTLE_01">He looks bigger than the last time I saw him.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_IGC_ISA_END_01">Monster. Killing his own as casually as he kills us.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_IGC_ISA_GHOSTSCOUT_02">Captain, I&apos;m detecting a significant energy build up in orbit above our base!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_IGC_SPAJ_BOSSBATTLE_01">I</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_IGC_SPAJ_END_01">I thought you never ran, Decimus?</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_IGC_SPAJ_END_02">Now he&apos;s bombing his own base?</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_IGC_SPAJ_LIGHTBRIDGEON_02">Thanks, Professor. I&apos;ll keep an eye out for more. Now let&apos;s find a way to get across that canyon.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_ISA_ANTIVEHICLE_01">Jerome, your vehicles won&apos;t be able to get past that shield. You&apos;ll need to destroy its power supply with your ground troops.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_ISA_COVWRECKAGE_01">There was a battle here near the end of the war. The Master Chief saved us all.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_ISA_DAMAGEDVEHICLE_01">J</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_ISA_DECUSFIRSTEAVESDROP_01">Captain, I&apos;m picking up a broadcast to local Banished channels.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_ISA_DECUSFIRSTEAVESDROP_02">Routing to you now.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_ISA_PLASMASTRIKE_02">I&apos;m detecting another energy build up, take cover!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_ISA_POSTBOMB_01">Nothing our restoration drones can&apos;t repair, we were lucky this time. That plasma beam came from the Banished&apos;s carrier ship, the one that attacked my outpost!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_ISA_POSTBOMB_02">T</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_ISA_RECRUITMARINES_01">Marine infantry squads now available from your main HQ building.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_ISA_RECRUITMARINES_02">Marines are solid all-purpose combat units which can capture objectives and gather resources on the field.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_ISA_REINFORCE_ADD01">Jerome, the captain is deploying heavy forces across the target area, keep an eye out for opportunities to coordinate fire.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_ISA_WRECKAGEFIN_01">Those wrecks are from the last days of the Covenant. The Banished are repurposing what&apos;s left to build new weapons. Scavengers picking from the bones of the dead.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_MARSQ_MARINES_ENEMYCAMPFOUND_01">Spirit of Fire Actual, we have eyes on the Banished camp, over.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_ANTIINFANTRY_01">Enemy infantry ahead. Hellbringers, you&apos;re up.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_BASETUTORIAL_11">Thanks, Captain. It&apos;s about time we did some damage of our own.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_BOSSBATTLEHALF_01">We&apos;ve damaged his armor! Don&apos;t let up!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_BRIDGE_CONFIRM_01">Bridge is up, let&apos;s go.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_BRIDGE_PROMPT_01">L</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_BRIDGE_PROMPT_02">Get that lightbridge activated, team.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_COVWRECKAGE_01">Isabel, where did all this wreckage come from?</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_COVWRECKAGE_03">It&apos;s good to know John&apos;s still out there.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_DECNEARLYDEFEATED_01">We have him on the ropes! One last push!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_DECUSFIRSTEAVESDROP_01">Sounds like we got his attention.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_EYESONCAMP_01">Spirit of Fire Actual, we have eyes on the Banished camp, over.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_FIRSTBASECLEARED_01">Spirit of Fire Actual, we&apos;ve destroyed the base. Awaiting new orders.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_FIRSTOPTIONALPOWER_01">Another power node, if we can take it, we&apos;ll be starving Decimus of resources.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_FOCUSFIREONDECIMUS_01">Everyone focus fire on Decimus, but watch out for more plasma strikes!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_HELLBRINGERGARRSIONS_01">Burn them out, Hellbringers!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_HUNTERS_INTRO_01">They&apos;ve got Hunters! Hellbringers, take them out before they can destroy our Warthogs!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_INTRO_01">You heard the captain, Strike One. Hit them hard, Marines.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_KODIAKSHELLS_ADD01">Kodiaks, take out these targets!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_KODIAKTARGETS_ADD01">Kodiaks, fire at will. Let the Banished know we&apos;re coming.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_LIGHTBRIDGE_02">Got it, Professor. Capture that power node, team!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_MOREENGINEERS_02">More Engineers!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_PLASMASTRIKE_02">Everyone, take cover!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_POSTBOMB_01">We can&apos;t turn down an invitation like that. What&apos;s the damage?</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_POSTBOMB_03">W</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_SALVAGEREINFORCEMENTS_01">Watch out team, enemy reinforcements incoming!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_SALVAGEREINFORCEMENTS_02">There&apos;s another dropship on its way!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_SALVAGEREINFORCEMENTS_03">Spirit incoming, get ready!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_SCOUNTCAMPCLEAR_01">Camp is clear, area secure.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_SILOS_01">Look what we have here. The Banished have been collecting supplies.</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_USESGRAVITYHAMMER_02">He&apos;s got some kind of gravity hammer!</str>
    <str id="M01_PIP_SPAJ_WARLORD_TAUNT_02">Put him down, team!</str>
    <str id="M01_SPAJ_MOREHUNTERS_01">More Hunters, watch out!</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_OBJ_DEFEATDECIMUS_01">Defeat Decimus</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_OBJ_DEFEATDECIMUSSHORTDESCR_01">Decimus is Atriox&apos;s right hand. Defeating him will destablize the Banished chain of command.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_OBJ_STRIKEATDECIMUSBASE_01">Strike at Decimus&apos; main base</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_OBJ_STRIKEATDECIMUSBASESHORTDESCR_01">Decimus is Atriox&apos;s right hand. Striking at Decimus&apos; main base will destablize the Banished chain of command.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_ADDINGBUILDINGS_01">You can add as many structures as your base has base sockets. As you upgrade your base, it will gain more sockets.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_ADDINGBUILDINGS_02">Now select the structure with @TutScrollCam@ and press @TutSelect@ to confirm or @TutCancel@ to cancel.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_ALLUNITS_01">Select all local units in view by pressing @TutLClUnits@ and all units across the battlefield by double tapping @TutLClUnits@.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_ANTIINFANTRY_01">Hellbringers are effective anti-infantry units.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_ANTIVEHICLESHIELD_01">Only infantry can pass through anti-vehicle shields. Use infantry to disable the shield by destroying its power source on the other side.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_BASETUTORIAL_01">Press @TutSelect@ on the base plot to open the radial.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_BASETUTORIAL_02">Now select the structure with @TutScrollCam@ and press @TutSelect@ to confirm or @TutCancel@ to cancel.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_BASETUTORIAL_03">Press @TutSelect@ on an empty base socket to open up the radial.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_CAPTUREPOWERNODE_01">Move infantry units nearby capture points and press @TutInteract@ to capture them.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_COLLECTRESOURCES_01">Move your units over Banished resource caches to collect them automatically.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_COLLECTSUPPLIES_01">Destroyed Banished Harvesters sometimes reveal collectible supplies in the wreckage. When you have a base, you can use these supplies to build your army.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_DPAD_01">@TutCyclBses@: Cycle base locations. @TutCyclSquds@: Cycle active squads @TutCyclAlrts@: Go to last alert</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_ENTERGARRISON_01">Infantry units can be moved into garrisons by selecting the unit and pressing @TutInteract@ over the garrison.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_GARRISONS">Garrisons provide a defensive bonus against enemy attacks.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_GATHERRESOURCES_01">Select an infantry unit and press @TutInteract@ over resource crates to gather resources, or simply move an infantry unit next to a resource crate to start gathering automatically.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_HELLBRINGER_01">Hellbringers carry heavy flamethrowers, which are effective against infantry units.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_HELLBRINGER_02">Hellbringers can be used to effectively clear garrisoned units</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_HELLBRINGERSVBASE_01">Hellbringer heavy flamethrowers are also effective against structures.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_HELLBRINGERSVHUNTERS_01">Vehicles are weak against Hunters, but Hellbringers are an effective counter against them.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_LEADERPOWERS_01">Access leader powers by pressing @TutPwrRadial@ to open the radial.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_LEADERPOWERS_02">Now select a leader power with the @TutRadMove@ and press @TutSelect@ to confirm.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_LEADERPOWERS_03">Press @TutSelect@ to use the leader power or cancel it with @TutCancel@.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_LPHEAL_01">Access the Restoration Drones leader power by pressing @TutPwrRadial@ to open the radial.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_MARINES_01">Marines are general infantry units and can be used to capture points on the battlefield.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_ONLYINFANTRYCAPTURE_01">Vehicle and air units cannot capture points. Only infantry units, such as Marines and Hellbringers, can be used to capture points.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_POPCAP_01">The maximum number of units you can build is capped. Once you reach that cap you will need to wait until some of your units die before you can build more.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_POPCAP_02">You have taken heavy losses. Build more units at your base to replenish your forces</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_POWERNODE_01">Once captured Power Nodes provide you with a steady stream of resources</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_SPECIALABILITY_GRENADE_01">Some units have special abilities. With a unit selected press @special_power@ to activate them</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_SUPPLYSILOS">The Banished store the supplies they&apos;ve gathered in supply silos. Destroy silos to reveal the supplies within and gather them with your units.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_TURRETS_01">Build turrets to defend your base</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_TURRETSSHORTDESCR_01">Build turrets so your base is defended as you move further into Banished territory.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUT_WARTHOG_01">Warthogs are light vehicles; useful for scouting and effective against infantry.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEX_TUTORIAL_ATRIOXLOGS_01">Y</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_BARRACKS">Build a Barracks</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_BARRACKSSHORTDESCR">Build a Barracks so you can start recruiting infantry units.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_CAMP">Clear the Banished camps</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_CAMPSHORTDESCR">Clear out the Banished camps as you push forward to establish a base.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_FIREBASE">Establish a HQ</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_FIREBASESHORTDESCR">Establish a HQ in order to build an army.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_GRENADEKILL">Grenade kills</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_GRENADEKILL_TRACK">Grenade kills:</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_GRENADEKILLSHORTDESCR">Use the Marines&apos; grenade special ability ten times. Throw grenades with @special_power@.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_GRENADETHROW">Use the grenade special ability</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_GRENADETHROW_TRACK">Grenades thrown:</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_HELLBRINGERS">Kill infantry with Hellbringers</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_HELLBRINGERS_TRACK">Squads killed with Hellbringers:</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_HELLBRINGERSSHORTDESCR">Hellbringers are effective anti-infantry units. Kill 15 units with Hellbringers.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_HELLBRINGERSSTRUCTURE">Destroy enemy base structures with Hellbringers</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_HELLBRINGERSSTRUCTURE_TRACK">Structures destroyed:</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_HELLBRINGERSSTRUCTURESHORTDESCR">Hellbringers are effective anti-building units. Destroy 20 enemy base structures with Hellbringers.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_LEADERPOWERCAS">Take no casualties from leader powers</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_LEADERPOWERCASSHORTDESCR">Keep your units clear from the Banished leader power attacks.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_MEDDRONES">Use Restoration Drones</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_MEDDRONES_TRACK">Restoration Drones used:</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_MEDDRONESSHORTDESCR">Use the Restoration Drones leader power to heal units and vehicles five times. Access the leader powers by holding @TutPwrRadial@.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_REACTOR">Build a Generator</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_REACTORSHORTDESCR">Build a Generator so you can start producing power.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_SUPPLYPAD">Build a Supply Pad</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_SUPPLYPADSHORTDESCR">Build a Supply Pad so you can call in supplies.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_OPTIONAL_OBJECTIVE_01">Destroy Banished supply silos</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_OPTIONAL_OBJECTIVE_POWERNODES">Capture 4 of Decimus&apos; power nodes</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_OPTIONAL_OBJECTIVE_POWERNODESSHORTDESCR">Capturing Decimus&apos; power nodes will increase your power income as well as starving the Banished of power resources.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_OPTIONAL_OBJECTIVE_SECONDBASE">Establish a second base</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_OPTIONAL_OBJECTIVE_SECONDBASESHORTDESCR">Establish a second base to increase the amount of resource and unit production buildings.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_PRIMARY_OBJECTIVE_01">Secure the base site</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_PRIMARY_OBJECTIVE_03">Capture the power node</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_PRIMARY_OBJECTIVE_04">Activate the lightbridge</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_PRIMARY_OBJECTIVEDESCR_01">Launch a surprise attack on the Banished camps so the UNSC can set up a forward base.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_PRIMARY_OBJECTIVEDESCR_03">Use your infantry troops to capture the power node to secure a power income from it.</str>
    <str id="M01_TEXT_PRIMARY_OBJECTIVEDESCR_04">Use the control panel to activate the lightbridge so your troops can cross.</str>
    <str id="M01_TUT_CALLOUT_CAPTURE">Move infantry units nearby to capture</str>
    <str id="M01_TUT_CALLOUT_TERMINAL">@A_Button@ Activate Lightbridge</str>
</string_table>