<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
    <str id="M02_AND_HALFWAY_DOMINATION_01">We&apos;re halfway there, Jerome. Let&apos;s make sure it goes our way.</str>
    <str id="M02_AND_HALFWAY_DOMINATION_02">Keep going, we&apos;re halfway there!</str>
    <str id="M02_AND_LOSING_DOMINATION_01">I&apos;m losing control, Jerome! We need to stop the Banished from holding those Towers!</str>
    <str id="M02_AND_LOSING_DOMINATION_02">The Banished nearly have full control! Take back some of those towers before they lock me out for good!</str>
    <str id="M02_AND_LOSING_DOMINATION_03">The Banished are going to take control unless we take some of those Towers!</str>
    <str id="M02_AND_WINNING_DOMINATION_01">I&apos;ve nearly got full control! Make sure you hold those towers until I&apos;m finished!</str>
    <str id="M02_AND_WINNING_DOMINATION_02">We&apos;ve nearly done it, just hold those towers a little longer!</str>
    <str id="M02_AND_WINNING_DOMINATION_03">We&apos;ve got control over all the Towers, let&apos;s make sure we hold them until I&apos;m done!</str>
    <str id="M02_AND_WINNING_DOMINATION_04">Hold those towers, Jerome. I&apos;ve nearly got full control now!</str>
    <str id="M02_BRUTE_HIJACKWRAITH_01">The demon has taken a Wraith! Stop it!</str>
    <str id="M02_BRUTE_LIGHTBRIDGE_01">Humans! Wipe them out!</str>
    <str id="M02_COMMS_SPAJ_FIRSTWRAITHPOSTHORNET_01">Where are our Hornets?</str>
    <str id="M02_CUT_BANISHEDBASE_DESTROYED_01">Impressive work, Spartan. Taking the Control Towers won&apos;t be a problem now.</str>
    <str id="M02_IGC_MAR02_INTRO_01">Ooh-Rah!</str>
    <str id="M02_IGC_MAR03_INTRO_01">Ooh-Rah!</str>
    <str id="M02_IGC_MAR04_INTRO_01">Ooh-Rah!</str>
    <str id="M02_IGC_PIP_PELIC_INTRO_01">Coming in now, sir.</str>
    <str id="M02_IGC_PIP_SPAJ_INTRO_01">Okay, listen up, team. You&apos;ve all been chosen for this mission because you&apos;ve seen plenty of action.</str>
    <str id="M02_IGC_PIP_SPAJ_INTRO_SPLIT_01">We can&apos;t send a large force in without alerting Atriox to our presence so I need the best.</str>
    <str id="M02_M02_TEX_TUT_AIRPADS">Airpads allow the production of air units.</str>
    <str id="M02_M02_TEX_TUT_CAPTUREPOWERNODE_01">Move infantry units nearby capture points and press @TutAttack@ to capture them.</str>
    <str id="M02_M02_TEX_TUT_CYCLOPS">Cyclops are strong anti-vehicle units.</str>
    <str id="M02_M02_TEX_TUT_HORNETS">Hornets are versatile anti-vehicle units with a vulnerability to ranged infantry.</str>
    <str id="M02_M02_TEX_TUT_LEADERPOWERS_01">Access leader powers by pressing @TutPwrRadial@ to open the radial.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_CAPTURETOWERS_01">Capture the Control Towers</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_CAPTURETOWERSSHORTDESCR_01">Capture the Control Towers so the Professor can gain control over the elevator.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_CLEARAREA_01">Clear the area of Banished troops</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_CLEARAREASHORTDESCR_01">Clear the area of Banished troops so the lightbridge can be safely activated.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_FINDROUTECARTOGRAPHER_01">Gain access to the Cartographer</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_FINDROUTECARTOGRAPHERSHORTDESCR_01">Explore the area to find a route through to the Cartographer.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_HIJACKWRAITH_01">Hijack the Wraith</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_HIJACKWRAITHSHORTDESCR_01">Use Jerome to hijack the Banished Wraith using @Y_Button@.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_JEROMETOLIFT_01">Secure the elevator entrance</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_JEROMETOLIFT_02">Get Jerome to the elevator entrance</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_JEROMETOLIFTSHORTDESCR_01">Secure the elevator entrance to make the area safe for Professor Anders.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_JEROMETOLIFTSHORTDESCR_02">Get Jerome to the elevator to enter the Cartographer.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_KEEPINFANTRYALIVE_01">Keep your infantry units alive</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_KEEPINFANTRYALIVESHORTDESCR_01">Until you establish a base, you will have limited infantry. Keep them alive.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_ADRENALINE">Use the Adrenaline leader power</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_ADRENALINESHORTDESCR">The Adrenaline leader power increases the movement speed of all non-hero infantry units.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_BOMBINGRUN">Use the Archer Missile leader power</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_BOMBINGRUN_TRACK">Archer Missiles used:</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_BOMBINGRUNSHORTDESCR">The Archer Missile leader power launches missiles from the Spirit of Fire. Access the leader power radial by holding @TutPwrRadial@.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_BUILDHORNETS">Build Hornets</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_BUILDHORNETS_TRACK">Hornets built:</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_BUILDHORNETSSHORTDESCR">Hornets are effective anti-vehicle units. Build 10 Hornets at the Airpad.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_HIJACKKILLS">Kill squads with a hijacked vehicle</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_HIJACKKILLS_TRACK">Squads killed with hijacked vehicle:</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_HIJACKKILLSSHORTDESCR">Use Jerome to hijack enemy vehicles with @Y_Button@ and turn the tables on the Banished.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_HOLD3DOMS">Hold 3 Control Towers at once</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_HOLD3DOMSSHORTDESCR">Capture and hold all 3 Control Towers at once to maximise the speed the Professor can access the elevator.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_KILLHORNETS">Destroy vehicles using Hornets</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_KILLHORNETS_TRACK">Hornet vehicle kills:</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_KILLVEHICLES">Destroy vehicles with a Cyclops</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_KILLVEHICLESSHORTDESCR">The Cyclops is an effective anti-vehicle unit. Build Cyclops at the Barracks and use them to destroy 20 enemy vehicles.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_KILLVEHICLETRACK">Cyclops vehicle kills:</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_LOTUSMINEKILL">Deploy Lotus Mines</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_LOTUSMINEKILL_TRACK">Lotus mine deployed:</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_LOTUSMINEKILLSHORTDESCR">Lotus Mines are effective against infantry units. Deploy Lotus Mines 4 times.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_WINWITHTICKETS">Finish with a 1000 point advantage</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONAL_WINWITHTICKETSHORTDESCR">Gain access to the Cartographer with a 1000 point advantage over the Banished.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONALDESTROYTANKFACTORIES">Destroy the Banished&apos;s vehicle Foundries</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_OPTIONALDESTROYTANKFACTORIESSHORTDESCR">Destroy the Banished&apos;s vehicle Foundries to slow the Banished&apos;s Wraith production.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_REACTIVATELIGHTBRIDGE_01">Reactivate the lightbridge</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_REACTIVATELIGHTBRIDGESHORTDESCR_01">Reactivate the lightbridge so the rest of the units can cross.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_RECONARE_01">Recon the area</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_RECONARESHORTDESCR_01">Recon the area as you make your way towards the elevator.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_TEX_BUILDAIRPAD_01">Build an Airpad</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_TEX_BUILDAIRPADSHORTDESCR_01">Build an Airpad so you can start building Hornets.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_TEX_BUILDRESOURCES_01">Build a Supply Pad and Generator</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_TEX_BUILDRESOURCESSHORTDESCR_01">Build a Supply Pad and Generator so you can start producing supply and power resources.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_TEX_CLIFFSIDE_01">Reactivate the lightbridge with Jerome</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_TEX_ESTABLISHBASE_01">Establish a forward base</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_TEX_ESTABLISHBASESHORTDESCR_01">Establish a forward base so you can start building a force large enough to take on the Banished.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_TEX_OPTIONAL_DESTROYBASE">Destroy the Banished base</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_TEX_OPTIONAL_DESTROYBASESHORTDESCR">Destroy the Banished base to limit their unit production and make it easier to capture and hold the Control Towers.</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_TEX_OPTIONAL_HIDDENFACILITY">Destroy the hidden facility</str>
    <str id="M02_OBJ_TEX_OPTIONAL_HIDDENFACILITYSHORTDESCR">Destroy the Banished hidden facility to slow their units on the field.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_AND_ATSHIPPINGLANES_01">Capture and hold it so I can start working on the elevator.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_AND_CAPTUREMORE_01">Jerome, I&apos;m starting to make progress on the elevator, but if you captured the other control towers I&apos;d be able to work faster.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_AND_CAPTUREPOINTS_01">I nearly have full control, make sure you keep hold of those towers!</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_AND_ENEMYTAKINGPOINTS">Jerome, the Banished are taking back one of the towers! If we can&apos;t unlock that elevator we&apos;ll never get to the Cartographer!</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_AND_GATEOPEN_01">That&apos;s it! We&apos;re in!</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_AND_GATEOPEN_02">That&apos;s it! I&apos;ve unlocked the elevator!</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_AND_SCORPIONALMOSTWIN_01">You&apos;re almost there, Spartan, but be careful. The Banished won&apos;t give up that elevator without a fight.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_ALTBUILD_01">Jerome, we&apos;ve already established a baseline of resources.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_ALTBUILD_02">Upgrade your Generator now to an Advanced Generator.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_ALTBUILD_03">Upgrading a Generator or building additional generators will also advance your tech level, allowing you to recruit more advanced units, buildings and upgrades.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_ALTBUILD_04">Now you&apos;ve reached a higher tech level, you have access to an Airpad. Build one now.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_ALTBUILD_SPLIT_01">You now have a Generator which provides you with a steady power income, but you&apos;re going to need more to help you capture those towers.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_ARMYREADY_01">Now start pushing out to capture those control towers while the enemy is regrouping.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_BASELOCATION_01">J</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_BASELOCATION_02">Isabel, update the Professor with anything she needs to know about the Forerunner control towers.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_BASEREADY_01">We&apos;re dropping in a base now. The Professor will brief you on your mission while you wait.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_BUILDAIRPAD_01">You should also request an airpad so you can start building air units.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_COUNTERS_01">We already know the Banished have Wraith tanks in the area, so you&apos;ll need air units to effectively counter them.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_COUNTERS_02">Keep in mind that air units are vulnerable to ranged infantry, so make sure you&apos;re using the right unit for the right job.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_DEADBANISHED_01">Negative. It sounds like we have another party in the mix. Be careful, the enemy of our enemy is not necessarily our friend.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_LEADERPOWER_01">J</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_LEADERPOWER_02">You can call in lotus mines to defend the captured towers.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_OPTIONALWRAITHFACTORYDESTROYED_01">Good work, Spartan. Each foundry you destroy diminishes the number of Wraiths you&apos;ll face in the field.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_SCORPIONALMOSTLOSE_01">You&apos;re losing ground, Spartan. We need to turn that around.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_SCORPIONREINFORCEMENTS_01">Jerome, I&apos;m sending in support to help you take those control towers.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_WRAITHFACTORY_01">Sabotaging those buildings will slow the enemy&apos;s ability to produce wraiths. It could give us the edge we need.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_WRAITHWAVE_01">Get some Hornets down there now to counter those Wraiths!</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_WRAITHWAVE_02">There&apos;s more enemy units dropping in from the east, Spartan.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_WRAITHWAVE_03">Hostiles incoming from the north!</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_WRAITHWAVE_04">It looks like that was the last drop for now, but they&apos;ll be back. Remember you can build Hornets at your Airpad to replace any you&apos;ve lost.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_CUT_WRAITHWAVE_05">Get those Hornets ready, Jerome. Here they come!</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_IGC_AND_CONTROLPOINTS_01">To open it up, I need you to capture three Forerunner control towers near the elevator. I&apos;m marking them on your map now.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_IGC_AND_CONTROLPOINTS_02">Capturing these towers will get me access to the elevator controls.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_IGC_AND_CONTROLPOINTS_03">The Banished won&apos;t want us reaching the Cartographer, so they&apos;ll fight hard to keep control of them.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_IGC_AND_CONTROLPOINTS_SPLIT_02">The more towers you hold, the faster I can take control.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_IGC_AND_PLAYERFAIL_01">We&apos;ve failed. They&apos;ve permanently shut down this approach to the Cartographer. Captain says return to the ship, we need another plan.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_IGC_AND_SHIPPINGLANESOPEN_01">The gate&apos;s opening, Spartan. Hold those points!</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_IGC_AND_SHIPPINGLANESPLAN_01">The only way to access the Cartographer is by way of an elevator the Banished currently have on lockdown.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_IGC_AND_SHIPPINGLANESPLAN_02">Remember, each tower you hold will increase the speed that I can take control.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_IGC_AND_SHIPPINGLANESPLAN_SPLIT_02">The Banished will be after them as well. If they succeed, we won&apos;t be able to get to the Cartographer!</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_IGC_CUT_CONTROLPOINTS_01">You&apos;re going to need a bigger army to capture those towers, Spartan. Build a Supply Pad and Generator first so you have a steady income of resources.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_IGC_CUT_PLAYERFAIL_01">We&apos;ve failed, Spartan. They&apos;ve permanently shut down this approach to the Cartographer. Return to the ship, we need another plan.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_IGC_CUT_PLAYERFAIL_DEADINFANTRY_01">Send in a Nightingale to collect the bodies, Isabel. We need to abort the mission.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_IGC_CUT_PLAYERVICTORY_01">Good work, team. We&apos;ve got a clear route to the Cartographer now and you hurt the Banished&apos;s Wraith production at the same time.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_IGC_CUT_PLAYERVICTORY_02">I</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_IGC_SPAJ_INTRO_01">Scout out the area. The Banished may still have troops moving along routes near the Cartographer.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_IGC_SPAJ_PLAYERVICTORY_01">Feels good to have a win, sir.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_ISA_ALLFACTORIESDESTROYED_01">Yes!  That was the last one.  That&apos;ll put a serious dent in their Wraith production.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_ISA_BANISHEDHAVECONTROL_01">T</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_ISA_BANISHEDSENTINELS_01">Looks like the Ark will only tolerate so much abuse before launching sentinels to defend itself.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_ISA_DEADBANISHED_01">It&apos;s a massacre! Anyone that could do this to the Banished isn&apos;t someone we want to run into.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_ISA_SKULLISLAND_01">Well, well. What do we have here?</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_ISA_WRAITHFACTORY_01">I don&apos;t think that&apos;s their only facility. I&apos;m detecting several similar structures in the area.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_ISA_WRAITHWAVE_01">Captain, we&apos;re detecting enemy units moving on Jerome&apos;s position!</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_ACTIVATELIGHTBRIDGE_01">I&apos;m across. Activating the lightbridge now.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_ARMYREADY_02">Understood, sir. Let&apos;s take those towers, troops.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_ATSHIPPINGLANES_01">Professor, we&apos;ve reached one of the Control Towers.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_BANISHEDBASE_01">Spirit of Fire Actual, we&apos;ve found a Banished base.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_BANISHEDBASE_02">Your priority is capturing those Control Towers, Jerome, but taking out that base would help. It&apos;s your call, Spartan.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_BANISHEDSENTINELS_02">Agreed. But whatever happened here we still have a job to do. Let&apos;s keep moving.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_BASEREADY_01">Spirit of Fire Actual, we have established a base.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_BUILDBASE_01">The Banished won&apos;t let us walk right into the Cartographer, so let&apos;s set up a base and build our assault force before we knock on that door.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_CAPTUREPOINTS_01">We&apos;ve taken one of the Control Towers, let&apos;s make sure it stays ours while we take the others.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_CYCLOPS_01">Banished vehicles! Send in our Cyclops!</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_DEADBANISHED_01">Spirit of Fire, we&apos;ve found destroyed Banished mining equipment. Do we have another team down here?</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_DEADBANISHED_02">Isabel, have you seen anything like this before?</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_GATEOPEN_01">Professor, the transport route gate is open.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_HIJACKWRAITH_01">Mind if I take this?</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_LIGHTBRIDGE_01">Wait here, I&apos;ll see if I can find a way around to get that lightbridge back online.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_OPTIONALWRAITHFACTORYDESTROYED_02">That&apos;s another Foundry out of action.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_REACHEDBASEPLOT_01">Spirit of Fire, we&apos;ve reached the base location.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_SENTINELATTACK_01">Spirit of Fire, we&apos;ve found out who&apos;s been attacking the Banished mining operation here.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_SKULLISLAND_02">Looks like they were trying to keep this facility hush-hush. Let&apos;s make a mess of it.</str>
    <str id="M02_PIP_SPAJ_WRAITHFACTORY_01">This must be where they&apos;re manufacturing their Wraiths.</str>
    <str id="M02_SPAJ_BANISHEDBASE_DESTROYED_01">Spirit of Fire Actual, the Banished base is out of action.</str>
    <str id="M02_TEX_DOMINATIONMODE_01">Capture and hold Control Towers to increase the points in your Domination Bar. The side who fills the Domination Bar first wins.</str>
    <str id="M02_TEXT_TUTORIAL_DOMINATIONPOINTS">Control Towers are key tactical points on the Ark. If a Control Tower already belongs to the enemy, you will need to liberate it first before you start capturing it.</str>
    <str id="M02_TUT_LEADERTREE_01">To unlock a Leader Power to use, open the Leader radial by pressing @TutPwrRadial@</str>
    <str id="M02_TUT_LEADERTREE_02">Select the Leader Power you want to unlock with @TutMoveCam@ and press @TutSelect@ to confirm.</str>
    <str id="M02_TUT_LEADERTREE_03">Any active Leader Powers you unlock will be available to use from the radial menu.</str>
    <str id="M02_TUT_LEADERTREE_04">Additional Leader Powers are unlocked by spending Leader Points, which you earn in battle.</str>
    <str id="M02_TUT_TEX_COUNTERS_01">Unit counters work on a &apos;rock, paper, scissor&apos; system; Air units counter vehicles, vehicles counter infantry, and infantry counter air.</str>
    <str id="M02_TUT_TEX_CYCLOPS_01">Cyclops are effective anti-vehicle infantry units.</str>
    <str id="M02_TUT_TEX_DOMINATIONCAPTURE_01">@X_Button@ Capture</str>
    <str id="M02_TUT_TEX_DOMINATIONTICKETS_01">Each Control Tower captured increases your points in the Domination Bar. Fill the bar to accomplish your objective.</str>
    <str id="M02_TUT_TEX_GARAGE_01">The Garage is now available, here you can build all of the UNSC vehicles.</str>
    <str id="M02_TUT_TEX_HINT_ACTIVATELIGHTBRIDGE">@A_Button@  Activate Lightbridge</str>
    <str id="M02_TUT_TEX_HINT_HIJACK">@special_power@ Hijack</str>
    <str id="M02_TUT_TEX_HINT_SPARTANSLAM">@special_power@ Spartan Slam</str>
    <str id="M02_TUT_TEX_MINIBASE_01">Mini-bases are small outposts that allow you to build standalone buildings in one or two slots.</str>
    <str id="M02_TUT_TEX_SPARTANHIJACK_01">Spartans can also use the Spartan Slam to hijack vehicles. Move the crosshair over a vehicle and press @special_power@ to hijack it.</str>
    <str id="M02_TUT_TEX_SPARTANSABOTAGE_01">Press @special_power@ with a hijacker selected to Spartan Slam out of the hijacked vehicle.</str>
    <str id="M02_TUT_TEX_SPARTANSLAM_01">Press @special_power@ to perform a Spartan Slam and reach the cliffside path.</str>
    <str id="M02_WRAIT_AMBUSH_01">Now! Mow the humans down!</str>
    <str id="M02_WRAIT_AMBUSH_02">Your bones will make fine ornaments!</str>
</string_table>