<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
    <str id="M02A_BRUTE_STOPTHEM_01">The prisoners have escaped! Send the alert!</str>
    <str id="M02A_GRUNT_RUNWAWAY_01">Run away! Run away!</str>
    <str id="M02A_HELLB_ALICEAPPEARS_01">Whoa!</str>
    <str id="M02A_HELLB_ALICEAPPEARS_02">T</str>
    <str id="M02A_HELLB_ALICEAPPEARS_03">Ooh, I felt that!</str>
    <str id="M02A_JUMPB_ATTACK_PRISONCAMPC_01">Take no prisoners this time!</str>
    <str id="M02A_MAR01_OORAH_01">OOH-RAH!</str>
    <str id="M02A_MAR02_OORAH_01">OOH-RAH!</str>
    <str id="M02A_MAR02_PRIMARYOBJECTIVE_01">Free the prisoners</str>
    <str id="M02A_MAR02_PRIMARYOBJECTIVE_SHORTDESCR_01">Destroy the power source of the light shield prison to free the prisoners.</str>
    <str id="M02A_MAR03_OORAH_01">OOH-RAH!</str>
    <str id="M02A_MAR03_PU_CONTACTOUTPOST_ADD01">There&apos;s another abandoned research post up ahead, hopefully we can use equipment there to contact the Spirit of Fire.</str>
    <str id="M02A_MAR04_OORAH_01">OOH-RAH!</str>
    <str id="M02A_MARSQ_OORAH_01">OOH-RAH!</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_CUT_LEADERPOWER_PROMPT01">Alice, the Spirit of Fire&apos;s Archer Missiles are primed for you when you need them.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_CUT_LEADERPOWER_PROMPT02">Archer Missiles are ready for you, Spartan.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_CUT_LEADERPOWER_PROMPT03">The Spirit of Fire&apos;s Restoration drones are online for you, Alice.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_CUT_LEADERPOWER_PROMPT04">You&apos;re in need of damage control, One-Three-Zero. Make use of the Spirit of Fire&apos;s restoration drones.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_CUT_LEADERPOWER_PROMPT07">Isabel has brought Lotus Mines online for you to help hold the line, Alice.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_CUT_LEADERPOWER_PROMPT08">Spartan, Lotus Mines are ready for you to set up defenses against the Banished.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_CUT_WHOAREBANISHED_01">I&apos;ll get Isabel to put a briefing package together for you so you can catch up. Good hunting.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_HELLB_CONTACTOUTPOST_ADD01">There&apos;s another abandoned research post up ahead, we can use the equipment there to contact the Spirit of Fire.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_HELLB_FREEDPRISONER_01">You&apos;re a sight for sore eyes, Spartan. I thought we&apos;d never see you again.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_IGC_CUT_LASTSTAND_01">Almost there, Spartan. I just need you to hold on a little longer.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_IGC_CUT_LASTSTAND_02">Isabel! Launch Archer Missiles, now!</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_IGC_CUT_PELICANEXTRACT_01">Pelicans incoming now, ready your team for extraction!</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_IGC_CUT_RESEARCHPOST_01">I</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_IGC_CUT_REVEAL_01">Good to hear from you, Alice. How did you make it out?</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_IGC_CUT_REVEAL_02">Isabel&apos;s got your signal and we&apos;re sending in Pelicans to extract you. But she&apos;s also intercepted enemy chatter. The Banished are heading to your position now.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_IGC_CUT_REVEAL_03">I</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_IGC_CUT_REVEAL_SPLIT_03">How would you like to cause them more trouble.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_IGC_SPAA_ALICERETURN_01">Ready your weapons, troops. We&apos;re going to get everyone back. It&apos;s gonna be a ball.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_IGC_SPAA_LASTSTAND_01">Spirit of Fire Actual, it&apos;s getting pretty busy down here, do we have an ETA on that extraction?</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_IGC_SPAA_LASTSTAND_02">Spirit of Fire Actual, they&apos;re throwing everything at us!</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_IGC_SPAA_PELICANEXTRACT_01">Yessir. You heard him, troops, pack it up! Move, move!</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_IGC_SPAA_PELICANEXTRACT_02">That&apos;s not going to hold them back, sir!</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_IGC_SPAA_PELICANEXTRACT_03">Close call. Where are we headed next, sir?</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_IGC_SPAA_REVEAL_01">Spirit of Fire Actual, this is Alice One-Three-Zero reporting in.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_IGC_SPAA_REVEAL_02">Commandeered an enemy vehicle, sir. I&apos;ve rescued some of our troops and we&apos;re ready to get back in the fight.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_IGC_SPAA_REVEAL_03">We&apos;ll hold the line until extraction, sir.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_IGC_SPAA_REVEAL_05">W</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_ISA_TURRETSHINT_ADD01">Alice, I have turrets ready to deploy to help shore up your defenses.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_MAR03_ENGINNEERSINTRO_ADD01">What are those things?</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_ALICEAPPEARS_01">I</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_ALICEFREESPRISONER_01">W</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_ENGINEERSINTRO_ADD01">Engineers. The Covenant used them for combat support. They&apos;re harmless but they can fix just about anything.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_ENGINEERSINTRO_ADD02">Make them your priority targets or they&apos;ll heal the Banished faster than we can hurt &apos;em.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_FINALPRISON_01">N</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_FINALPRISON_SPLIT_01">We can&apos;t call the Spirit of Fire on unsecured channels so we need to take control of the old research post here. Let&apos;s roll out.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_FREEOTHERCAMPS_01">We&apos;ve still got more of our people out there, let&apos;s go get them back.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_INTRO_01">Okay, Spartan. Let&apos;s get to work.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_JUMPBRUTES_01">Jump Pack Brutes! Keep your distance, and if you see them fly, get outta the way before they land!</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_LEADERALICE_01">We&apos;re only going to get one shot at a pickup, so let&apos;s get everybody before we call for a ride home. Stay close to me and we&apos;ll all get out of here together.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_MAPUNLOCKED_01">That&apos;s given us the layout of the prison compound. I&apos;ve marked our maps with their locations. Let&apos;s go get our people back.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_PRISONCAMPB_01">More cells up ahead, break them out of there!</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_PRISONCAMPB_02">Welcome back to the fight, everyone.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_PRISONCAMPB_03">Heads up! Looks like we woke the neighbours!</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_PRISONCAMPD_01">You know the drill team, don&apos;t spare the ammo.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_PRISONCAMPD_02">Hope you kept that Cyclops armor in good shape.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_RESEARCHPOST_01">W</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_SHOOTSHIELD_01">I&apos;m going to disable that shield and get you out of there.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_SLAM_ADD01">Easy pickings. I can take out those guards with one slam.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_TAKEWARTHOGS_01">Okay, soldiers. Saddle up. We&apos;re gonna need those Warthogs.</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_SPAA_WHOAREBANISHED_01">Only one question, sir. Who are the Banished?</str>
    <str id="M02A_PIP_TEX_TUT_NOLEADERPOWERS_01">Leader powers are inaccessible until Alice makes contact with the Spirit of Fire.</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_CALLOUT_ALICEHEALTH_01">Alice&apos;s Health</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_CALLOUT_SHIELDGENERATOR_01">Shield Generator</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_CALLOUT_SPARTANSLAM_01">@special_power@ Spartan Slam</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_BONUS_BOMBINGRUN_01">Kill units with Archer Missiles</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_BONUS_BOMBINGRUN_01_UPDATE">Units killed by Archer Missiles:</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_BONUS_BOMBINGRUNSHORTDESCR_01">Kill units with the Archer Missiles leader power. Select the power in the radial by holding @TutPwrRadial@.</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_BONUS_LOTUSMINES_01">Kill units with Lotus Mines</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_BONUS_LOTUSMINES_01_UPDATE">Units killed with Lotus Mines:</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_BONUS_LOTUSMINESSHORTDESCR_01">Kill units using the Lotus Mines leader power. Select the power in the radial by holding @TutPwrRadial@.</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_BONUS_SCAREDGRUNT_01">Kill the scared Grunt before he flees</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_BONUS_SCAREDGRUNTSHORTDESCR_01">Don&apos;t let the scared Grunt escape your wrath! No mercy!</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_BONUS_SPARTANSLAM_01">Kill units using Spartan Slam</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_BONUS_SPARTANSLAM_01_UPDATE">Slams executed:</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_BONUS_SPARTANSLAMSHORTDESCR_01">Execute a Spartan Slam by pressing @special_power@.</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_HOLDTHELINE_01">Hold the line until extraction</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_OPTIONAL_ALICEALIVE_01">Keep Alice alive for the entire mission</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_OPTIONAL_GATHERRESOURCES_01">Gather all resources</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_OPTIONAL_GATHERRESOURCES_01_UPDATE">Gathered resources:</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_OPTIONAL_GATHERRESOURCESSHORTDESCR_01">Without a base drop from the Spirit of Fire, Alice will need to gather resources from the area.</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_OPTIONAL_UNITSALIVE_01">Don&apos;t let prison squads die</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_OPTIONAL_UNITSALIVE_01_UPDATE">Prisoner died</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_OPTIONAL_UNITSALIVESHORTDESCR_01">Alice has a limited force to take on the Banished, keep the rescued units alive.</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_RESEARCHPOST_01">Take control of the research post</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_OBJ_RESEARCHPOSTSHORTDESCR_01">Take control of the research post and use it to reestablish contact with the Spirit of Fire.</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_TUT_BATTLEHARDENED_01">You have unlocked the Battle Hardened leader power. All units will automatically gain veterancy at 50% faster rate.</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_TUT_CONTROLGROUPS_01">To set control groups hold @TutSelUnits@ and use the @D-Pad@ to assign groups.</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_TUT_CYCLOPSTUTORIAL_01">Cyclops units are heavy anti-vehicle units.</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_TUT_ENGINEER_01">Engineers heal other units. Take them out with ranged units first to maximize your damage.</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_TUT_HEROUNITS_01">Hero units, such as Spartans, can deal and take a lot of damage, so use them to your advantage.</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_TUT_JUMPBRUTES_01">Jump Pack Brutes can jump over large distances, delivering a mighty blow when they land, but can be countered by Hellbringers.</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_TUT_LOTUSMINESARCHER_01">Use the Lotus Mines, Archer Missiles and Restoration Drones leader powers provided by the Spirit of Fire to fight off the Banished attack.</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_TUT_SPARTANSLAM_01">Select Alice and Press @special_power@ to attack with Spartan Slam</str>
    <str id="M02A_TEX_TUT_WARTHOGRAM_01">Press @special_power@ to use the Warthog&apos;s special ability to ram enemies.</str>
</string_table>