<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<str id="M03_BRU2_POWER_NODES_01">Stop them!</str>
	<str id="M03_BRU2_POWER_NODES_02">Guard the conduits with your life! For Atriox!</str>
	<str id="M03_BRU3_POWER_NODES_01">The humans are here!</str>
	<str id="M03_M03_TEX_OBJ__BONUS_COMPLETESHUTDOWN">Shut down all conduits in quick succession</str>
	<str id="M03_M03_TEX_OBJ__BONUS_COMPLETESHUTDOWNSHORTDESCR">Time your attacks to shut down all conduits within a short time of each other.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_AFTER_LIFT_01">Keep an eye out for Sentinels. Between the Banished and my poking around, the Sentinels are on high alert.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_AFTER_SKIRMISH_01">Up ahead, that's where we need to go. Come on.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_CENTRAL_CHAMBER_01">Let's find out!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_CONSOLE_01">Hang on, give me a moment to work. Uh, what's that sound?</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_DEADBANISHED_01">Look at the Sentinels take on that Banshee!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_EMPBLAST_01">An EMP targeted to disrupt the Sentinels’ command network. Good work, Isabel.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_EMPBLAST_02">Then let's watch our timing.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_ENGINEERREMINDER_01">Jerome, we need those Engineers gone before we can take out the conduit!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_ENGINEERSEARLY_01">Jerome, the Banished are sending in Engineers! They won't attack us, but they'll keep healing the Banished!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_ENGINEERSHERE_01">Take them out before they repair the conduits!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_ENGINEERSRETURN_01">Watch out, the Banished are sending in more Engineers!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_FINALCONDUIT_SENTWARNING_01">Heads up, Sentinels on the way!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_FINALCONDUIT_SENTWARNING_02">Here they come, Jerome!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_FINALCONDUIT_SENTWARNING_03">They're back. Isabel, prep the EMP.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_FIRSTCONDUIT_01">That's the conduit for the energy shields, but the Banished have locked it down.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_FIRSTCONDUIT_02">As much as I'd like a more scientific solution, I think you're just going to have to destroy it to force it to shut down.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_FIRSTCONDUITCAPT_01">The Cartographer's sending in Sentinels to protect itself!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_FIRSTSENTINEL_ARRIVE_01">Jerome, the Sentinels are on their way back!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_INTROCARTOGRAPHER_02">This is it. The Cartographer. It was a long journey, but it was worth it. It's magnificent.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_INVINCIBLESENTINELS_01">We can't take on those Sentinels, fall back!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_LIFT_04">Watch out for the Sentinels. They'll swarm in once you start attacking the conduits.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_MAP_ROOM_01">What's the status of our special project, Isabel?</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_MAP_ROOM_ATTACK_01">The Ark's portal network. Captain, Atriox has been using the Cartographer to map and take over the Ark's portal network!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_MAP_ROOM_ATTACK_SPLIT_01">There's hundreds of them! He's got coverage over the whole of the Ark!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_MAP_ROOM_BLOCKED_01">There's our goal...tucked right in behind that eyesore.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_MAP_ROOM_CLEAR_01">Time to find out what Atriox has been up to.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_MAP_ROOM_TERMINAL_01">Incredible, I can see so much of the Ark from here! Weapons systems, environmental controls, bioresource libraries…and…</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_MAPROOM_BARRIER_01">Oh, great. That was our way in.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_MAPROOMSWARM_01">Isabel, there's another swarm blocking our entrance to the Map Room. Power up the EMP.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_MAPROOMSWARM_02">That's cleared them out!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_NODES_ONE_01">Just two more to go.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_PROTECTORSENTS_01">We've got a new problem, Protector Sentinels incoming!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_PROTECTORSENTS_02">They're not part of the swarm, so we should be able to damage them.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_SECOND_NODES_02">We're nearly there, Jerome. One more and we'll be through the shield!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_SENTINEL_WAVE_01">Sentinel wave incoming, take cover!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_SENTINEL_WAVE_02">Sentinels on the way!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_SENTINEL_WAVE_03">Get into cover, quick! Sentinels coming!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_SENTINEL_WAVE_04">The sentinels are coming back!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_SENTINEL_WAVEFINAL_01">Isabel, we're going to need another EMP to clear them out.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_SENTINEL_WAVEFINAL_02">You're good to go, Jerome.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_SENTINEL_WAVEWARNING_01">Jerome, there's a wave of sentinels coming! Isabel, prepare the EMP!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_AND_WATCHBACK_01">Watch my back, I'm going to find out what Atriox is up to.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_CUT_BANSHEEATTACKBASE_01">Jerome, you've got Banshees attacking the base! Set up some anti-air defenses!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_CUT_BANSHEEATTACKBASE_02">Get those anti-air turrets built at your base before you lose it!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_CUT_COMBATREINFORCE_TUT_01">You're going to need more support, Jerome. I've managed to free up a few more fresh recruits for you.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_CUT_GARAGEDROP_01">Jerome, I'm sending in a Garage for you base in case you need to build more Wolverines.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_CUT_OPTIONALOBJECTIVE_01">Jerome, to support such a heavy Banished presence, they must have bases somewhere in the central chamber.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_AND_ARK_HOLOMAP_02">Well, I'd love to stay and find out more...</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_AND_ARK_HOLOMAP_03">...but I'd say that's our cue to go.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_AND_CART_BARRIER_01">This is much more advanced than anything I've ever seen.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_AND_CART_BARRIER_02">Well, we're in the right place...those power signatures I detected in the central chamber must be connected to this energy shield somehow.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_AND_LIFT_01">Nothing ventured, nothing gained, right?</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_AND_LIFT_02">Phew, smells bad - Brute bad. They must have been using these Passages to avoid the Sentinels.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_AND_LIFT_04">Okay, there are three more conduits in this area.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_AND_LIFT_SPLIT_04">Each of them are controlling the Forerunner shield blocking our path to the Map Room , so you'll need to shut down every one of them.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_AND_MAP_ROOM_01">I'm in.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_AND_WALL_SHUTDOWN_01">That's it, we're in!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_CUT_CART_BARRIER_01">Can you open it, Professor?</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_CUT_MAP_ROOM_01">That’s how his troops seem to be everywhere at once. At least we know how he’s doing it now.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_CUT_MAP_ROOM_SPLIT_01">Professor, I need to know how he’s controlling that network so we can take it out. Do you have what you need?</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_CUT_SENTINEL_ATTACK_01">Already standing by, Jerome.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_SPAJ_ARK_HOLOMAP_02">Spirit of Fire, we’re on our way back!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_SPAJ_CART_BARRIER_01">Spirit of Fire Actual, we've got a problem. The route through to the Map Room is blocked by some kind of energy shield.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_SPAJ_LIFT_01">Professor, wait!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_SPAJ_SENTINEL_ATTACK_01">Spirit of Fire, Isabel was right. There are Banished are still here. Requesting a base drop.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_SPAJ_SENTINEL_ATTACK_02">More Banshees! Take them down, Wolverines!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_IGC_SPAJ_WALL_SHUTDOWN_01">Let's go, Professor.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_ISA_BLOCKED_01">On the way, Spartan.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_ISA_BLOCKED_02">On the way, Spartan. We can use the openings in the top of the structure to send you what you need.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_ISA_EMP_READY_SPLIT_01">I had to sacrifice some power for stability but you'll be able to call in strikes from the Spirit of Fire now. I'm detecting a lot of Sentinels up ahead.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_ISA_INTROCARTOGRAPHER_03">It's much larger than any other Cartographer we've encountered so far; the power it must contain is incredible.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_ISA_MAP_ROOM_01">Professor, I'm detecting a lot of sentinels up ahead.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_ISA_MAP_ROOM_02">It's ready, Professor. You guys might want to hold onto something down there!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_ISA_SENTINEL_WAVEFINAL_01">Ready when you need it, Professor.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_BANSHEE_BASEATTACK_01">We've got Banshees attacking the base! We need some anti-air defenses!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_BANSHEE_BASEATTACK_02">Get some anti-air turrets built at our base before we lose it!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_BANSHEES_01">Banshees! Spirit of Fire, we're going to need those Wolverines!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_BLOCKED_01">Spirit of Fire, we may be here a while.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_CAPTURECONDUITS_01">You heard the Professor, let's shut down those conduits!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_CENTRAL_CHAMBER_01">That did it, we've opened the energy shield to the central chamber, Professor. What now?</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_CONDUITBASE_01">The Banished have a base here!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_CONDUITBASE_02">Let's build a minibase while we're developing our main base. We're going to need the extra support before we head into the central chamber.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_DEADBANISHED_01">They're dangerous. Let's find out what we need and get out of here.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_EMPBLAST_01">What was that?</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_ENGINEERSDEAD_01">Engineers are down, team. Target the conduit!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_ENGINEERSHEALING_01">The Engineers are healing the enemy troops, take them down!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_ENGINEERSHEALING_02">Prioritize the Engineers! With them down the Banished won't have any support!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_ENGINEERSHEALING_03">Stop the Engineers healing the Banished!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_ENGINEERSHERE_02">Professor, the Banished have Engineers.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_ENGINEERSHIELD_01">Target the Engineers to take out their shields!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_ENGINEERSSHIELDS_01">The Banished are being shielded by the Engineers! Take them out first!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_FINALCONDUIT_01">That's the last conduit!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_FINDFIRSTCONDUIT_01">Let's find a way to open the shield. Wait, what's that sound?</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_FIRSTCONDUIT_01">Professor, there's some kind of Forerunner structure here.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_FIRSTCONDUIT_02">Only one way to find out. Weapons free, team. Target that conduit.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_FIRSTCONDUITCAPT_01">Did you feel that, Professor?</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_FIRSTSENTINEL_01">Looks like they're here to stay this time, Professor. Any ideas?</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_FIRSTSENTINEL_LEAVE_01">Area is clear, everyone back to work!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_FIRSTSENTINEL_LEAVE_02">Move, while they're gone!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_GARAGEDROP_02">Roger that, sir.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_INTROCARTOGRAPHER_01">Is this it, Professor?</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_INTROCARTOGRAPHER_04">That means it's dangerous. Let's find what we need and get out of here.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_INTROSENTINELSWARM_01">Hold fire, team.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_INVINCIBLESENTINELS_02">Keep clear of those Sentinels, our weapons aren't making a dent!</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_LIFT_04">I never expected it to be easy, Professor.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_LIFT_05">Then we better work fast. Let's find those conduits, people.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_MAP_ROOM_BLOCKED_02">Time for some housekeeping. Take out the base, team.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_MAP_ROOM_CLEAR_01">That looks like it, Professor. It's all yours.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_NODES_ONE_01">That's the first conduit, Professor.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_NOGUARDS_01">The guards at the elevator have been dealt with, so we're clear to set up a new forward base.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_SENTINEL_WAVEFINAL_01">Professor, I don't think they're going to leave.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_SENTINEL_WAVEGONE_02">They're gone. Let's continue.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_SENTINEL_WAVEGONE01">Area's clear. Back to work.</str>
	<str id="M03_PIP_SPAJ_SENTINEL_WAVEWARNING_01">Move it, people! Get clear!</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_CALLOUT_ANDERS_HEALTH_01">Anders's Health</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_CALLOUT_CONDUIT_01">Forerunner Conduit</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_CALLOUT_CONDUIT_HEALTH_01">Conduit Health</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_CALLOUT_CONDUIT_HEALTH_EAST_01">East Conduit Health</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_CALLOUT_CONDUIT_HEALTH_NORTH_01">North Conduit Health</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_CALLOUT_CONDUIT_HEALTH_WEST_01">West Conduit Health</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_CALLOUT_EMPAVAILABLE_01">MAC Blast EMP is now available to use</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_COMBATREINFORCE_TUT_01">Increase the amount of units you can field at once by researching the 'Combat Reinforcements' upgrade at your Armory.</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_MINIBASEOPTIONALOBJECTIVESHORTDESCR_01">Destroy the minibases in the central chamber to slow the Banished's flow of troops.</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_OBJ_ANDERSMAPROOM_01">Clear the path to the map room</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_OBJ_BONUS_WOLVERINEKILLS">Kill 30 enemy air units using Wolverines</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_OBJ_BONUS_WOLVERINEKILLS_UPDATE">Air units killed by Wolverines:</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_OBJ_BONUS_WOLVERINEKILLSSHORTDESCR">Wolverines are anti-air units. Take out 30 enemy air units with them.</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_OBJ_DESTROY1STBANISHEDCONTROL_01">Attack the Forerunner conduit</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_OBJ_DESTROY1STBANISHEDCONTROLSHORTDESCR_01">The Forerunner conduits seem to be providing power to the shields. Attack them to shut them down.</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_OBJ_GAINACCESS">Gain access to the Cartographer map room.</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_OBJ_TAKESHIELDSDOWNSHORTDESCR">The Forerunner shields are blocking the way to the Map Room. Find a way to deactivate them.</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_OPTIONALOBJECTIVE_01">Destroy the minibases in the central chamber</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_OPTIONALOBJECTIVE_01_UPDATE">Banished Minibase destroyed:</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_TIMER_TITLE">Sentinel Swarm Imminent</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_TUT_BANSHEES_01">Banshees are air units with high maneuverability.</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_TUT_BUILDWOLVERINES_01">Build Wolverines from the Garage to counter the Banshees</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_TUT_MACEMP_01">The Spirit of Fire's MAC gun is now equipped with EMP blasts. Use it via the leader power radial when the Sentinel Swarm is active.</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_TUT_MAP_ROOMSHORTDESCR_01">The Professor needs to reach the Map Room to find out Atriox's plans. Open the path for her and keep her safe until she reaches it.</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_TUT_SENTINELSWARM_01">Keep away from the Sentinel Swarm</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_TUT_WOLVERINES_01">Wolverines are specialized anti-air vehicles.</str>
	<str id="M03_TEX_TUT_WRAITHS_01">Cyclops are a good counter against Wraiths.</str>
	<str id="M03_TEXT_CONDUITOBJECTIVE_UPDATE_01">Conduits shut down:</str>
	<str id="M03_TEXT_CONDUITOBJECTIVESHORTDESCR_02">Shut down the three power conduits in the central chamber to shut down the shield blocking the Map Room.</str>
	<str id="M03_TEXT_HINTMESSAGE_ARMORYNOTIFICATION">The Armory is now available to build at your base.</str>
	<str id="M03_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_02">Shut down the three power conduits</str>
	<str id="M03_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_02_UPDATE">Conduit shut down</str>
	<str id="M03_TEXT_OPTIONAL_OBJECTIVE_01">Avoid losing any units to the Sentinel Swarm</str>
	<str id="M03_TEXT_OPTIONAL_SENTINELSWARMOBJECTIVE_01">Keep your units safe from the Sentinel Swarm while shutting down the power conduits.</str>
	<str id="M03_TXT_TUT_SUPERSENTINELS_01">Use the Mac Blast EMP to stun the Protector Sentinels</str>
</string_table>