<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<str id="M04_COMMS_IGC_HORN_INTRO_01">Spirit of Fire, we have eyes on the first portal and we're returning to base.</str>
	<str id="M04_COMMS_IGC_HORN_INTRO_03">Looks like we're not going to make it back without a fight!</str>
	<str id="M04_COMMS_SPAD_DECIWIN_01">Is that it? Are we done?</str>
	<str id="M04_COMMS_SPAJ_BANISHEDPARTY_01">Someone's been busy.</str>
	<str id="M04_COMMS_SPAJ_DECIWIN_01">Spirit of Fire, Decimus is down.</str>
	<str id="M04_COMMS_SPAJ_PRISONBREAK_01">More prisoners. Get them out of there.</str>
	<str id="M04_COMMS_SPAJ_SURVIVORS_01">Break them out of there!</str>
	<str id="M04_COMMS_SPAJ_VEHCBARRIER_01">Our vehicles are blocked by that shield, get some infantry through there and shut down that portal!</str>
	<str id="M04_IGC_BRUTE_INTRO_01">Enemies on the way! Move faster, Grunts or I’ll throw you at them myself!</str>
	<str id="M04_MAR01_DECIWIN_01">And stay down!</str>
	<str id="M04_MAR01_FANGIRL_01">Two Spartans? This mission is in the bag!</str>
	<str id="M04_MAR01_TRICK_01">How are we getting across that?</str>
	<str id="M04_MAR03_DECIWIN_01">We got him!</str>
	<str id="M04_MAR03_FANGIRL_01">Isn't that the one that got busted up by Atriox? And he’s back already? What are those guys made of?</str>
	<str id="M04_MAR03_HALOKILLS_02">They’re going to have to get in line behind the Banished…</str>
	<str id="M04_MAR03_TRICK_01">I heard there's this trick you can do with grenades…</str>
	<str id="M04_MAR04_BOMBARDMENT_01">Did...did he say more attacks? Is there anybody left out there not shooting at us?</str>
	<str id="M04_MAR04_DECIWIN_01">And stay down!</str>
	<str id="M04_MAR04_FANGIRL_01">Two Spartans? This mission is in the bag!</str>
	<str id="M04_MAR04_HALOKILLS_01">Did you read the briefing about the “Halo”s this place makes? Giant rings. They kill everything!</str>
	<str id="M04_MAR04_TRICK_01">How are we getting across that?</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_CUT_BOMBARDMENT_01">You've definitely got the Banished's attention now. That was their carrier again. Watch out for more attacks.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_CUT_BOMBARDMENT_02">Their carrier's charging up for another blast! Get ready to move!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_CUT_BOMBARDMENT_03">You've got incoming! Move it!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_CUT_DECIBRAWL_01">Jerome, I'm dropping in some ODSTs to support you.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_CUT_HORNETSUPPORT_01">Jerome, with that Reaver gone, the skies are safe for our air units. I'm sending in a Hornet escort for you now.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_CUT_KILLZONEWARNING_01">Decimus is setting up a killzone. Jerome, you better use the portals to circumvent the area.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_CUT_LASTNODE_02">Be careful, Jerome. Decimus has had time to prepare for this.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_CUT_LASTNODE_03">He's right. We need to take the portals out once and for all. It's time to take down that control hub.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_CUT_LASTNODE_SPLIT_02">The Banished have shown a surprising amount of control over the Ark's systems so far…there’s no telling how he’ll use that against you.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_CUT_MINIBASE_01">Jerome, Isabel's found the location where you can build a minibase to bolster your forces.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_CUT_PORTALSCOUTREMIND_01">Jerome, send some scouts through the portal to run reconnaissance first, we shouldn't be leaping through blind.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_CUT_SCOUTWARNING_01">When you reach the next portal, I would send scouts through ahead of the main party. We don't know what's waiting for you on the other side.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_CUT_SECONDBASE_01">Good work securing the southern sector. I'm dropping in a base to help you maintain your position and support you.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_CUT_SECONDPORTAL_01">Concentrate on that portal, Spartan. Decimus can wait.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_CUT_SENTNODE1_02">Only three portals left before you reach the portal control hub, Spartans. Don't let anything stand in your way.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_DEC_ARKTAUNT_01">The Ark is ours, humans, and no one will stand before the might of the Banished!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_DEC_DECIBRAWL_01">My master broke you, Spartan! I shall take great pleasure in doing the same.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_DEC_DECIBRAWL_02">Did I tell you how the other humans screamed when we destroyed their base?</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_DEC_DECIBRAWL_03">Your arrogant species WILL be humbled! The only thing you are destined for is to be meat on my table!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_DEC_DECIBRAWL_04">I am impressed, humans, but Atriox will ensure you never leave the Ark. We will control this place and then the Banished will take all of your worlds.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_DEC_DECIBRAWL_05">Make the most of your victory, humans. It will be your last.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_DEC_FIFTHPORTAL_01">Protect the portal! Crush the humans like the insects they are!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_DEC_FIFTHPORTAL_02">Soon enough, little demon. Soon enough.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_DEC_FOURTHPORTALATTACK_01">Vermin! How many of you must I exterminate before you learn your place?</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_DEC_KILLZONE_TAUNT_01">What's wrong, Humans? Lost your nerve?  I'm waiting for you!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_DEC_LASTNODE_01">Fools. We’ll repair the damage you’ve done soon enough.. But, you have shamed me before Atriox and for that you will pay. We have unfinished business, you and I.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_DEC_SECONDPORTAL_01">Protect the portal, fools, or I'll take your heads!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_DEC_SECONDPORTAL_02">Stop them!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_DEC_SECONDPORTAL_03">This one is lost! We must reinforce the others!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_IGC_CUT_BANSHINC_01">Well done, team. We're a step closer to leveling the playing field.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_IGC_CUT_BANSHINC_02">The Spirit of Fire is under attack from the Banished's fleet! Return to the ship, NOW!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_IGC_DEC_SHOWDOWN_01">Human filth. Do you know what you have cost me? My salvage operation, the portals.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_IGC_DEC_SHOWDOWN_02">It will. As you can see, I've made some improvements.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_IGC_ISA_BANSHINC_01">That's it! All Banished portal signatures are down!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_IGC_ISA_BANSHINC_02">Captain! We have Banshees incoming!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_IGC_ISA_ISAUPDATE_01">Jerome, I've marked the first portal on your map.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_IGC_SPAD_GRUNTFALL_01">Room for a passenger?</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_IGC_SPAD_GRUNTFALL_02">I couldn't take that hospital bed any longer. Thought I should make myself useful.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_IGC_SPAD_GRUNTFALL_03">Next time I'll be putting him on the ground. Count on it.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_IGC_SPAD_SHOWDOWN_01">I was looking for a second round with the ringmaster, but his whipping boy will do just fine.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_IGC_SPAJ_BANSHINC_02">Sir? Captain Cutter? Isabel?</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_IGC_SPAJ_GRUNTFALL_01">Douglas. You're looking a lot better than last time I saw you.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_IGC_SPAJ_GRUNTFALL_02">Just remember to dodge next time, ok?</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_IGC_SPAJ_INTRO_01">I've got no problem with that. This time we came prepared.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_IGC_SPAJ_ISAUPDATE_01">Thanks, Isabel. We've got our orders, team. Neutralize  every portal we see until we reach the Banished's portal controller.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_IGC_SPAJ_SHOWDOWN_01">My heart bleeds.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_ISA_DECIBRAWL_02">Monster! Oh, please kill him for me.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_ISA_FIRSTPORTAL_02">Jerome, the Banished are using hacking devices to get their forces through those portals. Destroy the devices, and they won't be able to send any more troops in!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_ISA_HEAILYGUARDED_01">The Banished have got that side heavily guarded, Jerome. There may be a another route in.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_ISA_KILLZONEWARNING_01">Captain, I'm still reading heavy energy traces over the area ahead, I think it's a trap.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_ISA_LASTNODE_01">I'm still getting energy readings coming from nearby.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_ISA_LASTNODE_02">It's got to be a trap!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_ISA_LASTNODE_03">Well, if you're going to charge in, charge in well-armed.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_ISA_LASTNODE_04">But with that control, how long will it be before they figure out how to make a Halo?</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_ISA_PORTAL1_DOWN_02">Good work. Now that it's out of their control, we can move through it to reach the next portal. I've marked it on your map.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_ISA_PORTALCONTROLLER_01">That's the portal controller, Jerome. Take it out and the Banished won't be able to access the portal network anymore.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_ISA_PORTALCONTROLLERDESTROYED_01">That's it! All Banished portal signatures are shutting down! Wait, there's something coming through…</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_ISA_REAVER_INTRO_02">The Banished call them Reavers, anti-air walkers. They use their leaping capabilities for ambushes.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_ISA_SENTNODE1_01">Incoming! Get to cover!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_MAR02_AIRSUPPORT_01">We could do with some eyes in the sky.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_MAR03_AIRSUPPORT_01">What I wouldn't give for some air support.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_MAR03_AIRSUPPORT_02">Where's our air support?</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_MAR04_AIRSUPPORT_01">I'm telling you, we won't win this battle just from the ground.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_MAR04_AIRSUPPORT_02">Are we gonna get any air support?</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_PRI1_ISAFRIENDS_01">Are we glad to see you! There's more of us out there, you gotta help them!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAD_BOMBARDMENT_01">Okay, that was my fault.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAD_DECIDEAD_01">Phew. Talk about stubborn.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAD_FIFTHPORTAL_01">Come over here and try it, Decimus!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAD_FOURTHPORTALATTACK_01">He never sticks around, it is something we said?</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAD_LASTNODE_01">And that's the ball game!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAD_SENTNODE1_02">Hey, what can go wrong?</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAJ_CROSSRIVER_01">Get that bridge activated so we can get across!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAJ_DECIBRAWL_03">Watch your shields, he's got an EMP!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAJ_DECIBRAWL_04">Very well, I will tear you apart with my own hands!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAJ_DECIBRAWL_05">This is it, put him in the ground!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAJ_DECIDEAD_01">And you wouldn't know about that, would you?</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAJ_FORUTHPORTALANTIVEHICLESHIELD_01">Shut down that shield! We're going to need vehicle support here!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAJ_FORUTHPORTALANTIVEHICLESHIELD_02">Portal's down. Move out to the next one.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAJ_LASTNODE_01">Isabel, how are we looking?</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAJ_LASTNODE_02">We don't have much choice, Isabel.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAJ_LASTNODE_05">We won't give them the chance, Isabel.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAJ_NEEDTOCROSSBRIDGE_01">Spirit of Fire Actual, we're ready to take the portal into Decimus' base.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAJ_NODE1_01">We have a visual on the second portal. Target the Banished device!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAJ_PORTAL1_DOWN_01">We've cut off that portal from the Banished, Isabel.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAJ_PORTALCONTROLLER_01">You heard Isabel, team! Focus fire on that controller!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAJ_PORTALCONTROLLER_02">Keep going, it's almost done!</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAJ_REAVER_INTRO_01">I think we've got a new threat on the field. Isabel?</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAJ_SCOUTWARNING_02">Copy that, Sir. We've had enough surprises already.</str>
	<str id="M04_PIP_SPAJ_SECONDPORTAL_01">Spirit of Fire Actual, We’ve got eyes on Decimus!</str>
	<str id="M04_TEX_IGC_REAVER_INTRO_01">Banished Reavers are anti-air walkers that have the ability to jump over obstacles.</str>
	<str id="M04_TEX_OBJ_DEACTIVATETHREEPORTALS">Deactivate the next three portals</str>
	<str id="M04_TEX_OBJ_DESTROYPORTALCONTROL_01">Destroy the Banished portal controller</str>
	<str id="M04_TEX_OBJ_SPAD_PORTALSHIELDED_01">Eliminate Decimus</str>
	<str id="M04_TEX_ODSTTUTORIAL_01">ODSTs are elite soldiers, their fighting abilities second only to Spartans.</str>
	<str id="M04_TEX_PRIMARYOBJECTIVE_FIRSTPORTAL">Destroy the Banished device for the first portal</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_HINTCALLOUT_BANISHEDDEVICE">BANISHED DEVICE</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_HINTCALLOUT_PORTAL">PORTAL</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_HINTCALLOUT_PRISONSHIELDGEN">PRISON GENERATOR</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_HINTMESSAGE_CYCLEARMY">Press @TutCyclSquds@ to cycle between army locations</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_HINTMESSAGE_CYCLEBASE">Press @TutCyclBses@ to cycle to base locations</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_HINTMESSAGE_FASTCAMERA">Hold down @TutCamSpeed@ whilst moving @TutScrollCam@ for fast camera movement</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_HINTMESSAGE_FASTCAMERA_PC">Use @CameraUp@ @CameraDown@ @CameraLeft@ @CameraRight@ and hold @TutCamSpeed@ for fast camera movement.</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_HINTMESSAGE_LEADERPOWERPOINTS">Press @TutPwrRadial@ to access the Leader Power Menu and spend Leader Power Points to purchase new abilities.</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_HINTMESSAGE_LEADERPOWERREMINDER">Don't forget to utilise your available Leader Powers from the Leader Power wheel by pressing @TutPwrRadial@.</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_HINTMESSAGE_REAVERUNITINTRO">Reavers are Banished anti-air vehicles, able to make bounding leaps. They're particularly vulnerable to attacks from Cyclops units.</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_HINTMESSAGE_REINFROCEMENTTECHREMINDER">You can build an Armory at your base and purchase the Reinforcement upgrade to increase your army's population cap.</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_HINTMESSAGE_TELEPORTERFUNCTIONALITY">Select units and then move the cursor over the teleporter with @TutScrollCam@ and press @TutAttack@ to use the teleporter</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECT_DISPLAYNAME_HIJACKERDISH">Banished Device</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_01">Deactivate the first portal</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_02">Destroy the Banished device for the second portal</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_CLAIMALLBASES_DESC">Claim all the Base Expansions</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_CLAIMALLBASES_HINT">There are a number of sites suitable for UNSC Base expansions. Claim them all to dominate the map and gain advantage against the Banished forces.</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_CLAIMALLBASES_TRACK">Base Expansion Claimed</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_CROSSTHECHASM_DESC">Cross the Chasm</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_CROSSTHECHASM_HINT">The plates of the artificial amber terrain have separated for Forerunner Sentinel maintenance, creating a large chasm that must be crossed.</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_CROSSTHECHASM_TRACK">Chasm Crossed</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_DEFEATDECIMUS_DESC">Defeat Decimus</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_DEFEATDECIMUS_HINT">Decimus is taking a last stand against the UNSC in an attempt to try and preserve any remaining respect Atriox may have left for him. As Atriox's right hand, defeating Decimus will greatly weaken the Banished's strategical operations on the Ark.</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_DEFEATDECIMUS_TRACK">Decimus Defeated</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_DESTROYCONTROLNODE_DESC">Destroy the Banished Control Node</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_DESTROYCONTROLNODE_HINT">The Banished Control Node is the router networking all the Banished hacking devices on this arm of the Ark.</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_DESTROYCONTROLNODE_TRACK">Banished Control Node Destroyed</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_DESTROYDISHESBEFORESPAWN_DESC">Destroy Banished devices before reinforcements arrive</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_DESTROYDISHESBEFORESPAWN_HINT">The Banished Devices allow the Banished to teleport through the portals. Destroy the Banished Devices before the enemies can come through and reinforce the position.</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_DESTROYDISHESBEFORESPAWN_TRACK">Banished Device destroyed before enemies teleported through</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_DESTROYPORTALS_DESC">Locate and destroy the Banished teleporter hacking devices</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_DESTROYPORTALS_HINT">The Banished are using hacking devices to augment the Forerunner Portals for their own use, giving them a tactical advantage in the war for the Ark.</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_DESTROYPORTALS_TRACK">Banished hacking device destroyed</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_HORNETSSURVIVEREAVERS_DESC">Take out the Reavers without suffering Hornet casualties</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_HORNETSSURVIVEREAVERS_HINT">Ensure the survival of your Hornets from any of the Reaver reinforcements at each of the Banished augmented Portals.</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_HORNETSSURVIVEREAVERS_TRACKING">Reavers destroyed without Hornet casualties</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_LOCATEPORTALS_DESC">Find the Banished hacking devices.</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_LOCATEPORTALS_HINT">The Banished hacking devices emit a unique energy signature that the UNSC have tracked. The Hornet recon squadron have confirmed the locations. Get your assault team to these coordinates.</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_LOCATEPORTALS_TRACK">Banished hacking device found:</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_PRISONERSSURVIVEMISSION_DESC">Complete the mission with all the prisoners freed and alive</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_PRISONERSSURVIVEMISSION_HINT">Free the UNSC prisoners and ensure that they survive the mission on completion.</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_RESCUEUNSCPRISONERS_DESC">Rescue the UNSC Prisoners</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_RESCUEUNSCPRISONERS_HINT">The Banished are holding UNSC infantry captive from previous battles to gain intelligence.</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_RESCUEUNSCPRISONERS_TRACK">UNSC Prisoners Rescued</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_SURVIVEBOMBARDMENTZONE_DESC">Don't let any units get destroyed in the Capital Ship bombardment zone</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_OBJECTIVE_SURVIVEBOMBARDMENTZONE_HINT">Avoid the bombardment zone entirely, or carefully maneuver units through it to avoid the attacks from the Capital Ship.</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_PROGRESSBARLABEL_DECIMUSHEALTH">Decimus</str>
	<str id="M04_TEXT_TUTORIALRESOURCEPRODUCTION">Increase resource production at your base by building supply pads, generators and capturing nearby power nodes.</str>
</string_table>