<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
    <str id="M04A_IGC_PIP_CUT_SUCCESS_02">D</str>
    <str id="M04A_IGC_PIP_ISA_BEACHLANDING_01">Spartan! You have Banished incoming!</str>
    <str id="M04A_IGC_PIP_ISA_BEACHLANDING_02">Alice, they&apos;ve got Locusts at one of your minibases!</str>
    <str id="M04A_IGC_PIP_ISA_SUCCESS_02">I</str>
    <str id="M04A_IGC_PIP_ISA_SUCCESS_SPLIT_02">The captain recommends you keep a small base there to guard the portal, but be ready to move out. I think we&apos;re going to need your help down there again very soon. Isabel, out.</str>
    <str id="M04A_IGC_PIP_MARSQ_BEACHLANDING_03">Fall back!</str>
    <str id="M04A_IGC_PIP_SPAA_BEACHLANDING_01">Already on it, Isabel! Push &apos;em back, troops!</str>
    <str id="M04A_IGC_PIP_SPAA_BEACHLANDING_11">Alright, troops. Looks like the Banished want to put an end to our fun. The Captain is a little busy upstairs so we&apos;re on our own.</str>
    <str id="M04A_IGC_PIP_SPAA_SUCCESS_01">Negative, Isabel, looks like they&apos;ve given up.</str>
    <str id="M04A_OBJECTIVE_01">Survive first wave</str>
    <str id="M04A_OBJECTIVE_04">Defend your base</str>
    <str id="M04A_OBJECTIVE_05">Kill the Scarab</str>
    <str id="M04A_OBJECTIVE_BONUS_01">Get 20 kills with the Scorpion</str>
    <str id="M04A_OBJECTIVE_BONUS_02">Hijack a Locust</str>
    <str id="M04A_OBJECTIVE_BONUS_DESC_01">Use your Scorpion tanks to kill 20 enemy units.</str>
    <str id="M04A_OBJECTIVE_BONUS_DESC_02">Use Alice&apos;s hijack ability to get control of a Locust.</str>
    <str id="M04A_OBJECTIVE_BONUS_UPDATE_02">Units killed by Scorpion:</str>
    <str id="M04A_OBJECTIVE_DESC_01">Fight off the first wave of Banished attackers.</str>
    <str id="M04A_OBJECTIVE_DESC_04">Stop the Banished attackers from destroying your base.</str>
    <str id="M04A_OBJECTIVE_DESC_05">Stop the Scarab before it destroys your base.</str>
    <str id="M04A_OBJECTIVE_OPTIONAL_01">Build 2 turrets on the beach</str>
    <str id="M04A_OBJECTIVE_OPTIONAL_04">Upgrade beach turrets to anti-vehicle</str>
    <str id="M04A_OBJECTIVE_OPTIONAL_DESC_01">Boost your beach defenses by adding 2 turrets.</str>
    <str id="M04A_OBJECTIVE_OPTIONAL_DESC_04">Counter the Locust attacks by upgrading all beach turrets to anti-vehicle.</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_IGC_ISA_SCARAB_01">It&apos;s a Scarab! They&apos;re sending in a Scarab!</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_ISA_SCARABENDING_04">I&apos;m impressed! Is that it? Are there more incoming?</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_ISA_SCARABINTRO_01">That&apos;s it, Alice, they&apos;ve stopped! Wait...no, there&apos;s something else, and it&apos;s very big...</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_NIGHT_NIGHTINGALE_INTRO_02">Right here, sir. Someone need patching up?</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_SPAA_BUILDTURRETS_02">We&apos;ll need some turrets for support. Get some built and upgrade them to anti-vehicle turrets.</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_SPAA_DEFENDBASE_01">Defend the base! Nobody lays a finger on our HQ!</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_SPAA_GROUNDTROOPS_01">The ground troops are going to keep coming through the shallows. Let&apos;s make sure we have some Scorpions waiting to greet them.</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_SPAA_HERETHEYCOME_01">Here they come! Scorpion, wake up that gun!</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_SPAA_LOCUSTSINTRO_01">Keep those Locusts away from our base! Get some Cyclops in there!</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_SPAA_LOCUSTSINTRO_02">Cyclops teams, take out those Locusts!</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_SPAA_NIGHTINGALE_INTRO_01">That was just the beginning, they&apos;ll be back soon. Where&apos;s that Nightingale we called for?</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_SPAA_NIGHTINGALE_INTRO_03">Keep our Cyclops and Scorpions battle ready. We won&apos;t be able to hold this position without them.</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_SPAA_NIGHTINGALE_INTRO_04">We need to set up a defensive perimeter to hold them back. Let&apos;s get to work.</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_SPAA_OPTIONALOBJECTIVE_02">Alice, I recommend you upgrade the turret with anti-vehicle weaponry.</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_SPAA_PROTECTBASE_01">They&apos;re getting too close! Protect the base at all costs!</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_SPAA_REPAIRUNITS_01">Our Scorpions have taken a pounding! Get the Nightingale over there now!</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_SPAA_REPAIRUNITS_02">Our Cyclops need repairs. Get &apos;em fixed!</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_SPAA_SCARABENDING_01">Thanks for the heads up, Isabel. I guess we&apos;ve got them running scared.</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_SPAA_SCARABENDING_02">You heard Isabel, get ready, we&apos;re going to have our work cut out for us with this one!</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_SPAA_SCARABENDING_03">Keep hitting that Scarab! If we don&apos;t break it, it&apos;s over for us!</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_SPAA_SCARABENDING_04">Isabel, Scarab is down. Repeat, Scarab is down.</str>
    <str id="M04A_PIP_SPAA_WENEEDSOMESUPPORT_01">We&apos;ll need some turrets for support. Get some built and upgrade them to anti-vehicle turrets.</str>
    <str id="M04A_TEX_CALLOUT_BEACH_TURRET_01">Beach Turret 1</str>
    <str id="M04A_TEX_CALLOUT_BEACH_TURRET_02">Beach Turret 2</str>
    <str id="M04A_TEX_CALLOUT_PORTAL_CONTROLLER">Portal Controller</str>
    <str id="M04A_TEX_HINT_TURRET_UPGRADE">Upgrade a turret by selecting it and choosing Anti-Vehicle Turret from the radial menu</str>
    <str id="M04A_TEX_HUD_LABEL_BASE">Base Health</str>
    <str id="M04A_TEX_HUD_LABEL_SCARAB">Scarab Health</str>
    <str id="M04A_TEX_OPTIONALOBJECTIVE_01">Build a turret to defend the beach</str>
    <str id="M04A_TEX_OPTIONALOBJECTIVE_02">Upgrade the turret at the beach to an anti-vehicle turret</str>
    <str id="M04A_TEX_TUT_LOCUSTS_01">Locusts are excellent at destroying base structures. Counter them with units strong against vehicles such as the Cyclops.</str>
    <str id="M04A_TEX_TUT_NIGHTINGALE_01">Nightingales are the Spirit of Fire&apos;s support response unit. They will automatically repair and heal damaged vehicles and injured units.</str>
    <str id="M04A_TEX_TUT_SCORPIONS_01">Scorpions are excellent at destroying enemy infantry units.</str>
    <str id="M04A_TEX_TUT_SCORPIONS_02">You can build Scorpions at the Garage once you have upgraded your HQ tech.</str>
</string_table>