<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
    <str id="M05_COMMS_AND_GENERIC_WAVE_01">Enemies to the north!</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_AND_GENERIC_WAVE_02">Hostiles coming in from the north!</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_AND_GENERIC_WAVE_03">The enemy are sending in units from the north-east!</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_AND_GENERIC_WAVE_04">We&apos;ve got enemies inbound from the north-east!</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_AND_GENERIC_WAVE_05">They&apos;re sending in units from the east!</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_AND_GENERIC_WAVE_06">Enemies incoming from the east!</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_AND_GENERIC_WAVE_07">We have enemies coming in from the north and east!</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_AND_GENERIC_WAVE_08">Enemies inbound along north and east routes!</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_AND_GENERIC_WAVE_09">They&apos;re coming in from everywhere!</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_AND_GENERIC_WAVE_10">Enemies inbound from all routes! Repeat, enemies inbound from ALL routes!</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_AND_SPECIAL_ENCOUNTERS_01">Douglas, they&apos;ve sent in Banshees to attack the base!</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_AND_SPECIAL_ENCOUNTERS_02">The base is under fire from Banshees!</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_AND_SPECIAL_ENCOUNTERS_03">They&apos;re attacking our second base!</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_AND_SPECIAL_ENCOUNTERS_04">They&apos;re sending in Hunters to take out our Kodiaks!</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_AND_WAVE_FOUR_01">We&apos;ve got signals on the monitors again! A lot of them! Infantry to the north-east!</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_IGC_AND_REAVER_INTRO_01">Reaver! Isabel briefed me on them! They&apos;re bypassing the ravines! We need to take them out or they&apos;ll be at the cannon in no time!</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_KODIA_KODIAKCHOKES_02">Acknowledged. Calculating trajectories now.</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_SPAD_LIGHT_BRIDGE_DEACTIVATE_01">So long!</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_SPAD_LIGHT_BRIDGE_DEACTIVATE_02">Should&apos;ve packed a chute!</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_SPAD_LIGHT_BRIDGE_DEACTIVATE_03">Watch your step!</str>
    <str id="M05_COMMS_SPAD_LIGHT_BRIDGE_DEACTIVATE_04">I&apos;m never going to get tired of doing that!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_BARRICADEINCOMING_01">Douglas, there&apos;s a surge of Banished at the east barricade!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_BARRICADEINCOMING_02">The east barricade is under attack from the Banished, we&apos;ve got to protect it!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_BARRICADEINCOMING_03">Don&apos;t let them break through the east barricade! We need to defend it!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_BARRICADEINCOMING_04">We need to defend the east barricade! The Banished are trying to break through!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_BARRICADEINCOMING_05">The enemy is trying to break through the west barricade, we can&apos;t lose it!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_BARRICADEINCOMING_06">Douglas, the west barricade is under attack!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_BARRICADEINCOMING_07">Banished at the west barricade!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_BARRICADEINCOMING_08">The Banished are attacking the west barricade!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_BARRICADELOSING_01">Douglas, we&apos;re going to lose the west barricade if we don&apos;t stop the Banished there!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_BARRICADELOSING_02">The west barricade is being destroyed, we&apos;ve got to stop them breaking through!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_BARRICADELOSING_03">We&apos;re in danger of losing the west barricade, Douglas!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_BARRICADELOSING_04">They&apos;ve nearly broken through the west barricade!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_BARRICADELOSING_05">The east barricade is under heavy attack, if we lose it, they&apos;ll be able to get through!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_BARRICADELOSING_06">The Banished are breaking through the east barricade!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_BARRICADELOSING_07">The enemy has nearly destroyed the east barricade!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_BARRICADELOSING_08">The east barricade is almost destroyed, we&apos;ve got to stop them!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_BARRICADELOST_01">Douglas, we&apos;ve lost the east barricade! The Banished have broken through!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_BARRICADELOST_02">The west barricade is down! The Banished are coming through!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_BARRICADELOST_03">That&apos;s both barricades down, Douglas. We&apos;re going to have to fight harder to defend the cannon now!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_CANNON_ATTACKED_01">Douglas, the Particle Cannon is under attack! You&apos;ve got to push them back!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_CANNON_ATTACKED_02">We&apos;ve got to protect the particle cannon until it breaks through the shields!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_CANNON_DAMAGE_STATE_01">The particle cannon is taking hits! We&apos;ve got to protect it!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_CANNON_DAMAGE_STATE_02">The particle cannon is at twenty-percent integrity! We&apos;re going to lose it!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_CANNON_DAMAGE_STATE_03">The particle cannon won&apos;t last much longer! If we lose it, we lose everything!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_CANNON_WARNING_01">They&apos;re targeting the particle cannon! We can&apos;t lose it!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_CANNON_WARNING_02">Enemies are closing in on our particle cannon!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_CANNON_WARNING_03">Enemies at the particle cannon! Clear them out!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_CYCLOPSDROP_01">Captain, we could use some help. Requesting a Cyclops drop.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_HEALING_01">The Particle Cannon&apos;s taken damage! We need to repair it with restoration drones!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_LIGHTBRIDGE_01">Douglas, the Banished have activated the lightbridge, it&apos;ll give them a shorter route to the cannon!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_ODSTDROP_01">Captain, an ODST drop would be appreciated right now.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_POSTWAVETHREE_01">Douglas, the monitors have gone quiet - for now.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_PREP_01">Douglas, I&apos;m starting to get early warning alerts on those monitors. The Banished will be here soon!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_PREP_02">Douglas, that amber looks awfully fragile, could we use that to cut off some of their routes?</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_TURRET_01">We need some defences! Captain, requesting a turret drop!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_EIGHT_01">Douglas, the cannon&apos;s nearly broken through the carrier&apos;s shields. I just need a little bit longer.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_EIGHT_03">A</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_EIGHT_04">That was him.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_EIGHT_05">F</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_EIGHT_06">Infantry to the north-east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_EIGHT_07">Enemy armor coming from the east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_EIGHT_08">More armor, this time from the north-east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_EIGHT_09">Wraiths to the north-east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_EIGHT_10">They&apos;re sending in infantry from the east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_EIGHT_11">We have a Hunter and infantry coming from the north-east, they&apos;re after our base!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_EIGHT_12">More infantry from the east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_EIGHT_13">Enemy vehicles inbound from the east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_EIGHT_14">Wraiths and Locusts from the north-east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_FIVE_01">The monitors are lit up again - wait, they&apos;re coming in from a new route! We&apos;ve got enemy vehicles inbound from the east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_FIVE_03">Enemy armor from the east, Douglas!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_FIVE_04">They&apos;re sending in more Ghosts from the east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_FIVE_05">Douglas! Another charge of Ghosts from the east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_FIVE_06">Douglas! One of their Wraiths is making a beeline for our base!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_FOUR_01">Infantry and enemy armor coming from the north-east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_FOUR_02">Douglas, to the north! The Banished have sent in a couple of Wraiths!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_FOUR_03">More vehicles to the north-east! They&apos;ve got a Locust!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_FOUR_04">Another Wraith incoming from the north-east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_FOUR_05">Enemy vehicles inbound from the north-east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_ONE_01">Here they come! Infantry coming in from the north!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_ONE_02">More ground troops coming in from the north!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_ONE_03">Douglas, we&apos;ve got Hunters coming from the north!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_POSTEIGHTUPDATE_02">W</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_SEVEN_01">Infantry coming from the north-east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_SEVEN_02">Jump Brutes to the east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_SEVEN_03">Uh oh, we&apos;ve got a wave of suicide grunts coming from the north-east.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_SEVEN_04">Jump Brutes coming from the north, they&apos;re heading towards our base!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_SEVEN_05">Suicide Grunts inbound from the east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_SIX_01">Monitors show enemy vehicles coming from the east.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_SIX_02">They&apos;re sending in a Locust from the east to attack our base!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_SIX_03">More vehicles from the east, they&apos;ve got heavy armor this time!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_SIX_06">Ghosts and Wraiths inbound from the east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_SIX_07">Douglas, we&apos;ve got Wraiths coming from the east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_SIX_08">Ground troops coming in from the east, heading directly towards our base. Looks like they&apos;re support for a Locust strike!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_THREE_01">Douglas, you have enemy infantry coming in, this time from the north-east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_THREE_02">Hunters and infantry to the north-east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_THREE_03">Infantry inbound from the north-east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_THREE_04">More infantry from the north-east!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_TWO_01">We have more infantry inbound from the north!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_AND_WAVE_TWO_02">Douglas, Hunters to the north!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_ATR_WAVE_EIGHT_01">Ah, little Spartan - I see you&apos;ve recovered from our introduction. It seems you need another &apos;lesson&apos;.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_CUT_WAVE_NINE_01">Douglas, Professor! The Shipmaster has diverted some of his air units from the attack on the Spirit of Fire. They&apos;re heading your way.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_IGC_AND_CANNON_FIRES_01">I can overload the cannon and deliver one huge final blast, but it&apos;ll completely shut it down afterwards.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_IGC_AND_CANNON_FIRES_02">Here goes.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_IGC_AND_CANNON_FIRES_03">It worked! The shields are down!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_IGC_AND_PARTICLE_CANNON_02">Hard to estimate, Captain, this thing didn&apos;t exactly come with instructions. I&apos;ll draw as much power as I can into the cannon, but we&apos;re going to make one heck of a target.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_IGC_AND_PARTICLE_CANNON_03">I&apos;ve set up monitoring equipment along each of the possible routes, so I can alert Douglas as the Banished arrive.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_IGC_CUT_CANNON_FIRES_01">P</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_IGC_CUT_CANNON_FIRES_02">D</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_IGC_CUT_PARTICLE_CANNON_01">T</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_IGC_CUT_PARTICLE_CANNON_02">Agreed. Douglas, the Banished carrier is Atriox&apos;s biggest weapon and only means of slipstream transport, so he&apos;ll be sending everything he can to destroy that cannon.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_IGC_CUT_PARTICLE_CANNON_03">And with Atriox redirecting all his forces your way, he&apos;ll be leaving the base beneath the carrier relatively clear, giving Jerome and Isabel a chance to infiltrate it.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_IGC_CUT_PARTICLE_CANNON_SPLIT_03">They&apos;ll be standing by for word when you&apos;ve broken through the carrier&apos;s shields. Hold the line, team.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_IGC_SPAD_CANNON_FIRES_01">Nice shooting, Professor! Get ready for extraction back to the Spirit of Fire. Jerome, this is Douglas. The shield is down and you are a go.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_IGC_SPAD_PARTICLE_CANNON_01">Now that we&apos;ve crippled their portals, the Banished will have to make a traditional frontal assault using whatever local forces they have.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_IGC_SPAD_PARTICLE_CANNON_02">To reach the cannon, the Banished will have to pass through those choke points to the east and west, so we&apos;ve set up UNSC barriers there to defend them.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_IGC_SPAD_PARTICLE_CANNON_SPLIT_02">We need to make sure they hold fast.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_IGC_SPAJ_ROGER_01">Roger that, Douglas. Now get your troops clear. You don&apos;t want to be down there when Isabel gets started.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_KODIAKCHOKES_01">Kodiaks One and Two, this is Douglas. Stop as many as you can from reaching the east and west barriers. Stay alert.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_LIGHTBRIDGE_01">Got it, Professor. I&apos;ll see what I can do.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_PREP_01">Jerome, this is Douglas. We&apos;ve got a confirmed hit on the carrier&apos;s shield. It&apos;s going to take a while to punch through but it&apos;s working.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_PREP_03">Way ahead of you.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_WAVE_EIGHT_02">Sure thing, Professor. Think they&apos;ve taken enough punishment yet?</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_WAVE_EIGHT_03">Atriox.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_WAVE_EIGHT_04">Good. I&apos;ve got some anger to work off.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_WAVE_FIVE_02">These guys are relentless! I can see how they managed to survive the Covenant during the war!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_WAVE_FIVE_07">If we lose that, we won&apos;t be able to hold the line. Let&apos;s make sure that doesn&apos;t happen.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_WAVE_FOUR_01">Roger that, Anders. Target those Wraiths, troops! We can&apos;t let them through!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_WAVE_FOUR_03">They&apos;ll wreck our barricades in no time. Let&apos;s head them off, fast!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_WAVE_NINE_02">We need to get some anti-air defenses, ASAP! Turrets! Wolverines!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_WAVE_ONE_04">Hunters? Make sure our Kodiaks are protected!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_WAVE_POSTEIGHTUPDATE_01">What&apos;s the status on that shield? It&apos;s Banished central down here!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_WAVE_POSTEIGHTUPDATE_03">You got it.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_WAVE_SEVEN_01">They&apos;re trying to split our forces. Stay sharp.</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_WAVE_SEVEN_02">Head them off fast before they can detonate!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_WAVE_SEVEN_03">I</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_WAVE_SIX_01">I</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_WAVE_SIX_09">Defend the base, troops!</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_WAVE_THREE_02">I</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAD_WAVE_THREE_03">L</str>
    <str id="M05_PIP_SPAJ_PREP_01">Good to hear. We&apos;re making our way now. Keep that carrier busy for us.</str>
    <str id="M05_TEX_TUT_REAVER_01">Banished Reavers are anti-air walkers that have the predatory leap ability to jump over obstacles.</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_BARRICADE_E_CALLOUT">East Barricade</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_BARRICADE_W_CALLOUT">West Barricade</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_CANNON_CALLOUT">Particle Cannon</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_CANNON_HEAL_HELP">The Cannon is damaged. Use Restoration Drones to heal it.</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_CANNON_HUD_LABEL">Cannon Health</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_LIGHTBRIDGE_HELP">Kill the Brutes near the terminal before you can use it to turn the lightbridge off.</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_MISSION_OBJECTIVE_01">Defend the Particle Cannon</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_OBJ_BONUS_LIGHTBRIDGE_01">Kill 10 enemies with the lightbridge</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_OBJ_BONUS_LIGHTBRIDGE_01_UPDATE">Units killed by lightbridge:</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_OBJ_BONUS_LIGHTBRIDGESHORTDESCR_01">Deactivate the lightbridge while enemy units are crossing to drop them into the chasm below.</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_OBJ_BONUS_TURRETDROP_01">Kill 5 units with Turret Drop</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_OBJ_BONUS_TURRETDROP_01_UPDATE">Units killed by Turret Drop:</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_OBJ_BONUS_TURRETDROPSHORTDESCR_01">Use the Turret Drop leader power to kill 5 enemy units. Access the power by holding @Left_Trigger@.</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_OBJ_OPTIONAL_BARRICADES_01">Keep the barricades intact</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_OBJ_OPTIONAL_BARRICADESSHORTDESCR_01">The barricades are a critical part of the cannon&apos;s defenses, keep them intact throughout the invasion.</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_OBJ_OPTIONAL_BUILDBASES_01">Build on all available base plots</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_OBJ_OPTIONAL_BUILDBASES_01_UPDATE">Base plots occupied:</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_OBJ_OPTIONAL_BUILDBASESSHORTDESCR_01">Locate and build on all available base plots to increase your chances against the Banished invasion.</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_SHIELD_HUD_LABEL">Carrier Health</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_SHIELDBREACH_HUD_LABEL">Carrier shield breach in...</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_SIEGE_GUN">Long range Siege Turrets are available to build at your base.</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_TERMINAL_CALLOUT">Lightbridge Terminal</str>
    <str id="M05_TEXT_TIMER_HUD_LABEL">Mission Timer</str>
</string_table>