<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
    <str id="M06A_TEX_TUT_VULTURES_01">Vultures are armed with devastating Phoenix tactical missiles as their special ability. Press @special_power@ to launch a missile at the overshield.</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_TUT_PREPBANISHEDFLEET_01">Prepare for the Banished fleet</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_TUT_CONTROLGROUPS_01">The Vulture is a slow moving unit, so assign it to a separate control group so as not to slow down your Hornets.</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_TUT_ARCHERMISSILES_01">U</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_SECONDARYOBJECTIVE_02_DESC">Boost your capabilities by building a minibase</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_SECONDARYOBJECTIVE_02">Build a minibase</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_SECONDARYOBJECTIVE_01_DESC">Expand your defences to the flank by building two turrets to stop more Spirits getting through</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_SECONDARYOBJECTIVE_01">Set up AA defences on the flank</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_PRIMARYOBJECTIVE_04">Cut down the Banished ships before they can reach the Halo ring</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_PRIMARYOBJECTIVE_01">Destroy the Banished air production facilities</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_NEWOBJECTIVE_04_DESC">Destroy another 50 Spirits before too many escape</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_NEWOBJECTIVE_04">Defeat the final wave</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_NEWOBJECTIVE_01_DESC">Destroy 125 Spirits before too many escape</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_NEWOBJECTIVE_01">Stop the Banished airlift</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_NEWBONUSOBJECTIVE_02_DESC">Prevent all Spirits in the final wave from reaching the Halo ring</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_NEWBONUSOBJECTIVE_02">Destroy all Spirits in the final wave</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_NEWBONUSOBJECTIVE_01_DESC">Use the Vulture&apos;s Phoenix missile to knock a Spirit out of the sky</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_NEWBONUSOBJECTIVE_01">Destroy a Spirit with a Phoenix missle</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_HUD_BAR_04">Final Spirits Destroyed</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_HUD_BAR_03">Final Spirits Escaped</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_HUD_BAR_02">Spirits Destroyed</str>
    <str id="M06A_TEX_HUD_BAR_01">Spirits Escaped</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_VULT_FIREMISSILES_01">Launching missiles.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_VULT_CONTROLGROUPS_03">G</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_SPAJ_PREPDEFENSES_01">You heard him, squadron. Scramble!</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_SPAJ_OVERSHIELDDESTROYED_01">That&apos;s our opening, Hornets. Move in and mop up any survivors!</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_SPAJ_INCOMINGWAVE_04">H</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_SPAJ_INCOMINGFLEET_01">It&apos;s go time. Shoot down any ship that tries to get through!</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_SPAJ_FIRSTAIRFACILITY_01">We have eyes on an aircraft facility.  Level it, Hornets!</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_SPAJ_CONTROLGROUPS_02">Good work, squadron. Let&apos;s take out the rest of those facilities.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_SPAJ_CLEAROUTFORCES_01">We can&apos;t have them making even more flyers, can we? Sounds like we&apos;ve got new targets.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_SPAJ_ARCHERMISSILES_01">That&apos;s a confirmed hit.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_ISA_TURRETOFFLINE_03">The enemy have taken out one of our turrets!</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_ISA_TURRETOFFLINE_02">We&apos;ve lost a turret!</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_ISA_TURRETOFFLINE_01">Jerome, one of our turrets has just gone offline!</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_ISA_TAKETURRETS_01">Jerome, they&apos;ve got turret positions already set up for us.  How thoughtful of them.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_ISA_PREPDEFENSES_01">I&apos;m showing all clear, Captain. All Banished air facilities are down. Not too soon either - we&apos;re detecting incoming air units, ETA two minutes   and counting.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_ISA_INCOMINGWAVE_03">More Banished on the way.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_ISA_INCOMINGWAVE_02">T</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_ISA_INCOMINGWAVE_01">Y</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_ISA_CLEAROUTFORCES_01">Captain, I&apos;m detecting several Banished aircraft production facilities.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_SPIRITARRIVES_01">Prioritize those Spirits, Jerome. Those troop carriers can transport a lot of Brutes!</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_REPLACEAIRFACILITY_03">Whenever you clear out a Banished air facility, replace it with one of our own. You&apos;re going to need all the air unit support you can get before the fleet arrives.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_REPLACEAIRFACILITY_02">Get an air facility built on that empty plot, Jerome. We&apos;re going to need to be ready for that fleet.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_REPLACEAIRFACILITY_01">Spartan, you can use that base foundation to build an air facility of your own . You&apos;re going to need more air units when the Banished fleet arrives.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_PREPDEFENSES_SPLIT_01">Get your ships combat ready, upgrade any outstanding turrets to anti-air and replace any lost units. That fleet is going to be coming in fast.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_PREPDEFENSES_01">This is it, Spartan. The Banished fleet is moving towards you now. You only have two minutes to prepare.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_PLAYERKILLSALLSHIPS_01">Impressive work, Spartan. We&apos;re not tracking a single Banished ship.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_FAILSTATE_02">We&apos;ve lost, team. We have no way of stopping that fleet now.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_FAILSTATE_01">We let too many ships through, Spartan. We can&apos;t possibly hold the Halo against those kind of reinforcements.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_ENEMIESESCAPE_02">A few too many slipped through the net, we&apos;ve got to tighten it up or they&apos;ll wipe out our forces on the Halo.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_ENEMIESESCAPE_01">We need a higher hit rate than that, Spartan. If we continue to let the Banished through our forces on the Halo will be destroyed.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_ENEMIESDOWNED_01">Good work, Spartan. Keep that up!</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_DIVERTEDRESOURCES_03">I&apos;ve diverted more resources to you, Jerome. Use them to set up anti-air defenses and increase your air presence.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_DIVERTEDRESOURCES_02">I&apos;m sending more resources your way, Spartan. Increase our defenses down there.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_DIVERTEDRESOURCES_01">Jerome, I&apos;m diverting resources from the Spirit of Fire&apos;s reserves to help you get those air facilities up and running. We need to pour everything we have into this.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_CONTROLGROUPS_01">Keep going, Jerome. We can&apos;t leave a single one of those facilities standing. Every ship that gets through jeopardizes our ability to safely launch the Halo.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_CLEAROUTFORCES_02">As you neutralize those facilities, start setting up anti-air turrets. You&apos;ll need every advantage to intercept them before they reach the access point.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_CLEAROUTFORCES_01">Jerome, eliminate all ground forces along that flight path so we can establish a kill zone.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_BUILDANTIAIR_04">Get some anti-air turrets built, Jerome. We won&apos;t have much time once the Banished are on their way.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_BUILDANTIAIR_03">You need to build some anti-air turrets, Spartan. We won&apos;t be able to stop the Banished flyers without them.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_BUILDANTIAIR_02">Build anti-air turrets as you clear out the  flight path, Jerome. We need to make sure the route is covered from all sides.</str>
    <str id="M06A_PIP_CUT_BUILDANTIAIR_01">Remember to build anti-air turret defenses along the flight path. They&apos;ll be vital in stopping the Banished fleet getting to that portal.</str>
    <str id="M06A_IGC_PIP_VULT_ENGINEERSOVERSHIELD_01">They won&apos;t last long, sir.</str>
    <str id="M06A_IGC_PIP_SPAJ_WINCONDITION_02">Do we follow them, sir? They&apos;re still dangerous.</str>
    <str id="M06A_IGC_PIP_SPAJ_KILLSCOUTS_01">Banished scouts! Take them down!</str>
    <str id="M06A_IGC_PIP_SPAJ_ENGINEERSSLOWINGUS_01">Those Engineers&apos; shields are slowing us down. Time to call in the big guns, Captain?</str>
    <str id="M06A_IGC_PIP_SPAJ_ENGINEERSOVERSHIELD_01">Time to call in the big guns. Captain?</str>
    <str id="M06A_IGC_PIP_SPAJ_BASEWITHTURRETS_01">Spirit of Fire Actual, the Banished have their own air defenses set up here. It may take us some time to clear this out.</str>
    <str id="M06A_IGC_PIP_HORN_ENGINEERSOVERSHIELD_01">These shields are slowing us down, sir.</str>
    <str id="M06A_IGC_PIP_GHOST_ALARM_01">Humans! Sounds the alarm!</str>
    <str id="M06A_IGC_PIP_CUT_WINCONDITION_03">Negative. We have more pressing problems. I need you to get to the center of the Ark ASAP. You&apos;re headed to the Halo.</str>
    <str id="M06A_IGC_PIP_CUT_WINCONDITION_01">We did it, team. We&apos;ve broken the  Banished invasion fleet and the survivors are scattered and being recalled.</str>
    <str id="M06A_IGC_PIP_CUT_ENGINEERSOVERSHIELD_01">Affirmative, Spartan. Vulture 1, that&apos;s a confirmed go. Take out that overshield.</str>
    <str id="M06A_IGC_PIP_CUT_BASEWITHTURRETS_01">We can&apos;t afford that, Jerome. I&apos;m authorizing a missile strike. Ready on your mark.</str>
</string_table>