<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
    <str id="MBS_M00_PIP_AND_01">I</str>
    <str id="MBS_M00_PIP_AND_02">It would be a lot faster if you let me go down with them, Captain.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M00_PIP_AND_ADD01">I&apos;ve cleared up the scans a bit and it looks like there&apos;s a UNSC outpost or research station, but it&apos;s heavily damaged.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M00_PIP_AND_ADD01_SPLIT_02">It doesn&apos;t look good, but the Spartans will handle it. They always do.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M00_PIP_CUT_01">Professor Anders, any update on the source of that signal?</str>
    <str id="MBS_M00_PIP_CUT_02">Without Serina here I need you on the ship, Professor. Besides, we don&apos;t know what&apos;s waiting for us down there.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M00_PIP_CUT_03">Jerome, get Red Team to the Professor&apos;s coordinates, ASAP. I want you to make first contact with whoever&apos;s sending that signal.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M00_PIP_SPAJ_01">Understood, sir. We&apos;ll find them.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M00_TEX_INTELREPORT">Spirit of Fire recon teams are on the ground to meet Red Team.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M00_TEX_SUMMARY_01">Use Red Team to investigate and find the source of the signal.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M01_CUT_01">T</str>
    <str id="MBS_M01_PIP_AND_01">Captain, Isabel said the portal her outpost was using to contact Earth closed without warning. Once we start this fight, we have no way of calling for help if we need it.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M01_PIP_CUT_01">We need to hit the Banished with a surprise attack to put them on the back foot, then move south and establish an HQ. Once we have a base, we can begin our attack on Decimus.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M01_PIP_CUT_02">That&apos;s what you&apos;ll be working on, Professor. I need you to find us a way to get word back home.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M01_PIP_CUT_SPLIT_02">In the meantime, it&apos;s up to us to hold the line here. Let&apos;s show them what the Spirit of Fire can do.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M01_PIP_ISA_01">Captain, I appreciate a good rousing speech as much as the next AI but Atriox has had months to set up his forces on the Ark.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M01_PIP_ISA_02">D</str>
    <str id="MBS_M01_PIP_ISA_SPLIT_01">Even if we could find him, attacking him head on would be suicide.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M01_TEX_INTELREPORT">Hellbringer infantry are standing by to clear Banished defenses.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M01_TEX_SUMMARY_01">Lead the UNSC in an assault against Decimus&apos; salvage operation.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M02_PIP_AND_01">I</str>
    <str id="MBS_M02_PIP_AND_02">The Cartographer&apos;s defenses make it almost impenetrable; the only way up to it is by a Forerunner elevator.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M02_PIP_AND_03">If you can get access to the local Forerunner control towers I can take control of the elevator and take us up. It&apos;s our only chance of getting inside.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M02_PIP_CUT_01">The intelligence we captured at Decimus&apos; base indicates the Banished are using something called &apos;The Cartographer&apos;. What can you tell us, Isabel?</str>
    <str id="MBS_M02_PIP_CUT_02">We&apos;ll have to take it. We need to hit the Banished again before they find out what we discovered at their base.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M02_PIP_CUT_SPLIT_02">Get to the Cartographer and find out what Atriox is planning. Be careful, the Banished may still have traffic moving along the route.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M02_PIP_ISA_01">The Cartographer is a map of everything on the Ark; that means Atriox could use it to locate key systems and weapons on this installation.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M02_TEX_INTELREPORT">Hornets are on standby at the Spirit of Fire, ready to counter any enemy heavy armor.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M02_TEX_SUMMARY_01">Capture Forerunner Control Towers to gain access to the Cartographer</str>
    <str id="MBS_M02A_PIP_SPAA_01">Start log: senior chief petty officer Alice One-Three-Zero. I managed to make it out of the outpost and I&apos;ve been tracking an enemy convoy to one of their compounds.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M02A_PIP_SPAA_02">They took some of our troops prisoner back there, and I&apos;m not going to leave them behind.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M02A_PIP_SPAA_03">I&apos;ve spotted another abandoned research post, and I should be able to use it to send an encrypted message to the Captain.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M02A_PIP_SPAA_04">I don&apos;t think they&apos;re expecting trouble. Time for me to give them some. End log.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M02A_TEX_INTELREPORT">Even a lone Spartan can be a formidable force.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M02A_TEX_SUMMARY_01">Rescue UNSC prisoners with Alice-130 from deep behind enemy lines.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M03_PIP_AND_01">Understood, Captain. Isabel gave me everything the UNSC already knows about the area, and it looks like we&apos;ll need to reach the Map Room.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M03_PIP_AND_02">I</str>
    <str id="MBS_M03_PIP_AND_03">Also, I&apos;ve been running scans as we get closer; there seem to be large power signatures from the central chamber nearby.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M03_PIP_AND_SPLIT_03">I</str>
    <str id="MBS_M03_PIP_CUT_01">Professor, once you get inside the Cartographer I need you to find out what Atriox is using it for.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M03_PIP_ISA_01">B</str>
    <str id="MBS_M03_PIP_ISA_02">I</str>
    <str id="MBS_M03_TEX_INTELREPORT">Wolverine anti-air vehicles are on standby to counter enemy air units.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M03_TEX_SUMMARY_01">Protect Anders from Forerunner defenses to reach the Cartographer&apos;s Map Room.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04_PIP_CUT_01">Atriox&apos;s forces are too strong and too well entrenched for us to fight head-on.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04_PIP_CUT_02">Some of Atriox&apos;s troops will be stranded and the rest won&apos;t be able to redeploy as easily. It&apos;ll give us a fighting chance.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04_PIP_CUT_03">You&apos;ll need to neutralize each of the portals on the approach to the control hub or we&apos;ll be overrun.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04_PIP_CUT_SPLIT_01">But he&apos;s spread his troops far and wide, by abusing the Ark&apos;s network of portals. That&apos;s his biggest mistake.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04_PIP_CUT_SPLIT_03">To make things worse, our scouts believe Decimus arrived a few hours ago and he&apos;ll be looking for a rematch. Make sure he doesn&apos;t walk away from this one.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04_PIP_ISA_01">Thanks to the information the Professor got from the Cartographer, we know Atriox&apos;s key controller for the portal network is nearby.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04_PIP_ISA_02">The bad news is that we&apos;ve detected mass deployment of Banished forces in this area, which means Atriox knows of our plans.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04_PIP_ISA_SPLIT_01">If we destroy it, it&apos;ll cripple his ability to use that portal network.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04_PIP_ISA_SPLIT_02">The Banished will do everything they can to defend that portal control hub.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04_PIP_SPAJ_01">Looking forward to it, sir.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04_TEX_INTELREPORT_01">Portals can be used to travel across the battlefield when no longer under Banished control.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04_TEX_SUMMARY_01">Cripple the Banished&apos;s portal network</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04A_PIP_CUT_01">Spirit of Fire to Alice One Three Zero, we have deactivated the Banished&apos;s portal network, are you in position?</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04A_PIP_CUT_02">The Banished will be diverting their remaining troops from the network battle to try and reactivate it. Don&apos;t let that happen.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04A_PIP_CUT_03">Alice, you&apos;re going to have to take command on this one. The Spirit of Fire is under attack from the Banished carrier and I need to have all my attention focused on the bridge.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04A_PIP_ISA_01">Spirit of Fire to Alice One Three Zero, we have deactivated the Banished&apos;s portal network, are you in position?</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04A_PIP_ISA_02">The Spirit of Fire is under heavy attack from the Banished carrier, so he&apos;s asked me to be your liaison while he deals with it.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04A_PIP_ISA_SPLIT_02">You&apos;ve made quite an impression on the Banished down there, we&apos;re showing signs of massive troop movement your way.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04A_PIP_ISA_SPLIT_03">Can you hold out while we&apos;re dealing with this attack?</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04A_PIP_SPAA_01">Isabel? I wasn&apos;t expecting to hear from you. Where&apos;s the captain?</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04A_PIP_SPAA_02">Don&apos;t worry, Isabel. I&apos;ve got this one. Good to be working with you. Alice, out.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04A_PIP_SPAA_03">Don&apos;t worry, Captain, I&apos;ve got this. Alice, out.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04A_TEX_INTELREPORT_01">Set up defenses on the beachheads to intercept the enemy.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M04A_TEX_SUMMARY_01">Defend the last portal controller against a Banished invasion.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M05_PIP_AND_01">W</str>
    <str id="MBS_M05_PIP_AND_SAFE_01">Captain, we&apos;re on site of the Forerunner particle cannon we discovered at the Cartographer.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M05_PIP_AND_SAFE_SPLIT_01">We&apos;ve targeted the Banished carrier and we&apos;re ready to fire on your say so.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M05_PIP_AND_TURRETS_01">We have turret emplacements set up across the ops area. Use those to counter whatever the Banished throw at you.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M05_PIP_CUT_01">Do it. The Spirit of Fire wasn&apos;t built to fight a carrier like the Enduring Conviction, and we can&apos;t hold it off for long.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M05_PIP_CUT_03">That&apos;s where the second part of Isabel&apos;s plan comes in. Jerome, are you and Isabel in place?</str>
    <str id="MBS_M05_PIP_CUT_04">Good, be ready to get Isabel inside the carrier once its shields are down.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M05_PIP_CUT_05">Time is of the essence, people. Keep in touch and I&apos;ll do what I can from up here. Good luck.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M05_PIP_CUT_SPLIT_04">D</str>
    <str id="MBS_M05_PIP_SPAD_01">Captain, we&apos;re on site of the Forerunner particle cannon we discovered at the Cartographer.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M05_PIP_SPAD_SPLIT_01">We&apos;ve targeted the Banished carrier and we&apos;re ready to fire on your say so.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M05_PIP_SPAJ_01">Yes, sir. We&apos;re making our approach to the Banished base beneath that carrier.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M05_TEX_INTELREPORT">Build turrets and deploy your army across Banished routes leading to the cannon.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M05_TEX_SUMMARY_01">Protect the Forerunner particle cannon from the Banished until it breaks through the carrier&apos;s shields</str>
    <str id="MBS_M06_PIP_CUT_01">J</str>
    <str id="MBS_M06_PIP_SPAA_01">Roger that, Jerome. My team is standing by and ready to roll on your say so.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M06_PIP_SPAA_02">I&apos;ve got your back, Jerome. You just worry about getting there. Good luck.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M06_PIP_SPAJ_01">Alice, this is Jerome. Isabel and I are making our approach on the Banished base beneath the carrier.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M06_PIP_SPAJ_05">Good to hear. Once the carrier&apos;s shield is down we&apos;ll only have a small window of time to board it via the grav-lift. I need your team on standby in case we run into any problems.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M06_TEX_INTELREPORT">Use your snipers to spot targets for your long range Kodiak artillery.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M06_TEX_SUMMARY_01">Infiltrate a Banished compound to board the carrier &apos;Enduring Conviction&apos;.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M07_PIP_AND_01">When a new ring is launched, the Ark activates access points so sentinels can finalise preparations. Atriox must be using these points to send his troops up.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M07_PIP_AND_FOUNDRY_01">A</str>
    <str id="MBS_M07_PIP_AND_FOUNDRY_02">T</str>
    <str id="MBS_M07_PIP_CUT_01">About thirty minutes ago we lost contact with several of our landing parties on the new Halo ring. Shortly thereafter, we received confirmation of a large Banished invasion.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M07_PIP_CUT_02">We have to stop the flow of Banished reinforcements getting to this access point before our forces on the Halo are overwhelmed.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M07_PIP_CUT_SPLIT_02">Once that&apos;s done, we can send our forces up to help clean the Banished off the ring.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M07_TEX_INTELREPORT">Blisterback artillery units have been spotted in the area. Use Cyclops units to take them out.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M07_TEX_SUMMARY_01">Push back the Banished invasion to reach the Halo&apos;s Control Room</str>
    <str id="MBS_M08_PIP_AND_01">We&apos;ve got to get to that Control Room so I can deactivate the Halo&apos;s firing systems and plant our signal beacon.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M08_PIP_AND_SPLIT_01">If I can&apos;t do that, we won&apos;t be sending an SOS back home - we&apos;ll be sending a very large - and very live - bomb.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M08_PIP_CUT_01">We&apos;ve stopped the tide of Banished reinforcements arriving on the ring, but Atriox has already managed to gain a foothold near Alpha Base.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M08_PIP_CUT_02">If Atriox gets control of this Halo, he&apos;ll be holding a gun to the head of all life across hundreds of light years. We have to clear the Banished off this ring.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M08_PIP_CUT_SPLIT_02">It&apos;s up to you, Red Team.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M08_PIP_ISA_01">Our troops have been trying to reach the ring&apos;s Control Room, but the routes are cut off by a Banished shield.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M08_TEX_INTELREPORT">The Halo will have deployed Forerunner defenses to protect itself.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M08_TEX_SUMMARY_01">Get Professor Anders to the Control Room and clear the Halo of all Banished forces</str>
    <str id="MBS_M09_PIP_AND_01">I&apos;m in, and I think I&apos;ve found the Halo&apos;s weapon systems. Once I&apos;ve deactivated them, then I&apos;ll place the comms beacon.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M09_PIP_CUT_01">Professor, what&apos;s the update at the Control Room?</str>
    <str id="MBS_M09_PIP_CUT_02">Keep us updated. Jerome, Atriox will be sending everything to stop us.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M09_PIP_CUT_03">The clock&apos;s ticking and we don&apos;t have time to drop a base and build it up. You&apos;re going to have to rely on turret defenses, so keep them up and running.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M09_PIP_CUT_04">Okay everyone, let&apos;s get to work. Good luck.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M09_PIP_CUT_SPLIT_02">You need to hold the line and protect the Professor in the Control Room until she&apos;s finished her work.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M09_PIP_ISA_01">And I&apos;ve got all the ship&apos;s weapons systems primed and ready, so we&apos;ll help as much as we can from up here.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M09_PIP_ISA_FRESHTROOPS_01">Fresh troops will be sent in directly from the Spirit of Fire as soon as they&apos;re ready to deploy.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M09_PIP_SPAJ_01">Won&apos;t let you down, sir.</str>
    <str id="MBS_M09_TEX_INTELREPORT">M</str>
    <str id="MBS_M09_TEX_SUMMARY_01">Hold out against the Banished long enough for Anders to complete her mission.</str>
</string_table>