<?xml version="1.0" encoding="us-ascii"?>
<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<str id="TUTADV_OBJ_COMBAT">Advanced combat</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_OBJ_COMBAT_DESC">Learn the advanced combat techniques</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_OBJ_SELECTION">Advanced selection</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_OBJ_SELECTION_DESC">Learn the advanced selection techniques</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_AIRUNITS_01">Careful, commander. We've detected enemy air units nearby.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_AIRUNITS_02">Every type of unit has a counter-unit.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_AIRUNITS_03">Marines are an effective counter to air units, so I'm sending in Marine reinforcements now.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_AIRUNITS_04">Use your Marines to destroy those air units, commander!</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_ALLUNITS_01">Now select all your units from across the battlefield.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_ALLUNITS_02">Selecting all your units can be useful for quickly moving all your units at once. Move all your units to the next waypoint marker.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_ALLUNITS_03">There are enemies above you on the high ground. Units on higher ground will have an offensive advantage , so get up there and deal with them quickly!</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_ALLUNITS_04">You're under attack from the enemies above!</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_ALLUNITS_05">Move your units up there to take them out.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_ALLUNITS_06">Now that you're on higher ground, you have good visibility over the ground below.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_ALLUNITS_07">Make sure all your units are on the higher ground before moving on.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_ALLUNITS_08">Units on higher ground have extended sight and firing ranges. Engaging an enemy from higher ground can let you shoot them before they can shoot you back.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_CONTROLGROUPS_01">Control Groups are another way of managing large numbers of troops, and effective unit control is essential to winning battles.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_CONTROLGROUPS_02">Now let's assign some units to a Control Group using what you've already learned. Select all local units.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_CONTROLGROUPS_03">Now assign those units to a Control Group.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_CONTROLGROUPS_04">Excellent. Now you can use the D-Pad to quickly select those units assigned to that Control Group. Let's try that now.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_CONTROLGROUPS_05">Now use the D-Pad to select the units assigned to that Control Group again.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_CONTROLGROUPS_06">Good. You can have one Control Group assigned to each of the directions on the D-Pad.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_CONTROLGROUPS_07">Good. You can have one Control Group assigned to each of the Control Group commands.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_CONTROLGROUPS_08">Now move all your units to the next waypoint marker.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_CONTROLGROUPS_PCVERSION_04">Excellent. Now you can use the Control Group commands to quickly select those units assigned to that Control Group. Let's try that now.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_CONTROLGROUPS_PCVERSION_05">Now use the Control Group command to select the units assigned to that Control Group again.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_CONTROLGROUPS_PCVERSION_06">Good. You can have up to ten Control Groups assigned to each of the Control Group commands.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_CONTROLPANEL_01">Now keep moving to the next objective marker.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_CONTROLPANEL_02">You've reached a bridge. Move a unit to the control panel to activate the bridge.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_CONTROLPANEL_03">Cross the bridge to reach the next objective marker.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_DPAD_01">Your D-Pad can be used to move quickly around the battlefield.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_DPAD_02">Press left on the D-Pad to jump to your base. If you have multiple bases, multiple presses to the left on your D-Pad will cycle through all your bases.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_DPAD_03">Next, press down on the D-Pad to jump to your units. If you have multiple units across the map, repeatedly pressing down will jump between clusters of units.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_DPAD_04">Now hold up on the D-Pad to set a rally point. This is where new units move to when they are built from your bases.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_DPAD_05">You have a battlefield alert! Press right on the D-Pad to jump to the alert and take out the enemy!</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_DPAD_B04">By default, all units produced at a base are deployed in front of that base. To order all new units to report to a specific location on the battlefield, set a global rally point. Let's set a rally point now.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_DPAD_PCVERSION_01">You can use shortcut commands to move quickly around the battlefield.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_DPAD_PCVERSION_02">Press the 'base' shortcut command to jump to your base. If you have multiple bases, multiple presses will cycle through all your bases.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_DPAD_PCVERSION_03">Next, press the 'unit' shortcut command to jump to your units. If you have multiple units across the map, repeatedly pressing the shortcut command will jump between clusters of units.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_DPAD_PCVERSION_04">Now press the 'rally point' shortcut command to set a rally point. This is where new units move to when they are built from your bases.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_DPAD_PCVERSION_05">You have a battlefield alert! Use the 'battlefield alert' shortcut command to jump to the alert and take out the enemy!</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_ENEMYBASE_01">The enemy base has been located. Use the tactics we've covered to destroy all enemy forces.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_FINAL_01">That's the last of the enemy units, commander, well done!</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_FINAL_02">Choosing the right unit to counter enemy units is key to your success on the battlefield.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_FINAL_03">Congratulations, Commander! You have completed advanced training! Good luck out there.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_GROUPUNITS_01">Now let's move on to advanced unit selection techniques. Here come some reinforcements now.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_GROUPUNITS_02">Move your view over all the units and select them all at once.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_GROUPUNITS_03">Good. Your selected units are always shown grouped by type at the bottom of the screen.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_GROUPUNITS_04">Cycle through your selected unit types now.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_GROUPUNITS_05">Notice how the selection around each unit changes as you cycle through.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_GROUPUNITS_06">Now let's review other ways to quickly select units of the same type.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_GROUPUNITS_07">Well done. Each unit type has its own strengths and weaknesses, and knowing how to use those strengths and exploit those weaknesses is the key to victory.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_GROUPUNITS_SPLIT_05">Cycling is a good way to quickly select individual types of units from a larger group.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_INFANTRYUNITS_01">Excellent, but now the enemy is sending in Marines to counter your air units.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_INFANTRYUNITS_02">Your air units won't last long against their Marines, so friendly Scorpion tanks are inbound to help deal with them.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_OPTIONALOBJECTIVE_01">You have been receiving these instructions as Primary Objectives, which must be completed to progress.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_OPTIONALOBJECTIVE_02">You don't have to complete Optional Objectives to progress, but they will help you complete the mission, earn you additional points, and gain extra experience.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_OPTIONALOBJECTIVE_SPLIT_01">You will also receive Optional Objectives which will highlight helpful but non-critical mission opportunities.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_SPECIALABILITY_01">Use your Marines' grenades to quickly clear out those enemies.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_SPECIALABILITY_02">Impressive, commander. Units' special abilities can vary, but they always improve your unit's effectiveness in battle.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_SPECIALABILITY_03">Special abilities take a while to recharge before they can be used again, so timing is important. Use them wisely.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_TANKUNITS_01">Good work, commander, but we're not done yet.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_TANKUNITS_02">The enemy is planning a counter-attack with Scorpion tanks, which will easily destroy your Marines.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_TANKUNITS_03">Vehicles are vulnerable to air units, so I'm sending you some Hornets to counter the enemy tanks.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_UPGRADE_01">First, we're going to cover how to upgrade your units. Upgrading units boosts their combat effectiveness.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_UPGRADE_02">Let's upgrade your Marines with the Grenade Throw special abillity.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_UPGRADE_03">Use your base to upgrade your Marines now.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_UPGRADE_04">Good. Your upgrade will be ready in a few seconds.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_UPGRADE_05">Your Marines have now been upgraded with a special ability to throw grenades.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_UPGRADE_NEW_01">First, we're going to cover how to increase your base's tech level.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_UPGRADE_NEW_02">Upgrade your Firebase to a Combat Station now.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_UPGRADE_NEW_03">Upgrading your base has unlocked some unit upgrades. Upgrading units boosts their combat effectiveness.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_UPGRADE_NEW_B01">Higher base tech levels unlock new building slots and the production of more advanced units and unit upgrades.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_UPGRADEBASE_01">Now let's upgrade your base so you can start building more advanced units.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_UPGRADEBASE_02">Select your current base now.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_UPGRADEBASE_03">You can also select your other buildings to see what upgrades are available.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_CUT_WELCOME_01">Welcome to the advanced tutorial training, Commander. Advanced training will give you the upper hand on the battlefield.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_PIP_TEX_UPGRADE_08">Close the radial menu with @TutCancel@</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_AIRUNITS_01">Marines are an effective counter to air units.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_ALLUNITS_01">Double tap @TutLClUnits@ to select all units.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_ALLUNITS_01_PC">Press @TutAllUnits@ to select all units.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_ALLUNITS_02">Move all your units the higher ground.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_ALLUNITS_NEW_01">Move all your units to the objective marker with @TutAttack@.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_CONTROLGROUPS_01">Press @TutLClUnits@ to select all local units.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_CONTROLGROUPS_02">Hold down @TutSelUnits@ to change your D-Pad to Control Group mode.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_CONTROLGROUPS_03">Next, hold down any direction on the D-Pad to assign your selected units to a Control Group.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_CONTROLGROUPS_03_PC">Press @PCCGCreate@ + @PCCGSelect@ to assign your selected units to a Control Group.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_CONTROLGROUPS_04">Clear your selection with @TutCancel@.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_CONTROLGROUPS_05">Hold down @TutSelUnits@ to change your D-Pad to Control Group mode.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_CONTROLGROUPS_06">With @TutSelUnits@ still held, tap the D-Pad to select the Control Group you created.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_CONTROLGROUPS_06_PC">Press @PCCGSelect@ to select the Control Group you created.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_CONTROLGROUPS_07">The bottom left of the screen shows your Control Groups when @Left_Bumper@ is held.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_CONTROLPANEL_01">Move a unit to the control panel and press @TutSelect@ over the control panel.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_CONTROLPANEL_02">Use @TutMoveCam@ to select the lightbridge control and press @TutSelect@ to confirm and activate the lightbridge.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_CONTROLPANEL_02_PC">Select the lightbridge control and press @TutSelect@ to confirm and activate the lightbridge.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_DPAD_01">Press @TutCyclBses@ to jump to your base.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_DPAD_02">Press @TutCyclSquds@ to jump to your units.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_DPAD_03">Press and Hold @TutRlyPnt@ to set a rally point.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_DPAD_04">Press @TutCyclAlrts@ to jump to the alert.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_GROUPUNITS_01">Press and hold @TutSelect@ and use @TutMoveCam@ to move the reticle over all the units to select them.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_GROUPUNITS_02">When the expanded selection circle has covered all units, release the @TutSelect@ to confirm the selection.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_GROUPUNITS_03">Use @TutSelUnits@ to cycle through your selected unit types.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_GROUPUNITS_03_PC">Use @MouseScroll@ to cycle through your selected unit types.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_GROUPUNITS_04">Double tap @TutSelect@ on one of your units to select all units of that type on-screen.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_HINT_BUILD">You can build more units at your base to support your attack.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_INFANTRYUNITS_01">Vehicle units are an effective counter to most infantry units.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_MOVEMENTSPEED">Groups of different unit types move at the speed of the slowest type.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_01">Learn upgrades</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_01_DESC">Upgrade your base and marines, then use the Grenade Throw special ability.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_02">Learn advanced selection</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_02_DESC">Learn advanced techniques for selecting your units and buildings.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_03">Use control groups</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_03_DESC">Create a control group of your units and use it to select them.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_04">Select all units</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_04_DESC">Use the All Units command to select all your units at once.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_05">Get to the top of the cliff</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_05_DESC">Move your units to the top of the cliff and clear out any enemies along the way.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_06">Move over the bridge</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_06_DESC">Use the terminal to open the bridge and move your units over it.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_07">Destroy the enemy Hornets</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_07_DESC">Your marines are effective against flying units. Use them to destroy the enemy Hornets.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_08">Destroy the enemy Scorpions</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_08_DESC">Flying units are effective against vehicles. Use your Hornets to destroy the enemy Scorpions.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_09">Destroy the enemy Marines</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_09_DESC">Vehicles are effective against infantry units. Use your Scorpions to destroy the enemy Marines.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_10">Destroy the enemy Base</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OBJ_NEW_10_DESC">Use all the skills you have learned to take out the enemy base.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_OPTIONALOBJECTIVE_01">Press @TutObjectives@ to review your Optional Objectives.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_SPECIALABILITY_01">Some units have special abilities. Press @special_power@ to use a unit's special ability.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_SPECIALABILITY_02">Move the reticle over the enemy units and press @special_power@ to use your Marines' Grenade Throw special ability.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_TANKUNITS_01">Air units are an effective counter to most vehicle units.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_UPGRADE_01">Select your base with @TutSelect@.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_UPGRADE_02">Use @TutRadMove@ to select the Grenade Throw special ability and confirm the selection with @TutSelect@.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_UPGRADE_03">It looks like you haven't reached a high enough tech level to upgrade your Marines.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_UPGRADE_04">To increase your tech level, you'll need to build a Generator first.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_UPGRADE_05">As your tech level increases, you will have greater access to advanced units, buildings and upgrades.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_UPGRADE_06">Now you've finished building a Generator, notice that your tech level has increased.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_UPGRADE_07">You now have a high enough tech level to research the Grenade Throw.</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_UPGRADE_08">Now close the radial menu with @TutCancel@</str>
	<str id="TUTADV_TEX_UPGRADE_NEW_01">Use @TutRadMove@ to select the Combat Station upgrade and confirm the selection with @TutSelect@.</str>
</string_table>