<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_VETERANCY_01">Veterancy is gained through combat. A unit&apos;s veterancy level is indicated by a veterancy number over the unit.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_SUPPLYPAD_02">Now use @TutRadMove@ to choose the Supply Pad build option and confirm your selection with @TutSelect@.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_SUPPLYPAD_01">Select the empty build socket with @TutSelect@ to open the radial menu.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_SELECTUNITS_REMINDER">Select all your units by pressing @TutLClUnits@</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_SELECTUNITS_02">Move the reticle over your marines and press @TutSelect@ to select them again.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_SELECTUNITS_01">Move the reticle over a unit and press @TutSelect@ to select them.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_RESOURCES_04">Send your Marines to collect 30 Power.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_RESOURCES_03">Send your Marines to pick up 30 Supply.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_RESOURCES_02">Your power counter shows the amount of power you have.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_RESOURCES_01">Your supply counter shows the amount of supplies you have.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_11_DESC">Use your Hellbringers and Marines to kill the enemy attackers.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_11">Defeat the final attack</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_10_DESC">Use your Barracks to build a squad of Hellbringers.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_10">Build Hellbringers</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_09_DESC">Upgrade your base by adding 3 buildings.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_09">Build three buildings</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_07_DESC">Collect enough resources to build a new Base.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_07">Build a Base</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_06_DESC">Move your Marines into a Garrison and survive the next enemy attack.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_06">Use a Garrison</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_05_DESC">Use a Leader Power to heal your Marines.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_05">Heal your Marines</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_04_DESC">Attack and kill the enemy squad of Marines.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_04">Kill the enemy Marines</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_03_DESC">Select and move both squads of Marines to the top of the ramp.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_03">Move two squads</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_02_DESC">Select and move your squad of Marines to the end of the corridor.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_02">Move your Marines</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_01_DESC">Learn how to move the camera around the battlefield.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_OBJ_NEW_01">Learn camera controls</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_MOVEUNITS_02">Keep moving to the next waypoints by moving the reticle and pressing @TutAttack@.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_MOVEUNITS_01">Move your reticle over the waypoint marker and press @TutAttack@ to order your unit to move there.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_MARINES_03">Queuing unit build commands by selecting the option multiple times saves you time on the battlefield.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_MARINES_02">Now use @TutRadMove@ to select Marines and confirm the selection with @TutSelect@.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_MARINES_01">Select the Base with @TutSelect@ to open up its radial menu.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_LOCALUNITS_03_PC">Hold @TutSelect@ and move @MouseMove@ to drag the reticle between the two markers, known as &apos;paint select&apos;</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_LOCALUNITS_03">Hold @TutSelect@ and move @TutMoveCam@ to drag the reticle between the two markers, known as &apos;paint select&apos;</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_LOCALUNITS_02">Move all units to the next waypoint marker.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_LOCALUNITS_01">Press @TutLClUnits@ to select all units in view, known as all &apos;local units&apos;.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_LEADERPOWER_ALT_04">Press @TutSelect@ to heal your marines.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_LEADERPOWER_ALT_03">Select the Restoration Drones Leader Power by using the @TutRadMove@ and confirm your selection using @TutSelect@.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_LEADERPOWER_ALT_02">Open the Leader Powers menu with @TutPwrRadial@</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_LEADERPOWER_ALT_01">Move the reticle to your marines.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_LEADERPOWER_05">Press @TutCancel@ to close the Leader Tree</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_LEADERPOWER_04">Move the reticle over your units and press @TutSelect@ to heal them.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_LEADERPOWER_03">Select Restoration Drones by using @TutRadMove@ and confirm your selection using @Radial_select@.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_LEADERPOWER_02">Purchase the Restoration Drones Leader Power by using @TutRadMove@ and confirm your selection using @TutSelect@.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_LEADERPOWER_01">Press @TutObjectives@ to access the Leader Tree.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_GENERATOR_01">Press @TutSelect@ on an empty building socket and select a Generator from the radial.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_GARRISON_03">Use @TutRadMove@ to select the &apos;Leave garrison&apos; option from the radial.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_GARRISON_02">Select your garrisoned units with @TutSelect@</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_GARRISON_01">Press @TutGSon@ over a garrison to move selected units inside. Garrisoned units take less damage from attacks.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_CLEARSELECTION_01">Clear your currently selected units by pressing @TutCancel@.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_CAMERA_04_PC">Zoom the camera by holding @TutAlt@ and using @MouseScroll@.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_CAMERA_04">Zoom the camera by moving @TutZoom@ backward and forward.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_CAMERA_03_PC">Rotate the camera by holding @TutAlt@ and moving @MouseMove@ left and right.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_CAMERA_03">Rotate the camera by moving @TutRotCam@ left and right.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_CAMERA_02_PC">Use @CameraUp@ @CameraDown@ @CameraLeft@ @CameraRight@ and hold @TutCamSpeed@ to speed up the camera movement.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_CAMERA_02">Move @TutMoveCam@ and hold @TutCamSpeed@ to speed up the camera movement.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_CAMERA_01_PC">Move your view of the map using the @CameraUp@ @CameraDown@ @CameraLeft@ @CameraRight@</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_CAMERA_01">Move your view of the map using the @TutMoveCam@ to move the reticle. The reticle shows the focus of your camera.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_BUILDBASE_06">Use @TutRadMove@ to select the Firebase build option from the radial menu, then confirm selection with @TutSelect@.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_BUILDBASE_05">Move to the base plot and select it with @TutSelect@</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_BUILDBASE_04">Close the radial with @TutCancel@.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_BUILDBASE_03">Unfortunately you don&apos;t have enough resources to build a Firebase yet. We&apos;re going to have to collect some first.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_BUILDBASE_02">Select the base plot with @TutSelect@ to open the radial.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_BUILDBASE_01">Move your units to the base plot by the waypoint marker.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_BARRACKS_03">Now use @TutRadMove@ to select Hellbringers and confirm the selection with @TutSelect@.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_BARRACKS_02">Select the Barracks with @TutSelect@ to open up its radial menu.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_BARRACKS_01">Press @TutSelect@ on an empty building socket and select a Barracks from the radial.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_TEX_ATTACK_01">Attack enemy units by moving the reticle over them and pressing @TutAttack@.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_WELCOME_01">Good to see you out of cryo, commander. Let&apos;s run a quick simulation to refresh your basic training and get you ready for the battle ahead.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_VETERANCY_02">Veteran units are tougher and more effective in combat.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_VETERANCY_01">Impressive. Your units have become veterans through combat.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_SUPPLYPAD_02">Excellent. Notice that you now have a continuous stream of supplies from the Supply Pad.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_SUPPLYPAD_01">You&apos;ll need a Supply Pad to boost your supply income. Build one on the empty build socket.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_SELECTUNITS_01">Now select your squad of Marines.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_RESOURCES_NEW_02">You&apos;ll need resources to build your first Firebase. Let&apos;s go collect those resources now.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_RESOURCES_NEW_01">You&apos;ll need resources to build your first Firebase. Let&apos;s go collect those resources now.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_RESOURCES_04">When building structures and units, you&apos;ll use two types of resources: power and supply.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_RESOURCES_03">Next, gather some power by collecting these power resources.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_RESOURCES_02">Good. Notice that your supply increased after gathering the supply caches.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_RESOURCES_01">Always keep an eye out for resources on the battlefield. There are some supply caches nearby, move your marines over to them to gather the supplies inside.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_MOVEUNITS_03">The amount of fog of war lifted depends on a unit&apos;s line of sight and firing range.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_MOVEUNITS_02">As your units move, the dark areas ahead of them are revealed. The dark areas are the fog of war.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_MOVEUNITS_01">Good. Units must be selected before you can issue them orders. Let&apos;s issue a move order now.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_MARINES_02">Marines are a good all-purpose infantry unit and can always be recruited from any base or minibase. Note that they only require supply resources to produce.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_MARINES_01">Now recruit a squad of Marines from your Firebase&apos;s central structure.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_LOCALUNITS_01">Now move all the units under your command to the next location.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_LEADERPOWERMEDDRONES_02">Excellent. You&apos;ve unlocked Med-Drones. Now let&apos;s use them to heal your units.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_LEADERPOWERMEDDRONES_01">Good. Now select the &apos;Med-Drones&apos; Leader Power.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_LEADERPOWER_06">Leader Powers can make the difference between victory and defeat, so use them wisely.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_LEADERPOWER_05">Now you&apos;ve readied your Leader Power, use it to heal your units.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_LEADERPOWER_04">Excellent. You&apos;ve unlocked Restoration Drones. Now let&apos;s use them to heal your units.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_LEADERPOWER_03">Good. Now select the &apos;Restoration Drones&apos; Leader Power.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_LEADERPOWER_02">You can spend a Leader Point to unlock a Leader Power. Let&apos;s choose a power that will heal your units.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_LEADERPOWER_01">Your units have taken some damage during combat, but you have earned a Leader Point.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_GENERATOR_02">Now you have a steady income of the two resources, power and supply.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_GENERATOR_01">Your other resource is power. Build a Generator so you can produce power.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_GARRISON_03">Now the enemies have been dealt with, order your units out of the garrison.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_GARRISON_02">Good. Garrisoned units are better protected from enemy attacks.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_GARRISON_01">More enemies are coming, move your Marines into cover in that garrison.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_FINALATTACK_03">Good job, that&apos;s the last of them.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_FINALATTACK_02">Reinforcements are on the way to help you protect your base.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_FINALATTACK_01">The enemy are making a final attack, commander! Use your units to defeat them!</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_CLEARSELECTION_01">Here&apos;s another squad of Marines. Let&apos;s take command of them as well.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_CAMERA_04">Good. Now that your view is focused on your Marines, have a look around.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_CAMERA_03">First, move your view to your Marines.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_CAMERA_02">It&apos;s important to be aware of what&apos;s happening around you at all times.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_BUILDBASE_NEW_01">You&apos;ve got enough resources to build that base. Select the base plot and call it in.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_BUILDBASE_06">Your Firebase is now ready.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_BUILDBASE_05">Good. The Firebase will take some time to build, so it&apos;s a good time to collect more supplies while you wait.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_BUILDBASE_04">Now call in a Firebase from the Spirit of Fire.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_BUILDBASE_03">Now you have some resources, it&apos;s time to build a base so you can recruit more units. Move your units back to the base plot and select it.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_BUILDBASE_02">This is a base plot, and it&apos;s where we&apos;re going to establish our base. Let&apos;s call in a base drop now.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_BUILDBASE_01">Next, you&apos;ll need to build more units to grow your army. Move all your units to the marked base plot.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_BASICTUTORIALCOMPLETE_01">You&apos;ve completed basic training. You can now complete the advanced training or head straight down to the war. Good luck out there, Commander.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_BARRACKS_04">Good work. Building units is crucial to success on the battlefield.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_BARRACKS_03">Hellbringers are powerful anti-infantry units.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_BARRACKS_02">Now build a squad of Hellbringers from the barracks. Like all advanced units, they require both supplies and power to build.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_BARRACKS_01">Next, build a Barracks so you can recruit advanced infantry units.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_ATTACK_03">Good work, commander.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_ATTACK_02">Your units have also been trained to automatically attack enemies when they are within firing range.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_PIP_CUT_ATTACK_01">There are enemy Marines nearby. Order your squad to attack them.</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_OBJ_RESOURCES_DESC">Learn the essential information about resources</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_OBJ_RESOURCES">Resource essentials</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_OBJ_BASIC_SELECTION_DESC">Learn the basics of selecting units</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_OBJ_BASIC_SELECTION">Basic selection</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_OBJ_BASIC_COMBAT_DESC">Learn the basics of ordering your units in combat</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_OBJ_BASIC_COMBAT">Basic combat</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_OBJ_BASE_BUILDING_DESC">Learn how to build and extend your base</str>
    <str id="TUTBAS_OBJ_BASE_BUILDING">Learn base building</str>
</string_table>