<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ01_01">It’s time to take command.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ01_02">In Blitz, you win by scoring more points than your opponent. Do this by capturing control zones.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ01_04">Your starting army is waiting for orders.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ01_05">Reinforce them before moving out.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ01_06">Play the Marines card from your card hand.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ01_07">Nice work.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ01_08">Your remaining cards are too expensive to play.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ01_09">Cycle out the Scorpion to draw a new card.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ01_10">Nice. The Hellbringers card is a cheap but effective option. Play it now.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ01_11">You've got yourself an army!</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ02_01">Now your Energy is low.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ02_02">You need to wait for your Energy to replenish before playing more cards.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ02_03">Keep an eye out for Energy Cores. They drop periodically into the map, and will permanently increase your Energy income.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ02_04">There's one now.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ02_05">The enemy is trying to take that Energy Core! Get to it before they do!</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ02_06">Collect all of the Energy from that Core. Each cell provides a boost to your Energy income.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ02_07">Your Energy income has increased nicely.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ03_01">You have enough Energy to play another card.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ03_02">Play the Cyclops.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ03_03">This unit looks hurt. That's because it wasn't played at your base.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ03_04">Its health and attack damage are reduced. This effect is called Deployment Fatigue.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ03_05">Fatigue ends after a few seconds. If the unit avoids being hit while Fatigued, its health is restored.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ04_01">Your army is ready. It's time to win this game.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ04_02">The enemy has captured the first control zone!</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ04_03">Get there and take it away from them.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ05_01">You are now scoring points. Score 200 points to win a Blitz match.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ05_02">You must leave a unit at this zone to keep control of it.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ05_03">Lets reinforce. Call in a Warthog.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ06_01">This deck has some extra firepower – unit cards with Keywords.  The Jackrabbit card you just drew has the Blast keyword.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ06_02">If the Jackrabbit dies it will explode, causing massive damage. Keywords like this can give you an edge in battle.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ06_03">Play the Wild Jackrabbit now.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ07_01">The enemy has taken another zone!</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ07_02">Scoring has stopped. You can only score points if you control more zones than your opponent.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ07_03">They’ve taken the last zone!</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ07_04">Now the enemy is scoring!</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ07_05">Time to turn this fight around.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ08_01">Capture one of the enemy-held zones and win the game.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ08_02">Your card hand is unlocked. Play any cards you need. Good luck.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ08_03">Careful, that enemy Marauder has the Rally keyword. He's buffing his allies with bonus damage.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ08_04">Send your Wild Jackrabbit in there and blow him up.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ08_05">You've lost control of the central zone. Send a unit there to take it back</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ09_01">Good work. You’ve captured two zones!</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ09_02">In a normal Blitz match you’ll need to score 200 points to win.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ09_03">We’ll end this training round to let you jump into a real game.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ09_04">Try playing with my deck in a versus match or a Blitz Firefight against the A.I.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ09_05">Your card collection is waiting for you in the Blitz menus if you want to inspect your armies.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ09_06">I’ll see you on the battlefield, Commander.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ10_02">It takes 200 points to win a Blitz match.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ10_03">The battlefield is yours, Commander.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ10_04">Congratulations!</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_PIP_CUT_OBJ10_05">I hope you enjoyed this training match. Your card collection is available in the Blitz menus.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ01_CYCLECARD_0OF1">Cycle Scorpion Card: 0/1&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cycling a card sends it to the bottom of your deck - for a small cost – and draws a new card from the top.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ01_CYCLECARD_1OF1">Cycle Scorpion Card: 1/1&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cycling a card sends it to the bottom of your deck - for a small cost – and draws a new card from the top.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ01_PAYUNITCARDAGAIN_0OF1">Play Hellbringers Card: 0/1&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Open your card hand and select the highlighted card. Check the on-screen controls for help.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ01_PAYUNITCARDAGAIN_1OF1">Play Hellbringers Card: 1/1&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Open your card hand and select the highlighted card. Check the on-screen controls for help.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ01_PLAYUNITCARD_0OF2">Play Marines Card: 0/1&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Open your card hand and select the highlighted card. Check the on-screen controls for help.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ01_PLAYUNITCARD_1OF2">Play Marines Card: 1/1&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Open your card hand and select the highlighted card. Check the on-screen controls for help.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ01_TOOLTIP_00">Open your card hand and select the highlighted card. Check the on-screen controls for help.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ01_TOOLTIP_01">&lt;h1&gt;Cycling&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt;Cycling&lt;/b&gt; a card sends it to the bottom of your deck - for a small cost – and draws a new card from the top.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ02_COLLECTENERGY_0OF3">Collect Energy: 0/3&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Select your army and follow the waypoint to reach the Energy Core.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ02_COLLECTENERGY_1OF3">Collect Energy: 1/3&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walk over Energy Cells to pick them up.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ02_COLLECTENERGY_2OF3">Collect Energy: 2/3&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walk over Energy Cells to pick them up.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ02_COLLECTENERGY_3OF3">Collect Energy: 3/3&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walk over Energy Cells to pick them up.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ02_TOOLTIP_01">Your Energy supply is your own, but Energy income is shared across your team.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ02_TOOLTIP_02">Energy ticks up slowly over time. Collect Energy Cores to increase this tick rate.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ03_PLAYUNITCARD_0OF1">Play Cyclops Card: 0/1&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Open your card hand and select the highlighted card. Check the on-screen controls for help.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ03_PLAYUNITCARD_1OF1">Play Cyclops Card: 1/1&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Open your card hand and select the highlighted card. Check the on-screen controls for help.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ03_TOOLTIP_01">Fatigued units have half health and deal half damage for 8 seconds.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ04_CAPZONEB_0OF1">Capture Zone B: 0/1&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Select your army and move onto the highlighted Control Zone.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ04_CAPZONEB_1OF1">Capture Zone B: 1/1&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Select your army and move onto the highlighted Control Zone.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ04_TOOLTIP_01">Stand on Zone B and clear out the enemy to capture it for your team.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ05_PLAYUNITCARD_0OF1">Play Warthog Card: 0/1</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ05_PLAYUNITCARD_1OF1">Play Warthog Card: 1/1</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ06_PLAYKEYWORDCARD_0OF1">Play Wild Jackrabbit Card: 0/1</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ06_PLAYKEYWORDCARD_1OF1">Play Wild Jackrabbit Card: 1/1</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ08_CONTROLTWOZONES_0OF2">Control Two Zones: 0/2&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Play more cards to bolster your army.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ08_CONTROLTWOZONES_1OF2">Control Two Zones: 1/2&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Play more cards to bolster your army.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ08_CONTROLTWOZONES_2OF2">Control Two Zones: 2/2</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ08_TOOLTIP_01">Hold more zones than the enemy to win. At least one unit must stay on a zone to hold it.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ09_SCOREFULLY">Score 200 Points</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_TEX_OBJ09_TOOLTIP_02">Well done!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Play a match-made game or a Blitz Firefight to test your new skills in battle.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CARDPLAY_GEN_01">To play a card, open your hand…select the card you want…then deploy it onto the battlefield.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CARDPLAY_GEN_02">Commands display on-screen at all times to remind you how to do this.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CARDPLAY_PC_01">To play a card, you can use any combination of mouse and keyboard controls.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CARDPLAY_PC_02">Left-click on a card to select it, then click a valid location on the battlefield to play it there.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CARDPLAY_PC_03">Or, double-tap keyboard shortcuts to quickly select and play cards at your mouse’s current location.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CARDPLAY_XBOX_01">To play a card, open your card hand by pressing and holding the left trigger.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CARDPLAY_XBOX_02">Move the left stick in the direction of the card you want to select.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CARDPLAY_XBOX_03">Then press A to play that card.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP1_01">Welcome to Blitz, Commander. My name is Captain James Cutter.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP1_02">Blitz is a new way to play real time strategy. There’s no base building involved…just winner-take-all combat from the moment the game begins.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP1_03">In Blitz, you’ll create and protect your armies by playing cards. Every player has a deck of 12 unit and power cards that cycle repeatedly during a match.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP1_04">Bring your favorite army compositions to battle by building your own decks.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP1_0402">I’ve given you a starting library of cards, and there are more to collect when you play and complete challenges and campaign missions.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP1_05">Blitz matches are faster-paced than typical RTS multiplayer matches.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP1_06">The main objective is to score enough points within a time limit to win. Do this by capturing - and holding - more control zones than your opponent.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP1_07">Just like that!</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP2_01">Now, let’s get you started.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP2_02">Welcome to your base. Every match starts here and you can return when you need to heal and regroup.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP2_04">This is your card hand.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP3_01">Cards cost Energy to play. A card’s Energy cost is shown in its top-left corner.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP3_02">If you don’t have enough Energy to play a card, its cost is shown in red.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP3_03">Energy is Blitz’ only resource and it accumulates slowly over time. You can increase the speed at which you gain Energy during a match, but we’ll cover that later in the tutorial.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP3_04">If you don’t want to wait for the required Energy to play a card, Cycle it out and draw a new card.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP3_05">Cycling, like playing a card, moves that card to the bottom of your deck to be played again later.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP3_06">It costs a small amount of Energy to Cycle, but sometimes it’s worth the price.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP4_01">One last thing, Commander.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP4_02">There are two types of cards in Blitz: Units and Powers.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP4_03">Unit cards deploy persistent units on the battlefield. Play unit cards to reinforce your army and capture zones to win the game.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP4_04">Power cards unleash devastating Leader Powers to turn the tide of battle.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP4_05">In Blitz, every Leader has a unique set of powers, giving them more specialized roles.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP4_06">This deck contains the Archer Missiles power card, which calls in a missile strike from the Spirit of Fire.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP4_07">Power cards often require special targeting control. Let’s target the enemy troops with your Archer Missiles power.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP4_08">First, play the power card just like you would a unit card. This puts you in targeting mode.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP4_09">Archer Missiles require you to point in the direction you want to fire</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP5_01">They weren’t ready for that hit!</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CHAP5_02">You’ve got the basics of Blitz, Commander. Let’s head into battle and see what you can do.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CYCLE_GEN_01">To Cycle a card, open your hand, select the card you want, and choose Cycle instead of Play.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CYCLE_PC_01">To Cycle a card, select it from your hand then left-click the Cycle button below or press TAB on your keyboard.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_CYCLE_XBOX_01">To Cycle a card, open your hand, select the card you want, and press X.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_POWERS_GEN_01">Aim like so, and confirm.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_POWERS_GEN_02">You can always cancel a power while targeting to return the card to your hand.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_POWERS_PC_01">Aim the mouse like so, and left-click again to release the power.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_POWERS_PC_02">You can always press ESC or right-click the mouse to cancel a power and return it to your hand.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_POWERS_XBOX_01">Aim with the left-stick, and press A to confirm targeting.</str>
	<str id="TUTBLI_VIDEO_CUT_POWERS_XBOX_02">You can always cancel a power while targeting by pressing B to return the card to your hand.</str>
</string_table>