<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<str id="UIDLC5.CEASEFIRETIMER.TITLE">Please Don't Shoot Me!</str>
	<str id="UIDLC5.CODEX.UNITBAN.BODY.CANNONFODDER">Quantity is its own quality.

Cannon Fodder are an infantry unit which replaces standard Grunts in Yapyap THE DESTROYER’s army. They are unarmed, excitable, and poorly trained, but free: they cost no resources to deploy (just takes time and population cap). Though each unit is not exactly a powerhouse combatant, the Grunt Swarms are very useful for scouting, overwhelming enemy positions, and capturing points. In addition to standard infantry upgrades the Swarm can be trained in ancient Unggoy art of being Anklebiters, which gives them a weak close-combat capability and ability to dogpile the enemy and slow them down. Yapyap can also get them fired up with his Refer a Friend upgrade, which gives the unit a self-heal by packaging his best-selling novel on Grunt leadership together with some bandages.
 
An endless horde of overzealous Unggoy, ready to be marched into battle at a moment’s notice! As Yapyap has lost (he says “misplaced”) more Grunts in their revolution than were even carried to the Ark in the first place, it’s a bit of a mystery where these recruits are coming from. All that anyone knows for sure is that Yapyap THE DESTROYER argues with his Throne of Woe, gives it a few good kicks, and glassy-eyed reinforcements show up at camp the next day, ready to fight for the glory of Yapyap! In these dark days Grunts adrift are a gift, so other Grunts don’t ask any questions.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC5.CODEX.UNITBAN.BODY.GRUNTGOBLIN">Large and in charge.

Those nasty humans and Banished bullies won’t know what smacked them when the Grunt Goblin enters the battlefield! Piloted by Top Grunt jockeys, each Goblin is armed with unstoppable power wrists and heavy needle cannon right from the start, and can upgrade to the Shardstorm launcher for additional crystalline explosive fireworks. When the Goblins fancy feet get to stepping they can be upgraded to allow Grunt Hustle, increasing the movement speed for all nearby friendly units for a short period of time. While footloose and fancy free under the effect of the Grunt Hustle, the Goblin and nearby Grunt units are deadlier - as deadly as a Grunt can be, that is. And nest-mother said those dancing lessons would never pay off!
 
Also known as the Balaho battlesuit, Goblins are a patent-pending combination of amazing good looks and punchiness in a single value-packed package. But wait, there’s more! Act now and you can get not one. Not two. But THREE Goblins on the battlefield, for a true Grunty triple-threat. Forget fighting fair, for these suits have hearts of blamite and fists of justice that will deliver the Ark to its rightful owners: the Unggoy. And with the Ark in their grasping claws the rest of the galaxy will tremble! At least, that’s what the Throne of Woe keeps telling Yapyap THE DESTROYER. But wait, how did Yapyap get ahold of these incredible new machines and find time to modify them? Mind your own business is how.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC5.CODEX.UNITBAN.BODY.GRUNTRIDERS">Backseat driver.

The Grunt Rider is an infantry unit which replaces Suicide Grunts. The Grunts chosen to lord it over captured Brutes still lack much common sense, so going from carrying a backpack to being a backpack may not be a step up. Grunt Riders have a simple partnership with their Brutes: the Brutes punch things with their fists, while the Grunts tell them where to go and throw plasma grenades at enemies, allies, small animals, inanimate objects, and strange noises. The Brute’s attacks as-is, they can upgrade their punch force with Grunt-engineered plasma gloves by investing in Punch Harder, You!
 
Unlike methane and infusions, the Grunt and Brute pairing is not a perfect match. Among other quirks, some Brute Riders have a tendency to develop an obsession with biofuels, power management, and gladiatorial fights, much to the annoyance of everyone else in the rebellion. Other Brute Riders suffer “accidents” at the fists of the Brutes if they get too bossy. The rest simply hope to survive long enough to get promoted to Locust driver or methane hauler.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC5.CODEX.UNITBAN.BODY.HEAVYGRUNTS">They eat Spartans for breakfast!

Heavy Grunts are elite infantry who replace Jump Pack Brutes. Heavy Grunts are Yapyap THE DESTROYER’s enforcers , wearing heavy armor and armed with plasma pistols. When they need to break out the big guns the leader uses his Fuel Rod Cannon. This cannon can be upgraded with the Party’s Over special ability, which fires an EMP round that stuns vehicles and aircraft. And though war never changes, their unit size can. The My Plus One upgrade adds an additional squad member to the entourage.
 
Heavily augmented using strange machinery found on the Ark, Heavy Grunts are part Grunt, part machine, all awesome. Even without their new battle armor the Heavy Grunts are bad to the bone, and their chainmail undervests, mirrorshade lenses, and bad attitude prove it. They are led by the Shadow Master of Buwan, a red-beret-wearing Grunt spoken of in hushed whispers, who has taught his disciples ancient Balaho martial arts and a number of useful rope knot tricks.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC5.CODEX.UNITBAN.BODY.METHANEWAGON">Flamethrower guitar attachment is on order.

The Methane Wagon is a support vehicle unit which can be deployed by Yapyap THE DESTROYER. It’s slow, rickety, unstable, and the parking brake is a chunk of wood, but other than that it works as well as you would expect a Grunt contraption to. Whether by design or malfunction the Wagon emits a Methane Aura: clouds of infusion-enriched methane that enhance the aggression and damage of nearby Grunts, while confusing and reducing the damage of enemy units in the stinky cloud. The Wagon can also make special deliveries of enriched gas clouds by catapult-launching kegs with the Methane Delivery special ability. The aura and clouds can be upgraded with The Good Stuff by drawing upon illegal infusions stashed aboard by its party-hard operators. Unfortunately, these special brews are rather…volatile. The Methane Wagon will detonate violently when its structural integrity is compromised.
 
Yapyap THE DESTROYER dreams of owning a fleet of gold-plated warships to lord over the mean streets of Balaho. Well, Yapyap doesn’t yet have the gekz saved up to afford that, so he has to settle for a souped-up Shadows in the meantime. But with a few more successes on the Ark he can at least upgrade them with aftermarket iridium plating, hubcaps molded with the face of legendary Grunt heroes, and massive spoilers which ensure the Great Journey can be travelled in style. Although it has not yet reached its final form the Methane Wagon’s mix of combat and support abilities do make it the mullet of Grunt mechanized warfare: all business on the front lines, but party central in the rear.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC5.CODEX.UNITBAN.BODY.YAPYAP">Enough talk!

Once in a thousand generations comes a Grunt with the combined wisdom of Ang’napnap the Enlightened, the charisma of Awlphhum Who Became Tolerable, and a strategic acumen unmatched since Yayep the Archdeacon of Indolence. That time has not yet come, but Yapyap THE DESTROYER (he likes to shout that last part) does embody the mythic skills of one, maybe two, of these legendary heroes. He leads his brave (if not so bright) warriors from atop his Throne of Woe, having abandoned the Banished to locate the fabled Golden Methane Hydrate Mines of Sabator hidden somewhere on the Ark (and why would that Kig-Yar fortuneteller lie?) and secure a position as the Halo Wars 2 main character.
 
Yapyap THE DESTROYER is more of an idea Grunt, and has better things to do than come down to the battlefield personally (his managerial expertise would be wasted on the front lines). With style and panache he leads the Grunts to glorious victory or not-so-total defeat from his secret lair, throwing good Grunts after bad with Grunts from Above troop deployment and Shade Drop, while also playing the long game with defensive abilities such as the Surprise Party and Gruntdome deployable shield tower. And if Yapyap THE DESTROYER runs low on bodies, he can always put on a thrilling display of tactical cowardice with the Please Don’t Shoot Me ability, which puts a temporary armistice in place. While the rebellious Grunts don’t have much of a long-term strategy, they can avoid a loss simply by denying the enemy a win, with abilities such as Guilt Trip ensuring combat losses don’t embolden the enemy and the Get Back Out There advanced ability which returns injured Grunts back to the nearest HQ. When the combat music starts late in the Blitz match he can also send out invitations for the Methane Party, which drops gas-filled explosive barrels that damage the enemy and leave behind a lingering aura that makes Grunt units more effective.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC5.CODEX.UNITBAN.TITLE.CANNONFODDER">Cannon Fodder</str>
	<str id="UIDLC5.CODEX.UNITBAN.TITLE.GRUNTGOBLIN">Grunt Goblin</str>
	<str id="UIDLC5.CODEX.UNITBAN.TITLE.GRUNTRIDERS">Grunt Riders</str>
	<str id="UIDLC5.CODEX.UNITBAN.TITLE.HEAVYGRUNTS">Heavy Grunts</str>
	<str id="UIDLC5.CODEX.UNITBAN.TITLE.METHANEWAGON">Methane Wagon</str>
	<str id="UIDLC5.CODEX.UNITBAN.TITLE.YAPYAP">Yapyap THE DESTROYER</str>
	<str id="UIDLC5.LEADERSELECT.ROLE01.GRUNT">The Stinky Bunch</str>
	<str id="UIDLC5.LEADERSELECT.ROLE02.GRUNT">Blast Off</str>
	<str id="UIDLC5.LEADERSELECT.ROLE03.GRUNT">Driving Lessons</str>
	<str id="UIDLC5.LEADERSELECT.SHORTDESCR.GRUNT">At last, a Grunt rises to become a mighty leader. Or at least outnumber the enemy with an endless supply of cheap, expendable units!</str>
	<str id="UIDLC5.LEADERSELECT.SHORTDESCR.GRUNT.BLITZ">At last, a Grunt rises to become a mighty leader. Or at least outnumber the enemy with an endless supply of cheap, expendable units!</str>
	<str id="UIDLC5.LEADERSELECT.TITLE.GRUNT">Yapyap THE DESTROYER</str>
</string_table>