<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<str id="UIDLC41SER.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.BISON">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Heavy-duty cryotech support vehicle.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

The Bison is a hero vehicle available to Serina. In Serina’s employ it is a heavily-armored and shielded vehicle that synergizes well with other cryotech vehicles and abilities. It is fitted with a powerful &lt;b&gt;Coldsnap launcher&lt;/b&gt;, which fires experimental cryo shells that damage and chill enemies caught in its area-of-effect. The launcher can be upgraded, which increases its rate of fire, and chill effect. When the Bison &lt;b&gt;deploys&lt;/b&gt; it leeches ambient heat energy to augment its defensive systems, creating a &lt;b&gt;chill aura&lt;/b&gt; that affects nearby enemies. These systems can also be upgraded to further boost defenses and the area of the chill aura.

Bisons are versatile, durable vehicles that served in most groundside combat elements of the old Colonial Military Authority (CMA) in a number of roles, including armored personnel carrier and recovery vehicle. It remains in service with several UNSC Army units and local militias (such as the Sedran Colonial Guard). The variant designed by Serina uses the proven chassis as a testbed which holds a vacuum energy siphon, scientific instrumentation, and cryotech weaponry in one mobile package. As there are no Bisons aboard the Spirit of Fire at present, Isabel has looked at improving and repurposing the siphon with her own research data on Forerunner vacuum cells. However, the delicacy and intricacy of Serina's manufacturing template complicates this effort.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC41SER.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.CRYOLEADER">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;A mind of ice and fire.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Serina was activated on January 7, 2530, by Daedalia Technology, a Martian firm well-known for the seeding and development of artificial intelligences for military and corporate markets. Serina was their greatest work of that era, an omni-capable second-generation “Smart AI” that displayed both impressive intellectual capacity and remarkable computational efficiency. 

Her assignment to the UNSC &lt;i&gt;Spirit of Fire&lt;/i&gt; was fortuitous, despite a somewhat rocky period of acclimation to the ship’s unorthodox crew. Under the orders of Captain James Cutter, Serina administered the deployment of forces on Harvest’s surface, and successfully managed later campaigns on both Arcadia and the enigmatic Forerunner facility known as Shield 0459. 

Unfortunately, the life of a smart AI is limited and their constructed minds cannot be slowed or stopped. While the &lt;i&gt;Spirit of Fire&lt;/i&gt; drifted in the void after their victory over the Covenant at Shield 0459, Serina imagined, planned, and built for a future she would never see.

Serina had a remarkable aptitude for research and analysis, and her thoughts often turned to the work of Ellen Anders. In particular, the Professor’s early work on vacuum energy extraction—and its potentially useful side effects with regard to heat siphoning—fascinated Serina. 

Serina’s experimentation and engineering expertise gives her access to unique &lt;i&gt;cryotech&lt;/i&gt;-enhanced units and abilities that can slow targets, and render them inert. If the chill gets intense enough the target will freeze. &lt;i&gt;Frozen&lt;/i&gt; targets are immobile and unable to perform any actions, but don’t take damage unless they are shattered. Frozen units that take a significant amount of damage or are targeted by certain special abilities (such as &lt;b&gt;Seismic Charge&lt;/b&gt;) will &lt;i&gt;shatter&lt;/i&gt; and immediately take a massive amount of damage. Frozen units that are left alone will &lt;i&gt;thaw&lt;/i&gt; out after a short time, and do not suffer the damage spike.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC41SER.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.CRYOTROOPER">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Nerves of steel and hands of frost.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Cryo Troopers replace Hellbringers in Serina’s combat force. Fury runs hot and cold, as evidenced by Serina’s plans for a cadre of cryotech-equipped infantry. Cryo Troopers are armed with a portable &lt;b&gt;cryo spray&lt;/b&gt; which deals damage and inflicts a chilling effect on enemy units. This can shut down enemy vehicles and structures (including turrets), temporarily shutting them down even if they are not subsequently shattered. They can be upgraded with &lt;b&gt;advanced cryo&lt;/b&gt; systems, which increases the damage, range, and area covered by the chilling field of their spray.

Hellbringers are qualified to maintain, operate, and deploy a number of specialist weapon systems in the UNSC arsenal. This includes a range of incendiary, thermobaric, energetic, chemical, and biological weapons that most UNSC personnel are not even aware of. Serina reasoned their hazardous material qualifications and daredevil reputation made them well-suited for field testing experimental cryotech weaponry. Who better to strap on experimental and unstable power cells that tap strange energies than Marines who routinely wear volatile chemical packs into battle? She was probably right, if the spirited discussion about her cryotech weapon templates among the &lt;i&gt;Spirit of Fire&lt;/i&gt;’s Marines is any indication.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC41SER.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.ICEBARRIER">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Cryotech area denial system.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Serina learned much about warfare from monitoring the activities of Sergeant Forge and Captain Cutter, including the value of controlling the flow of battle by manipulating the terrain. Among her tools to accomplish this is the &lt;b&gt;Ice Barrier&lt;/b&gt; leader power, which creates a frozen block at a target location. The block of ice can be used to block chokepoints and disrupt enemy formations, and will &lt;i&gt;chill&lt;/i&gt; nearby enemies. The barrier can be shattered by enemy attacks.

Ice Barriers are weaponized versions of Ander’s early, failed, experiment with creating compact, zero-point energy condensers. Activation overloads the delicate barrier generators, but not before the area around them are drained of thermal energy.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC41SER.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.PEGASUS">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Death on frozen wings.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

The Frostraven is an aerial support vehicle unique to Serina. It is equipped with a vacuum energy extractor, nicknamed the &lt;b&gt;cryo ray&lt;/b&gt;, which chills and then freezes enemy units. The Frostraven can also unleash its special ability, a &lt;b&gt;shockwave missile&lt;/b&gt;, which shatters any frozen enemies in the target area. With the &lt;b&gt;Heavy Cryo Projector&lt;/b&gt; upgrade the Frostraven’s cryo ray becomes even more powerful, chilling and freezing the targeted unit faster.

The ZAV-48 Frostraven is a conjectural design that pairs research work Serina conducted on weaponized vacuum energy cryotech with a modified EV-44 airframe. As Isabel continues to review and integrate the knowledge left behind by Serina, it is possible that she will take this design from theory to prototype, but it is not without some irony that Anders has now focused her full attention on unraveling the secrets of the Forerunners rather than continuing this line of research and development.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC41SER.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.BISON">Bison</str>
	<str id="UIDLC41SER.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.CRYOLEADER">Serina</str>
	<str id="UIDLC41SER.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.CRYOTROOPER">Cryo Trooper</str>
	<str id="UIDLC41SER.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.ICEBARRIER">Ice Barrier</str>
	<str id="UIDLC41SER.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.PEGASUS">Frostraven</str>
	<str id="UIDLC41SER.LEADERSELECT.ROLE.CRYO.1">Hail Storm</str>
	<str id="UIDLC41SER.LEADERSELECT.ROLE.CRYO.2">Counter Chill</str>
	<str id="UIDLC41SER.LEADERSELECT.TITLE.CRYOLEADER">Serina</str>
</string_table>