<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.BODY.ARBITER">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Ripa ‘Moramee&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Driven to control and dominate, with a nearly insatiable bloodlust and ambition, Ripa 'Moramee was considered a radical choice as Arbiter. Ripa came to relish the nearly unchecked power and authority he wielded as an Arbiter, and his fearsome reputation was known by all—including a young Covenant warrior known as Atriox. Unbound by traditional notions of honor and loyalty, it is possible that Atriox could have convinced Ripa to join his cause, had Ripa survived events on Shield 0459. 

As a Banished warhost leader Ripa would inspire fear and awe in those in his dominion, reflected in the &lt;b&gt;Conduit of Rage&lt;/b&gt; passive ability. Conduit of Rage is triggered on the activation of leader powers, slightly healing the Arbiter’s nearby units and increasing their damage and speed for a short time. Continuing to use leader powers extends the duration. 

Ripa also had unrestricted access to experimental &lt;b&gt;Stasis&lt;/b&gt; weapons, which immobilize units in their area of effect for a short time, in his role as Arbiter. Units in stasis cannot move or deal damage, but also cannot be harmed. Ripa used these weapons to delay enemy units and—on the rare occasion he was feeling generous—shield allies from harm.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.BODY.ARBITERHERO">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Ripa ‘Moramee&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Though a talented strategist, Ripa prefers to make fights personal. On the battlefield Ripa wields his two relic blades with devastating skill, and can trigger his &lt;b&gt;Arbiter’s Rage&lt;/b&gt; ability to temporarily become a murderous avatar of war. 

While &lt;i&gt;Raging&lt;/i&gt; the Arbiter can leap to attack air units, moves faster and does significantly more damage. Upgrades include &lt;b&gt;Swift Fury&lt;/b&gt; which increases his movement speed and damage, &lt;b&gt;Conduit Incarnate&lt;/b&gt; which activates Conduit of Rage when the Arbiter kills an enemy while Raging, and &lt;b&gt;Arbiter’s Reprisal&lt;/b&gt; which reflects damage back towards his attackers.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.BODY.ELITEASSAULTTEAM">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Instruments of vengeance.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

The Enforcers are fast-moving, battle-hardened Sangheili armed with plasma rifles, plasma casters, and plasma grenades which can be deployed by the Arbiter in place of Jump Pack Brutes. They excel in hit-and-run attacks where they can rush in to attack with their plasma weapons and then disengage to allow their energy shields to regenerate. 

Enforcers can also use their special &lt;b&gt;Stasis Grenade&lt;/b&gt; ability to take targets they cannot effectively deal with out of action, and raid enemy bases to shut down production for a short time. They can be upgraded with an &lt;b&gt;Arbiter’s Champion&lt;/b&gt; to add an additional Sangheili warrior armed with a plasma caster.

Disgraced Sangheili have few options to recover their honor, even in death. Had Ripa joined with Atriox and thrown off the Prophets’ shackles he had powerful tools to exploit Sangheili warriors seeking redemption. Though Ripa could not lead through loyalty or charisma as a general, as the Arbiter he could bind Sangheili with iron-clad oaths that traded unquestioning service as his vassals for a return to the rolls of honor.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.BODY.ELITEGRUNTSQUAD">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Grunts commanded by an Elite&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;

The Grunts in this squad are armed with plasma pistols, led by an Elite with a plasma rifle. Upgrades allow the unit to cloak themselves for a while and add an Elite second-in-command.

A Grunt’s lot is not a happy one, but this squad has the advantage of being led by an Elite rather than a Brute, and whilst their average life-span is still short, it may be fractionally less unpleasant. The unit is relatively fast and effective against all enemy types and better at ranged combat than a Brute-led squad.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.BODY.PHANTOM">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Assault dropship.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

The Phantom is a fast, heavily armed aerial transport available to the Arbiter. It is armed with &lt;b&gt;heavy plasma cannons&lt;/b&gt; for engaging enemy air and ground targets, and can initially embark two infantry squads using its integral grav lift. These squads can fire from the Phantom, or be deployed at any time with the &lt;b&gt;Eject&lt;/b&gt; ability. The Phantom’s squad capacity can be increased to three squads with the &lt;b&gt;Gunboat Capacity&lt;/b&gt; upgrade.

The &lt;i&gt;Enduring Conviction&lt;/i&gt; carried a number of Phantom dropships to augment its existing stocks of Spirit troop carriers and Lich deployment platforms when it deployed to the Ark. The Banished Phantoms that would have been used by the Arbiter are heavily modified to serve as gunships and firing platforms, and are capable of long-range subluminal travel.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.TITLE.ARBITER">The Arbiter</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.TITLE.ARBITERHERO">The Arbiter</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.TITLE.ELITEASSAULTTEAM">Elite Enforcers</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.TITLE.ELITEGRUNTSQUAD">Grunts</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.TITLE.PHANTOM">Phantom</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.BATTLEAPC">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Armored personnel carrier.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Mastodons are heavy troop carriers available to Commander Jerome. Each is armed with an M41 &lt;b&gt;machine gun&lt;/b&gt; in a remotely operated weapon station, but the vehicle’s primary offensive utility comes from the three units of infantry it can carry. Each of these units can engage the enemy using their weapons through the APC’s &lt;b&gt;firing ports&lt;/b&gt;. The Mastodon can be upgraded to carry an additional infantry unit. If the Mastodon is destroyed the troops within will survive, but suffer heavy damage.

M650 Mastodons are widely used by the UNSC Army and colonial defense forces. Their large troop compartments enable them to carry heavy infantry (such as Spartans in powered assault armor) and their armor protects against most heavy weapons, but their size made them difficult to deploy and they lack the mobility of smaller (but far less protected) Warthog troop carriers. With troops in short supply on the Ark--and reinforcement unlikely--Jerome has investigated starting production of these vehicles to minimize infantry casualties.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.COMMANDERJEROME">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;UNSC Expeditionary Force Commander&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

With the authority granted to him as the ranking Navy and UEG official in a designated administrative region, Captain Cutter has conferred Jerome-092 the acting rank of Commander. The rank itself is a formality, but one insisted on by Isabel to better align the ship’s ad-hoc command structure with the letter of UNSC regulations. 

As force commander, Jerome-092 selects units in his army to &lt;b&gt;Inspire&lt;/b&gt; the troops around them, increasing their resilience and damage. Once inspired they can be further buffed with abilities that trigger temporary acts of &lt;b&gt;Spartan Morale&lt;/b&gt;-which further augments their armor, damage output, and speed. His &lt;b&gt;Victory Mine&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Enduring Salvo&lt;/b&gt; abilities also Inspire nearby troops when they are activated. 

As the battle reaches the peak of ferocity he can call in his trump cards: the Spartans of &lt;b&gt;Omega Team&lt;/b&gt; and the ability to conduct a &lt;b&gt;Field Promotion&lt;/b&gt;, which calls in an elite kill team of Spartans and upgrades all standard units to the first level of veterancy, respectively. When his troops are at low population, he can also activate &lt;b&gt;Time For Heroes&lt;/b&gt; to Inspire his army and allow them to gain veterancy at a greatly-increased rate.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.COMMANDMANTIS">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Theseus unleashed!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

The Command Mantis is a hero vehicle deployed by Commander Jerome. It is an upgraded variant of the Mantis all-environment bipedal walker armed with twin &lt;b&gt;high energy lasers&lt;/b&gt; and fitted with an advanced &lt;b&gt;energy shield&lt;/b&gt;. 

The Mantis can operate in an unmanned combat mode or be piloted by Commander Jerome. When piloted by Commander Jerome the mech’s long-range &lt;b&gt;missile launchers&lt;/b&gt; are also deployed, though these do have a minimum engagement distance.  Jerome-092 is free to disembark at any time with the &lt;b&gt;unload&lt;/b&gt; ability. 

The Command Mantis is tailored specifically for Jerome’s neural interface and &lt;b&gt;cannot be Hijacked&lt;/b&gt;. Upgrades to Commander Jerome also affect the Command Mantis, and he continues to Inspire while operating the mech.

Nicknamed &lt;i&gt;Theseus&lt;/i&gt; by Jerome-092, his personalized Command Mantis is a mobile command post and linebreaker unit that complements both his augmented physiology and leadership style. It incorporates one of the &lt;i&gt;Spirit of Fire&lt;/i&gt;’s command-and-control nexus relays, enhancing Jerome’s situational awareness of the battlefield and serving as a backup for the UNSC battlenet should the ship be crippled or destroyed.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.HEROJEROME">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;UNSC Expeditionary Force Commander&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Commander Jerome has proven himself to be an inspirational and highly capable leader, though some aspects of his Spartan conditioning conflict with his strategic instincts. Among these is a preference for direct action. On the battlefield, Commander Jerome can &lt;b&gt;Inspire&lt;/b&gt; nearby troops and take the fight to the enemy with a custom Hydra &lt;b&gt;missile launcher&lt;/b&gt;, shrugging off attacks with his &lt;b&gt;energy shield&lt;/b&gt;. 

Commander Jerome cannot hijack vehicles, but he can deploy his personal Command Mantis onto the battlefield from the Spirit of Fire. Upgrades include increasing the radius of his Inspire ability and adding a suppressing orbital barrage to the Command Mantis.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.OMEGATEAM">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Enemies’ end.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Omega Team is a Spartan special forces team available exclusively to Commander Jerome. All &lt;b&gt;three&lt;/b&gt; members of Omega Team are deployed into battle via drop pods. Legendary soldiers in their own right, Omega Team members &lt;b&gt;Inspire&lt;/b&gt; nearby units in addition to packing heavy weapons. 

Robert-025 is armed with a fast-firing Plasma Cannon, Leon-011 is fitted for close-quarters combat with a custom Energy Sword, and August-099 is a crack shot with her Railgun. As Spartans, each member of Omega Team has &lt;b&gt;energy shields&lt;/b&gt; and the ability to &lt;b&gt;Hijack&lt;/b&gt; enemy vehicles.

Omega Team is a fast reaction team of Spartan super-soldiers deployed to colony worlds threatened by the Covenant. Using the fastest transports available, Omega Team rushes to reinforce local defenses and buy time for a UNSC response or—more often—an emergency evacuation and enforcement of classified last-stand protocols. 

In this latter role Omega Team is responsible for denial of critical resources, data, and personnel to the enemy by any means necessary, including deployment of weapons of mass destruction to prevent capture and utilization. 

Red Team worked closely with Omega Team several times, including the defense of Arcadia’s capital city when it was attacked in 2531, but were separated when the &lt;i&gt;Spirit of Fire&lt;/i&gt; departed the system to chase retreating Covenant forces. Commander Jerome has discerned they survived the war, based on UNSC records recovered from the Henry Lamb facility, but he can only speculate as to their current activities.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.BATTLEAPC">Mastodon</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.COMMANDERJEROME">Commander Jerome</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.COMMANDMANTIS">Command Mantis</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.HEROJEROME">Commander Jerome</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.OMEGATEAM">Omega Team</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.LEADERSELECT.ROLE01.ARBITER">Elite Assault</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.LEADERSELECT.ROLE01.COMMANDERJEROME">Mechanized Force</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.LEADERSELECT.ROLE02.ARBITER">Vicious Blade</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.LEADERSELECT.ROLE02.COMMANDERJEROME">Special Operations</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.LEADERSELECT.ROLE03.ARBITER">Covert Ops</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.LEADERSELECT.ROLE03.COMMANDERJEROME">Final Stand</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.LEADERSELECT.SHORTDESCR.ARBITER">The Arbiter Ripa 'Moramee utilizes special stasis fields to trap enemies and control the battlefield.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.LEADERSELECT.SHORTDESCR.ARBITER.BLITZ">The Arbiter Ripa 'Moramee utilizes special stasis fields to trap enemies and control the battlefield.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.LEADERSELECT.SHORTDESCR.COMMANDERJEROME">Omega Team's leader and a veteran Spartan of the Spirit of Fire, Jerome inspires and bolsters troops under his command.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.LEADERSELECT.SHORTDESCR.COMMANDERJEROME.BLITZ">Omega Team's leader and a veteran Spartan of the Spirit of Fire, Jerome inspires and bolsters troops under his command.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.LEADERSELECT.TITLE.ARBITER">The Arbiter</str>
	<str id="UIDLC2.LEADERSELECT.TITLE.COMMANDERJEROME">Commander Jerome</str>
</string_table>