<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<str id="DLC31JOH.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.COLOSSUS">Heavy-metal mayhem.

The Colossus is a superheavy vehicle unit which can be deployed by Sergeant Johnson in place of the Scorpion. It is relatively slow, but fitted with a devastating arsenal, capable of taking down almost any foe. The Colossus’ primary weapon is a long-range heavy railgun, a massive weapon originally designed for installation on fortified structures. While the rail cannon can only target ground units, its autocannon has an all-environment engagement profile. After upgrades the Colossus can use Stomp, sending out a shockwave that stuns and damages enemy ground units.

The Colossus is a next-generation exoskeleton combat unit designed by Materials Group and Hannibal Weapon Systems for the UNSC Army. Isabel retains its manufacturing templates from her supply-chain training on Earth, though manufacturing these massive combat machines represents a considerable burden on the Spirit of Fire’s supplies. Sergeant Johnson claims to have acquired the materials for his Colossus units via the classic Marine Corps logistical expediency of ‘borrowing’ equipment that isn’t nailed down (or couldn’t be pried free), but his actual source for these machines is a mystery wrapped in an enigma, protected by shield generators and several tons of Titanium-A armor plating.</str>
	<str id="DLC31JOH.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.JOHNSON">That’s Sergeant MAJOR Johnson to you, chucklehead!

From the halls of Installation 04 to the shores of Harvest, Sergeant Johnson represented the UNSC with distinction and honor his entire life, and is remembered as a hero in death. However, in a twist of fate (and poor records-keeping), the UNSC Marine Corps accidently assigned the life-challenged veteran to a position on board the long-lost Spirit of Fire. Even with the small handicap of being dead, Johnson isn’t one to disobey a direct order from his beloved Corps and he sprung back to life ready to kick all butts that need kicking. The subsequent story of how he arrived at his new duty station is still classified, but trust us, it’s a good one.

Sergeant Johnson favors a strong defense backed by heavy bipedal killing machines: Siege Turret Drop and Bunker Drop extend his fortifications, while EMP MAC Blast and Mech Overcharge give his combat walkers an upper hand in critical battles. But that’s not all, the Corps has seen fit to issue Sergeant Johnson the Digging In Deep advanced power, letting him construct all structures on existing bases (excluding turrets) for free. Oh, and he can also get up close and personal with the Banished by leading from the front lines in the Green Machine, his personalized HRUNTING/YGGDRASIL MARK I[J] Armor Defense System.</str>
	<str id="DLC31JOH.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.JOHNSONMECH">Lean, mean, killing machine.

When Sergeant Johnson joined the Corps they didn’t have any fancy-schmanzy power armor, but he’s a quick learner. He drops onto the Ark in the “Green Machine,” a bipedal weapon system custom-fitted with an array of miniguns, phased-plasma fusils, sonic blindwolf repellers, repair beacon pods, and fast-regen energy shields. He keeps a sharp stick handy as a backup weapon. The energy shielding rapidly regenerates after it hasn’t been hit for a few seconds, which plays well with Sergeant Johnson’s preferred tactics of hit-and-run raids and well-timed combined-arms strikes. The suit’s repair beacon ability heals up to ten nearby allies with constructor beams tuned to a pleasing Marine Corps-approved green color.

The suit can be upgraded in the field, further enhancing the Green Machine’s killing power. The Gauss Chaingun upgrade adds specialized high-power ammunition while the Beacon Shield pairs the repair beacon with a bubble shield, reducing incoming damage for those inside the repair radius. And last—but certainly not least—the suit can be upgraded with a Smart Missile pod for dealing with pesky nuisances at long range. Why doesn’t he wear a helmet? Well, would YOU hide behind an armored faceplate if you had Sergeant Johnson’s rugged good looks?</str>
	<str id="DLC31JOH.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.MANTIS">Mark IX Armor Defense System.

The Mantis is a combat vehicle used in a number of different configurations by the UNSC and licensed security forces. The Mantis replaces the Warthog in Sergeant Johnson’s force. Its default weapon is a chaingun, which can target both ground and air targets. The Missile/Shield Requisition upgrade increases the number of missiles the Mantis can fire and adds energy shielding, while the Gauss/Designator Requisition upgrade replaces the conventional chaingun with a gauss repeater and adds a networked target designator. The target designator allows the Mantis to “paint” a single unit and coordinate attacks using the local battlenet, increasing all damage the target takes from friendly units. Groups of Mantis walkers will smart target their designators.

Highly mobile, well-protected, air-droppable, and reconfigurable, the Mantis represents the state-of-the-art in infantry walkers. Mantis units were stationed at the Henry Lamb Research Outpost for site security, but many were destroyed in the initial Banished attack. Well aware of their combat potential, Isabel has begun producing a modified version of the Mantis for the use of Spirit of Fire’s ground forces, with adjustments to reuse parts produced for the Cyclops and Colossus. While capable, these units lack the neural interface control systems installed on contemporary UNSC models; a necessary concession due to the Spirit of Fire’s older manufacturing technology.</str>
	<str id="DLC31JOH.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.COLOSSUS">Colossus</str>
	<str id="DLC31JOH.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.GREENMACHINE">Green Machine</str>
	<str id="DLC31JOH.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.JOHNSON">Sergeant Johnson</str>
	<str id="DLC31JOH.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.JOHNSONMECH">Green Machine</str>
	<str id="DLC31JOH.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.MANTIS">Mantis</str>
	<str id="DLC31JOH.LEADERSELECT.BODY.DROPBUNKER">Home away from home.

The Bunker Drop is an air-droppable garrison building used by the UNSC. It is permanent, but does cost population capacity. It has enough fire points for squads, and has a built-in table for card games while the troops wait for enemies to wander by. The Reinforced Bunker upgrade increases its infantry capacity and adds a shield.</str>
	<str id="DLC31JOH.LEADERSELECT.ROLE01.JOHNSON">Mech Offense</str>
	<str id="DLC31JOH.LEADERSELECT.ROLE02.JOHNSON">Bunker Down</str>
	<str id="DLC31JOH.LEADERSELECT.ROLE03.JOHNSON">Titan</str>
	<str id="DLC31JOH.LEADERSELECT.SHORTDESCR.JOHNSON">Sergeant Major Avery Johnson, a hero of the Covenant War, geared up for battle. He's a dangerous adversary due to his powerful mechs and solid command.</str>
	<str id="DLC31JOH.LEADERSELECT.SHORTDESCR.JOHNSON.BLITZ">Sergeant Major Avery Johnson, a hero of the Covenant War, geared up for battle. He's a dangerous adversary due to his powerful mechs and solid command.</str>
	<str id="DLC31JOH.LEADERSELECT.TITLE.DROPBUNKER">Bunker Drop</str>
	<str id="DLC31JOH.LEADERSELECT.TITLE.JOHNSON">Sergeant Johnson</str>
</string_table>