<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<str id="UIDLC4.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.BANISHED.DESCRIPTION">The Banished fight a desperate battle against a terrifying and ancient enemy on the Ark.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.BANISHED.LONGDESCRIPTION">The Banished fight a desperate battle against a terrifying and ancient enemy on the Ark.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.BANISHED.TITLE">AWAKENING THE NIGHTMARE</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.COMINGSOON">COMING SOON</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.COOPERROR">Your co-op partner does not own this DLC</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.COOPERRORDESCRIPTION">Both players are required to own these missions to play co-op.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.DESCRIPTION">Select the Halo Wars 2 main campaign or DLC content to play.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.MAIN.DESCRIPTION">Captain Cutter and the Spirit of Fire return to battle a new threat to the Ark.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.MAIN.PURCHASE">Purchase Halo Wars 2</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.MAIN.PURCHASEDESCRIPTION">Purchase Halo Wars 2 main game from the store.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.MAINCAMPAIGN.TITLE">HALO WARS 2</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.MISSIONS.DESCRIPTION">Major Vaughan and his crack ODST team race against time to stop an unknown Banished plan.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.MISSIONS.PURCHASE">Purchase Operation: Spearbreaker</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.MISSIONS.PURCHASEDESCRIPTION">Purchase the two new missions from the store.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.MISSIONS.TITLE">OPERATION: SPEARBREAKER</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.PURCHASE">PURCHASE NOW</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.TITLE">SELECT CAMPAIGN OR MISSION</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CAREERPAGE.CAMPAIGNPANEL.PURCHASECAMPAIGN">Purchase this campaign in the store</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.BODY.FLOATSLOW.M02A">&lt;b&gt; From the journal of Val ‘Telram, Sangheili Guard and translator.&lt;/b&gt;

I was overseeing a group of Huragoks when I heard the shrieking of metal, an almost animalistic cry that pulled at my gut as the Sentinels tore the Enduring Conviction apart. I would have given anything to be with my clan brothers then, to die a warrior’s death among my brethren. Instead, I watched helpless as the Sentinels carved up the ship – my home and family.

The shame I felt nearly drove me to madness. It had been weeks since I had even unsheathed my blade, but they told me my skills as an interpreter were more important than my swordsmanship. When we left the Covenant to join with Atriox, we lost access to all logistics and docking support. No more repair crews, just the few Huragoks we happened to have on board when the Shipmaster pledged allegiance to the Banished. 

My ability to communicate with the Huragoks, the sign language and the patience required to learn it, quickly isolated me from my own kind. While my brothers fought in battle, I was to work with the Huragoks to secure resources and unlock ancient technology. How I wished we had a Unggoy Deacon that could have taken my place. I felt less than a warrior. 

Now at last I feel that vengeance and redemption is within my reach, and the instrument is the very thing that has separated me from my warrior brothers. Atriox has charged the mysterious Lekgolo known as Colony to seek out Forerunner weapons, and it has found a long forgotten ship. I have been assigned to watch over and communicate with a Huragok, which goes by the name of ‘Floats Low But Steady’ because of its habit of almost skimming the ground as it works. Within the span of a day, it has started ‘talking’ to the ship and the launching systems that hold it. I consider myself fluent, but there are occasional words I cannot accurately translate. The closest translations seem to be ‘bloom’, ‘grow’ or ‘seed’.

The Jiralhanae look with disgust as I work with Floats Low as they fear what they do not understand, but they cannot hide their awe at the results. The Ship seems to grow and rebuild itself from the very launch system, a spear to drive deep into the heart of our enemies.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.BODY.HOLDFAST.M01B">&lt;b&gt; Balkarus, Brute captain.&lt;/b&gt;

Attention pack brothers! 

The next Jiralhanae that comes to me asking for Unggoy replacements to bolster the ones he has ‘misplaced’ will lose his tongue to my blade! I understand patience is troublesome for warriors such as us, but hurling the whelps at the cloaking field to watch them fizzle and pop is a waste of resources!

True, it is amusing and I am willing to turn a blind eye to the occasional ‘accident’, but as disgustingly numerous as the Unggoy are, our forces here are limited until the operation is over. Besides, the grating squealing of the pathetic ones are likely to attract the unwanted attention of the Sentinels, which will slow down our plans.

Until the operation is over, the cloaking field must remain in place, and we must hold here to ensure its function. Despite their weaknesses, the humans seem to have eyes everywhere and they must not find out our plans. Save your bloodlust for the enemy, or strive for patience until the operation is complete. We are close now, and it will not be long before we can indulge ourselves again. 
Stay your hand, pack brothers, and sate your urges with the knowledge that we will soon have vengeance on the humans for the loss of the Enduring Conviction.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.BODY.NEWCOMMANDER.M01A">&lt;b&gt; Balkarus, Brute captain.&lt;/b&gt; Recorded Date: 4/1/2559 &lt;/b&gt;

Forticus, we have received the Huragok you sent us and have already put them to work around the operation site. I have tasked a Sangheili to look after them, for I cannot stomach to be around them for long. Simply the sight of the Sangheili communicating to those creatures with strange hand signals repulses me. I often need to punt three of four short ones into a deep chasm before my mind settles again!

I fear I would need to kick a thousand Unggoy into the depths to restore my peace of mind after meeting our new commander. While stationed at the raid camp, I heard utterings about a Lekgolo who had risen up the ranks to the standing of actually having Atriox’s ear! I now know those rumors to be true, and that it calls itself ‘Colony’. I have only glimpsed its hulking form from a distance, but the others swear they actually heard it speak, or something close to the sound.  I can tell many of the younger Brutes are nervous in its presence and guard their conversations, for if they are truly a hive mind, then surely all eels hear what one hears.

Atriox appears to have tasked Colony with investigating the ancient technologies here and restoring them for our own use. He, they – whatever it is – seems to have curbed its feasting habits and has already made progress in establishing a cloaking field over the site. Such power makes me nervous. The Lekgolo are formidable fighters, but sometimes I wish the Covenant had left them burrowing away amongst the relics like the worms they are. Still, if it gives us the chance to strike back at the humans, then I welcome it, but it is not the natural way of things!

I must end my transmission now; I swear I heard something slithering behind me.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.BODY.TENSEDBOLT.M02B">&lt;b&gt;Unknown Author, Installation 00, Date: 29,823 BCE&lt;/b&gt;

It disturbs me to admit, but I always feel a wash of ennui after dismantling one of the Librarian’s ship-seeds. As with all my master’s designs, architecture and function balance in perfect harmony. It seems such a pity to put it back in the box.

It is as if a mighty archer has flexed their muscles, drawn back the bow to full strength and then suddenly frozen in full pose. The tension remains, the action and all potential postponed, perhaps never to be realised. The temptation to launch it and to break the stasis is strong, so I must busy myself with other tasks. However, every Refugia has some buried inert marvel of technology; weapons, ships, power sources - all patiently waiting to be put to use once again.

This is the way of things, and at least the ship is in sympathy with this installation. As with all the Librarian’s plans, Installation 00 has performed admirably, but now it lays dormant, sleeping. It is my task to watch and maintain this installation should the threat arise once again.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.TITLE.FLOATSLOW.M02A">Floats Low But Steady</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.TITLE.HOLDFAST.M01B">Hold Fast</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.TITLE.NEWCOMMANDER.M01A">A New Commander</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.TITLE.TENSEDBOLT.M02B">A Tensed Bolt</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.FORERUNNER.BODY.CUSTODIANSENTINEL">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Forerunner system offensive/defensive drones.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;

The Controller Sentinels’ primary function is to guard valuable Forerunner technologies on the Ark. Developed and deployed to counter the escalating threat from the UNSC and the Banished, these flying Sentinels are loosely ‘tethered’ within set radii of important sites and will attack anyone that comes close, or attempts to take control of the sector.

An impenetrable energy shield protects the front of each Controller Sentinel, an improvement on the already powerful shields used by the Enforcer Sentinels whose function was to suppress Flood outbreaks. Underneath it fires a continuous Sentinel Beam to prevent enemies from hiding in its blind spot, but its primary weapon is a devastating supercharged Sentinel Pulse.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.FORERUNNER.BODY.FORERUNNERSHIP">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;A long dormant Despair-class fighter.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Forerunner Despair-class fighters saw action during the Forerunner-Flood war against the rogue Monitor Mendicant Bias. After the firing of the Halo superweapon, some of these fighters moved to Shield Worlds and Halo installations. 

The Forerunner ship found and reactivated by Colony’s Huragoks was ‘regrown’ from a ship-seed planted by the Librarian prior to the Halo activation. Ship-seed technology provides all the building blueprints needed to build a ship upon activation using on-site materials.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.FORERUNNER.TITLE.CUSTODIANSENTINEL">Controller Sentinel</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.FORERUNNER.TITLE.FORERUNNERSHIP">Forerunner Ship</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.M01.COLLECT.UNLOCKCONDITION">Unlock by finding a collectable in 'Gatecrashers'.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.M01LOGS.UNLOCKCONDITION">Unlocked by completing 'Gatecrashers'.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.M02.COLLECT.UNLOCKCONDITION">Unlock by finding a collectable in 'Not On My Watch'.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.M02LOGS.UNLOCKCONDITION">Unlocked by completing 'Not On My Watch'.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.BOOMERANGCOMPANY">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;1st Squad, 1st Platoon, B Company, 9th Shock Troops Battalion.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Major Vaughan’s command squad, callsign Sunray 1-1, is the lead element of Boomerang Company, the UNSC’s most elite force of Orbital Drop Shock Troopers. 

Warrant Officer Quinn has been many things in her life, but none have been as meaningful as service in the ranks of the &lt;i&gt;Spirit of Fire&lt;/i&gt;’s 9th Shock Troops Battalion. A highly trained signals intelligence analyst and electronic warfare operator, Quinn accompanies ODST pre-assault and deep strike post-assault teams on missions that require the application of technical wizardry in addition to raw firepower.

With Professor Anders’ departure on the Halo ring it has fallen to Quinn and other UNSC personnel who have demonstrated affinity with—and knowledge of—Forerunner systems to be boots-on-the-ground resources for task force commanders. It’s a job she relishes.

Quinn and Major Vaughn have a long history of service together on board the &lt;i&gt;Spirit of Fire&lt;/i&gt;. Quinn has no particular love for the ship itself—and despises its recycled air and the peculiar pull of the barracks’ artificial gravity—but she cares deeply for the crew and troops aboard it. When Quinn accompanies Vaugh on his Ark expeditions, she serves as the command squad’s technician and “Ark door opener,” in addition to handling a prototype target designator for the &lt;i&gt;Spirit of Fire&lt;/i&gt;’s new &lt;b&gt;EMP Ordnance&lt;/b&gt; support drop.

Petty Officer Gruss is the Navy combat medic assigned to Major Vaughan’s command squad. A woman of (very) few words, the ODSTs make it their mission to interpret “Doc’s” opinion of their shenanigans by analyzing her body language, sighs, rude gestures, and grunts of disapproval. This friendly harassment ends when combat begins, for Doc holds the lives of the troopers in her able hands, wielding biofoam and trauma packs across the squad’s position with incredible skill and delicacy. So perfect is her timing in dealing with injury that it borders on the prescient, and squad members resign themselves to the inevitable if Doc appears near them during battle.

In addition to her medical skill, Gruss has shown a remarkable talent for escape and evasion by avoiding the Marines’ many and varied attempts to induct her into their ranks as an honorary Helljumper. This irks some members of the battalion, but even ODSTs are not crazy enough to risk the ire of a medic (and Major Vaughan) by pressing the issue. When deployed with the command squad Doc patches up the team’s injuries with her &lt;b&gt;medkit&lt;/b&gt;.

Cursed with always being the right woman at the right place at the right time, Turpin wishes for nothing more than a life of glorious anonymity, rather than a life filled with fateful encounters. Turpin’s recent assignment to the command squad has the rest of Boomerang Company nervous, as her reputation for dragging fellow Marines into perilous adventure is well known among the &lt;i&gt;Spirit of Fire&lt;/i&gt;’s crew and troops. As the squad prepares to deploy for a routine recon mission on the Ark’s surface, Turpin crosses her fingers that nothing of interest or importance will transpire, just this once.

Turpin carriers the squad’s battlenet relay and operates a drone &lt;b&gt;high-energy laser&lt;/b&gt; weapon platform designed by Isabel.

Lance Corporal Sparks is the squad sniper, and something of a wildcard even among the &lt;i&gt;Spirit of Fire&lt;/i&gt;’s impressively large cast of misfits and rogues. Sparks’ long list of non-judicial punishments and reprimands would have landed him a full-time billet in the ship’s brig were it not for two unique qualities: his unparalleled skill with a SRS-99 anti-materiel rifle, and supernatural ability to acquire the rarest (and tastiest) meal packs on the ship. Luckily, Helljumpers value good chow and a good shot more than adherence to UNSC regulations, which keeps this “Lance Criminal” from behind bars—so far.

Sparks provides fire support for the command squad with his &lt;b&gt;sniper rifle&lt;/b&gt; and assists Turpin by designating priority targets for her drone. He also contributes to the squad’s morale with his vast knowledge of terrible jokes and patently ridiculous (but completely true) “war stories” from his civilian days.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.BOOMERANGCOMPANYGRUSS">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;1st Squad, 1st Platoon, B Company, 9th Shock Troops Battalion.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Major Vaughan’s command squad, callsign Sunray 1-1, is the lead element of Boomerang Company, the UNSC’s most elite force of Orbital Drop Shock Troopers (though that’s what they all say). 

&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;UNSC Navy Medic.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Petty Officer Gruss is the Navy combat medic assigned to Major Vaughan’s command squad. A woman of (very) few words, the ODSTs make it their mission to interpret “Doc’s” opinion of their shenanigans by analyzing her body language, sighs, rude gestures, and grunts of disapproval. This friendly harassment ends when combat begins, for Doc holds the lives of the troopers in her able hands, wielding biofoam and trauma packs across the squad’s position with incredible skill and delicacy. So perfect is her timing in dealing with injury that it borders on the prescient, and squad members resign themselves to the inevitable if Doc appears near them during battle.

In addition to her medical skill, Gruss has shown a remarkable talent for escape and evasion by avoiding the Marines’ many and varied attempts to induct her into their ranks as an honorary Helljumper. This irks some members of the battalion, but even ODSTs are not crazy enough to risk the ire of a medic (and Major Vaughan) by pressing the issue. When deployed with the command squad Doc patches up the team’s injuries with her &lt;b&gt;medkit&lt;/b&gt;.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.BOOMERANGCOMPANYQUINN">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;1st Squad, 1st Platoon, B Company, 9th Shock Troops Battalion.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Major Vaughan’s command squad, callsign Sunray 1-1, is the lead element of Boomerang Company, the UNSC’s most elite force of Orbital Drop Shock Troopers (though that’s what they all say). 

&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Signals Reconnaissance Specialist.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Quinn has been many things in her life, but none have been as meaningful as service in the ranks of the &lt;i&gt;Spirit of Fire&lt;/i&gt;’s 9th Shock Troops Battalion. A highly trained signals intelligence analyst and electronic warfare operator, Quinn accompanies ODST pre-assault and deep strike post-assault teams on missions that require the application of technical wizardry in addition to raw firepower.

With Professor Anders’ departure on the Halo ring it has fallen to Quinn and other UNSC personnel who have demonstrated affinity with—and knowledge of—Forerunner systems to be boots-on-the-ground resources for task force commanders. It’s a job she relishes.

Quinn and Major Vaughan have a long history of service together on board the &lt;i&gt;Spirit of Fire&lt;/i&gt;. Quinn has no particular love for the ship itself—and despises its recycled air and the peculiar pull of the barracks’ artificial gravity—but she cares deeply for the crew and troops aboard it. When Quinn accompanies Vaughan on his Ark expeditions, she serves as the command squad’s technician and “Ark door opener,” in addition to handling a prototype target designator for the &lt;i&gt;Spirit of Fire&lt;/i&gt;’s new &lt;b&gt;EMP Ordnance&lt;/b&gt; support drop.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.BOOMERANGCOMPANYSPARKS">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;1st Squad, 1st Platoon, B Company, 9th Shock Troops Battalion.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Major Vaughan’s command squad, callsign Sunray 1-1, is the lead element of Boomerang Company, the UNSC’s most elite force of Orbital Drop Shock Troopers (though that’s what they all say). 

&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Designated Marksman.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Sparks is the squad sniper, and something of a wildcard even among the &lt;i&gt;Spirit of Fire&lt;/i&gt;’s impressively large cast of misfits and rogues. Sparks’ long list of non-judicial punishments and reprimands would have landed him a full-time billet in the ship’s brig were it not for two unique qualities: his unparalleled skill with a SRS-99 anti-materiel rifle, and supernatural ability to acquire the rarest (and tastiest) meal packs on the ship. Luckily, Helljumpers value good chow and a good shot more than adherence to UNSC regulations, which keeps this “Lance Criminal” from behind bars—so far.

Sparks provides fire support for the command squad with his &lt;b&gt;sniper rifle&lt;/b&gt; and assists Turpin by designating priority targets for her drone. He also contributes to the squad’s morale with his vast knowledge of terrible jokes and patently ridiculous (but completely true) “war stories” from his civilian days.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.BOOMERANGCOMPANYTURPIN">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;1st Squad, 1st Platoon, B Company, 9th Shock Troops Battalion.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Major Vaughan’s command squad, callsign Sunray 1-1, is the lead element of Boomerang Company, the UNSC’s most elite force of Orbital Drop Shock Troopers (though that’s what they all say). 

&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Drone Controller.&lt;b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Cursed with always being the right woman at the right place at the right time, Turpin wishes for nothing more than a life of glorious anonymity, rather than a life filled with fateful encounters. Turpin’s recent assignment to the command squad has the rest of Boomerang Company nervous, as her reputation for dragging fellow Marines into perilous adventure is well known among the &lt;i&gt;Spirit of Fire&lt;/i&gt;’s crew and troops. As the squad prepares to deploy for a routine recon mission on the Ark’s surface, Turpin crosses her fingers that nothing of interest or importance will transpire, just this once.

Turpin carries the squad’s battlenet relay and operates a drone &lt;b&gt;high-energy laser&lt;/b&gt; weapon platform designed by Isabel.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.BODY.MAJORVAUGHAN">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;1st Squad, 1st Platoon, B Company, 9th Shock Troops Battalion.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Major Vaughan’s command squad, callsign Sunray 1-1, is the lead element of Boomerang Company, the UNSC’s most elite force of Orbital Drop Shock Troopers (though that’s what they all say). 

&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Mustang.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Born to a family of politicians and corporate executives, Vaughan lived a life of privilege and luxury in the most prestigious of Earth’s arcologies. But when a family squabble escalated, a rebellious young Vaughan made the worst and best decision of his life by enlisting in the UNSC Marines. 

Rammed through boot camp during the height of the insurrection, Vaughan had no time to regret his decision before shipping off to war against terrorists and separatist movements in the Outer Colonies. His first duty station as a green recruit was the &lt;i&gt;Spirit of Fire&lt;/i&gt;, an old ship retasked with transporting UNSC military and police forces to colonies it once established. Few appreciated the irony more than Vaughan, given the role his own family played in exacerbating colonial tensions. 

Years later he found himself on the &lt;i&gt;Spirit of Fire&lt;/i&gt; again, this time as a commissioned ODST officer on a campaign against the alien Covenant that would take him from half-glassed colonies to ancient Forerunner shield worlds, and beyond. It’s been a long road, but Vaughan takes solace in the fact that this is definitely &lt;b&gt;not&lt;/b&gt; the course his family had pre-charted for him.

The &lt;i&gt;Spirit of Fire&lt;/i&gt;’s unusual situation makes Vaughan one of the highest-ranking UNSC officers in the Ark conflict, but he prefers to leave strategy and high-level operational planning to the experts. He’s a Helljumper, and his place is in a drop pod plunging feet-first and on fire into the cauldron of battle. In addition to coordinating Boomerang Company’s deployments and leading the command squad, Vaughan carries the squad’s SPNKr &lt;b&gt;rocket launcher&lt;/b&gt;, which he occasionally uses as a blunt teaching instrument to knock sense into younger ODSTs.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.BOOMERANGCOMPANY">ODST Command Squad Sunray 1-1</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.BOOMERANGCOMPANYGRUSS">Corpsman Gruss</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.BOOMERANGCOMPANYQUINN">Warrant Officer Quinn</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.BOOMERANGCOMPANYSPARKS">Lance Corporal Sparks</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.BOOMERANGCOMPANYTURPIN">Corporal Turpin</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.CODEX.UNITSUNSC.TITLE.MAJORVAUGHAN">Major Vaughan</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.LEADERSELECT.ROLE01.SERINA">Sub-Zero</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.LEADERSELECT.ROLE02.SERINA">Blizzard</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.LEADERSELECT.ROLE03.SERINA">Frostbite</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.LEADERSELECT.SHORTDESCR.SERINA">Smart AI that ran the Spirit of Fire's systems before being lost with all hands, Serina was an expert in cryo technology.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.LEADERSELECT.SHORTDESCR.SERINA.BLITZ">Smart AI that ran the Spirit of Fire's systems before being lost with all hands, Serina was an expert in cryo technology.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.LEADERSELECT.TITLE.SERINA">Serina</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.LOADGAME.ENTITLEMENT.ERROR">You need to install the %1 DLC to load this savegame.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.MISSIONBRIEFSCREEN.LOCATION.M01">NORTH SPIRE/UNKNOWN BANISHED OPERATION</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.MISSIONBRIEFSCREEN.LOCATION.M02">NORTH SPIRE/FORERUNNER LAUNCH</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.MISSIONBRIEFSCREEN.LOCATION.MISSIONDLC401">NORTH SPIRE/UNKNOWN BANISHED OPERATION</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.MISSIONBRIEFSCREEN.LOCATION.MISSIONDLC402">NORTH SPIRE/FORERUNNER LAUNCH</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.MISSIONBRIEFSCREEN.TITLE.MISSIONDLC401">GATECRASHERS</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.MISSIONBRIEFSCREEN.TITLE.MISSIONDLC402">NOT ON MY WATCH</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.MISSIONSPAGE.DLCMISSIONSTITLE.DLC4">OPERATION: SPEARBREAKER</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.MISSIONSPAGE.MISSIONNAME.DLC4M01">GATECRASHERS</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.MISSIONSPAGE.MISSIONNAME.DLC4M02">NOT ON MY WATCH</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.MISSIONSPAGE.NEWMISSIONSAVAILABLE">@NewIcon@ New missions available!</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.MISSIONSPAGE.SHORTDESCR.DLC4M01">Major Vaughan leads his Boomerang Company ODSTs to a Banished operation site.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.MISSIONSPAGE.SHORTDESCR.DLC4M02">Major Vaughan and his ODST team battle to stop the Banished from launching a Forerunner ship.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.PAUSESCREEN.SHORTDESCR.DLC4M01">Major Vaughan leads his Boomerang Company ODSTs to a Banished operation site.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.PAUSESCREEN.SHORTDESCR.DLC4M02">Major Vaughan and his ODST team battle to stop the Banished from launching a Forerunner ship.</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.PAUSESCREEN.TITLE.DLC4M01">Gatecrashers</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.PAUSESCREEN.TITLE.DLC4M02">Not On My Watch</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.RICHPRESENCE.MISSIONNAMES.M01">Gatecrashers</str>
	<str id="UIDLC4.RICHPRESENCE.MISSIONNAMES.M02">Not On My Watch</str>
</string_table>