<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<string_table xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<str id="UIEP2.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.BANISHED.PURCHASE">Purchase Awakening the Nightmare</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.BANISHED.PURCHASEDESCRIPTION">Purchase the new campaign from the store.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CAMPAIGNSELECTION.BANISHED.TITLE">AWAKENING THE NIGHTMARE</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.BUILDBAN.BODY.MEGATURRET">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Heavy artillery emplacement.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

The Mega Turret is an automated, long-range artillery platform available to Warlord Pavium. They fire powerful plasma torpedoes that can be upgraded to scorch the impact point and leave a pool of &lt;b&gt;Lingering Death&lt;/b&gt;. As if this devastation wasn't enough, they can also use Banished-modified &lt;b&gt;Compound Detonators&lt;/b&gt; for even greater damage. These mega turrets are massive and power hungry, and require a standard base building slot.

The Mega Turret was used to protect Covenant military and religious installations, but these massive cannons have also been encountered at remote colonies and outposts guarding nothing of obvious value and reflexively attacking all who approach without long-forgotten authorization codes. The Banished deploy the Mega Turret as a straightforward anti-siege weapon at war camps on the Ark which have the necessary infrastructure and permanence to support their use.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.BUILDBAN.TITLE.MEGATURRET">Mega Turret</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.BODY.BROTHERSINARMS.M02_01">Plipbab, Grunt coordinator at High Charity crash site. Transcription Date: 6/4/2559

Central base, this is Plipbab, reporting from the High Charity salvage operation. There was a tragical  accident this morning, and, uh, we’re going to need more Unggoy. Voridus has been experimenting with the wormguy weapons and so we were movin’ some of his new incendiary jelly. Everything was goin’ fine and I was bein’ real responsible! Then one thing led to another and there was a big noise and it started rainin’ Grunt gumbo, and you know it’s never good when a coordinator is wading through little chunks of his buddies.

So I go to ‘fess up to Ol’ Angry Chops and I know he’s gonna be in a punchin’ mood, but he’s doing argues with Pavium! Pavium was all like “WHY ARE YOU SO CHARGY?” and Voridus is all like “WHY ARE YOU SO BOSSY?” – somethin’ like that, I got scared and I don’t remember much. So now Pavium’s in charge of the excavations at High Charity, but I think he’s also makin’ sure Voridus doesn’t break anything important. Voridus is known for the breakin’, so they say. [1/2]</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.BODY.BROTHERSINARMS.M02_02">Plipbab, Grunt coordinator at High Charity crash site. Transcription Date: 6/4/2559

So anyway, I says to myself, “Plipbab,” I says, “this is maybe not a good time to give angry Brute commanders bad news” and I start sneakin’ away, but Pavium smells right through my sneak and does a growl. So now I know I’m in trouble anyway, so I just tell him about the exploding Grunts and do my most bravest cower. 

And I’m pretty sure I’m gonna be dead, but Voridus, he just starts laughing! And then Pavium starts laughin’, and so I start doin’ laughs too! And we’re all havin’ a great time and Voridus says it reminds him of a time he stole some Covenant weapons but they overcharged in the teleporter, and Pavium is laughing and says that he had to bail him out of that mess too, and then Voridus says it didn’t happen like that, and Pavium says that it did, and then they’re arguing again so I slowly stop laughin’ and sneak back to my post. 

So that’s my story about when I didn’t get in trouble and instead was best friends with Voridus and Pavium. Those guys are real scary – it’s like the only time they’re not fighting is when they’re fighting with somebody else. [2/2]</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.BODY.IDLEHANDS.M04_01">Unknown Author, Installation 00, Date 12/13/2552 

Recently I have had troubling thoughts. 

I am caretaker of this installation and it is my duty to maintain the natural balance of things, and I have performed my task admirably. But what I have learned from this experience, this war, is the terrible cost of peace. 

For millennia, all was quiet and still and the wonderful designs of this installation meant I had relatively little to do except making improvements and the occasional minor systems repair. The paradox is that the better I perform in my job, the less I have to do.  

As a result, I am conflicted by the recent events on this installation. The damage caused by the invaders and their war horrifies me, but it has given me a purpose once again. The one constant is that this installation is the most important thing in the galaxy and I must protect it at all costs. The destruction that scars the place I am duty bound to protect has focused my thoughts for the first time in centuries, and so it is once again through conflict that I have found a renewed sense of purpose. [1/2]</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.BODY.IDLEHANDS.M04_02">Unknown Author, Installation 00, Date 12/14/2552 

I have marshalled my sentinels to construct a protective quarantine shell around the crash site of the object once known as High Charity. If the Flood were to escape and infect this installation, then everything we fought so hard for so long ago would be jeopardized. This installation’s primary purpose is to create the only weapons capable of stopping a mass Flood outbreak. Upon sealing the shell, my Sentinels will raze the perimeter and modify the refugia to ensure that no sentient life survives nearby. I must deprive the Flood of any host bodies in close proximity to their prison. When all this is done, I will keep a battalion of Sentinels on patrol in the vicinity, not only to guard against the Flood, but to guard against future invaders bent on self-destruction.

This destruction is regrettable, but I consider it a responsible pruning, necessary to the greater good of this installation. I only wish I had the resources to repair the rest of the damage wrought by the war. The moon at the center of the Foundry has been largely depleted, and without necessary support structures in place there is no way for us to find fresh sources for raw materials. 

More frequently, the same thought occurs to me; this installation’s purpose is to safeguard the galaxy, and therefore must be preserved against all threats. But the inhabitants of the galaxy themselves have proven themselves time and time again to be the biggest threat to this installation, their self-destructive actions apparently impossible to curb. 

I shall pursue this paradox, for it is only a matter of time before I will be forced to address it tangibly. [2/2]</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.BODY.PANDORASBOX.M01_01">Field report, comms officer G. Peterson, SF-193-938. Transmission date: 6/1/2559

We’re two klicks out from the High Charity crash zone, but even from this distance it still dominates  the skyline. I wish we had been around to see it hit the dirt, it sure made one heck of dent. It may have been the Covenant’s capital city once, but now it’s nothing but a giant reminder of their failure. 

It’s eerily quiet here, spooky even, and it’s not just the history of the place. Approximately three-hundred meters around the crash zone all life stops growing, as if it hit an invisible line it refuses to cross. Might be intentional on the part of the Ark, but we don’t know enough about the area yet to be sure. Greenery makes way to razed, blackened ground and trees look like used matchsticks, hacked off at the head and stunted. The creepiest thing is there’s no sound from animals, birds, or even insects. Hard to say whether they fled the desolation or the sheer number of Sentinels swarming around here… [1/2]</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.BODY.PANDORASBOX.M01_02">Field report, comms officer G. Peterson, SF-193-938. Transmission date: 6/1/2559

Isabel’s reports from the war indicate that the strange dome over the remains of High Charity is some kind of protective measure the Ark’s systems created after High Charity crashed. Something about walling off alien threats too big to quickly deal with otherwise. It definitely explains the Sentinel presence here. Regardless, after seeing what the Sentinels did to the Enduring Conviction, we’re not about to anger these bees, no matter what kind of honey could be inside.

Our orders are to sit tight and observe. After Major Vaughan’s close shave with that Forerunner ship, the captain has us watching all potential hot spots for Banished activity and odds are Atriox will make a play for High Charity. From what we’ve seen before, Atriox has no compunctions about messing with the Ark in order to get what he wants. [2/2]</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.BODY.TREADCAREFULLY.M03">From the journal of Suta ‘Noram, Sangheili Guard 6/4/2559 

Commander Pavium has stationed me at his salvage operation to provide security in case the humans try to interfere. Though the Jiralhanae are usually ruled purely by instinct and rage, Pavium appears to have a strong tactical mind. Though he would kill me for suggesting so, he would make a fine Sangheili. 

I stand guard as the jabbering Unggoy blast through the wreckage to clear a route through to the ruins of High Charity, so that once Pavium’s and Voridus have looted the area around High Charity of its weapons, we may transport them out quickly and avoid the brunt of the Sentinels wrath.

Perhaps it is the offensive musk of the Jiralhanae or the insistent chattering of the Unggoy, but I feel uneasy. There is something wrong about this. We have all heard the rumors of what happened to High Charity, but we do not talk too loudly about them, for fear of giving them life. I see a glint of the same fear in the eyes of some of the older Jiralhanae, those for whom the Covenant is not just a distant memory.

When we joined the Banished, we set aside all Covenant lies and those gullible enough to believe in them. But now that High Charity looms over us like a giant dead thing, those lies do not seem so foolish. Are we not as guilty as the Covenant by ignoring the warnings about High Charity as they ignored the tales of the Halo Rings?

One thing is certain. There is danger here. The Ark does not deploy its Sentinels without good reason and their numbers are many.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.BODY.UNCOMFORTABLETRUTH.M05_01">Unknown Author, Installation 00, Date 2/19/2553 

High Charity has been successfully sealed, the perimeter has been razed, the Sentinel defences defenses put in place and the Flood contained. I allowed myself a small self-congratulation for a job well done, but now that the dust has settled I find my mind wandering into forbidden territories again.

Therefore, I have set myself the task of cataloguing and researching the Flood and its myriad forms. Of course this installation has full databanks on the Flood’s history and the war my creator’s waged against it, but there is always a small chance of new discoveries, even if it is simply reassessing old knowledge with the context of recent events.

Many regard the Flood as the ultimate representation of chaos, traditionally thought of as the enemy of the natural balance of the universe, a direct threat against the Mantle itself. However, with all things, what is chaotic can form patterns and purpose when viewed from a far or close enough distance. In fact, the most disturbing thought is the single-mindedness of the Flood, its one goal to subsume all sentient life, to make all as one. [1/2]</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.BODY.UNCOMFORTABLETRUTH.M05_02">From records I have studied, as the Flood grows closer to critical density it absorbs the knowledge and intelligence of its hosts. As it grows in strength, co-ordination and self-awareness, it forms Proto-Graveminds and then finally the Gravemind itself. Once a Gravemind has been created, The Flood’s race memory is re-established and it becomes almost unstoppable. This scenario is what led to the creation of the last Halo Array so many years ago. 

From the perspective of the Flood, is this not an attempt at bringing order to the galaxy rather than chaos? It is a dangerous line of thought, and I know there was another who fell into this trap and indeed became instrumental in the downfall of my creators civilization. Fortunately, my loyalty and duty to this installation precludes me from following that path.

My conclusions are still disturbing. The Flood are indeed the great threat to the galaxy my creators feared, but they are the truest to their nature. The Forerunners, the San’ Shyuum, the so-called Reclaimers all declare peace through unity and civilization, yet endlessly make war amongst themselves and others. Wars fought in defense of their own independence while each forcing their own ideas of unity upon their enemies. 

I stand here as a guardian of that chaos. It is an uncomfortable truth. [2/2]</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.BODY.WARPEDREFLECTIONS.M03">Plutus, Brute captain. Emergency signal. 6/4/2559

Voridus, this is Plutus! This is not a call for help, as I know it is already too late for us, but rather a warning. The Flood scourge has breached our base and I can hear the screams of my Jiralhanae brothers from the outer corridors as they fall to the monstrosities. 

We were preparing the laser drills for power extraction when an Unggoy spotted the first form. We laughed at typical Unggoy panic until we saw a Wraith engulfed by a wave of seething sickness. Our defences did little to stop the sheer numbers of Flood when they first attacked, swarming over the turrets and silencing them under mounds of filth. We fell back inside, but they crawled and slithered through the vents and cracks and our base became a slaughterhouse.

I watched as battle-hardened Jiralhanae scream in terror as the Flood twisted their forms into horrifying new shapes, their eyes pleading for a swift death. Warriors I had fought side by side with turned upon me with unknowing eyes and terrible rage.  I ordered the few survivors to fall back to the inner corridors as I planted my last cache of plasma mines, hoping to put an end to the torment suffered by those infected. 

There were moments of silence after the mines exploded, which we used to count our numbers and weapons. We have not enough to hold for an hour, let along push back this enemy. Already, the uncanny screams have started rumbling again, and the pounding has begun as they fling their battered and contorted bodies against the door. 

We laughed at the Covenant rumors about High Charity, but they were all true. The Flood will consume all. You must...

[Transcription ends]</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.TITLE.BROTHERSINARMS.M02_01">Brothers in Arms I</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.TITLE.BROTHERSINARMS.M02_02">Brothers in Arms II</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.TITLE.IDLEHANDS.M04_01">Idle Hands I</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.TITLE.IDLEHANDS.M04_02">Idle Hands II</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.TITLE.PANDORASBOX.M01_01">Pandora's Box I</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.TITLE.PANDORASBOX.M01_02">Pandora's Box II</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.TITLE.TREADCAREFULLY.M03">Tread Carefully</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.TITLE.UNCOMFORTABLETRUTH.M05_01">An Uncomfortable Truth I</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.TITLE.UNCOMFORTABLETRUTH.M05_02">An Uncomfortable Truth II</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.CAMPAIGN.TITLE.WARPEDREFLECTIONS.M03">Warped Reflections</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODHISTORY.BODY.BLIGHTLANDS">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Parasitic expansion.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

The Flood can survive and grow in almost any environment, but it thrives in a surprisingly narrow band of habitability. The interior of Flood hives provide a controlled environment for accelerated growth, but in time an entire planet’s biosphere can be altered to approximate these ideal conditions. 

Blightlands are the first step of this conversion process: areas around established hives filled with specialized Flood growths which harvest the vitality of the soil, soak up solar energy, and consume all native life within its boundaries. While they briefly flower with a grotesque vitality, ultimately these zones are themselves consumed to provide raw materials for city-sized spore towers and colossal stacks of strange Flood organs that finish the planet’s ruination.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODHISTORY.BODY.COMBATFORMS">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Pestilent puppets.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Combat forms are relatively intact sentient hosts under the control of an infection form that has nested within. Though sections of the host's body are consumed and converted into Flood cells, some limbs and sensory organs are retained to utilize available weapons, tools, vehicles, equipment, and even starships. The infection form does augment its new body and repair minor damage in order to better serve as a living weapon, but ultimately the combat form is utterly disposable.

The infection form driving the host body does not feel pain or fear, though the same cannot be said for the host. Worse, in some horrific circumstances the infection form is unable to completely dominate the original personality and the victim remains fully aware of their irrevocable transformation and use as a tool of the parasite.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODHISTORY.BODY.FLOODHIVES">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;The graveyard of dreams.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

The Flood’s only desire is to expand and corrupt. Once sufficient numbers of infected are available the parasite can establish lairs for defense and the growth of specialized forms. These lairs are usually repurposed spaces, for the Flood does not build when it can instead infest. Access tunnels and hallways are quickly converted into fetid lairs choked with spores and buildings are broken up into mucus-filled nest chambers in which nightmares are birthed. These tumorous blights are often the most obvious targets for attack and cleansing, but they are simply a symptom of Flood infestation, not its cause. A distinction the Forerunners learned far too late, after countless burned hives and toppled spore towers resulted in only empty victories.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODHISTORY.BODY.GRAVEMIND">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;A single intelligence inhabiting multiple instances.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

A Gravemind is the apex of the Flood’s coordinating intelligences. It is a monument of ancient sins; a self-aware &lt;b&gt;compound mind&lt;/b&gt; that transcends individual hosts and lesser key minds; a formless intellect who knows all that the Flood have ever possessed. 

The Gravemind brings its horrific form of peace through unification, salvation through assimilation. Its only goal is the consumption of every thinking creature in the galaxy. The Gravemind’s most recent physical avatar was destroyed when the Master Chief fired the Ark’s incomplete Halo, but it is only a matter of time before it rises again.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODHISTORY.BODY.HIGHCHARITY">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;City of the dead.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Once the capital of the Covenant and the jewel of their star-spanning empire, High Charity is now a shattered collection of wreckage sealed off and buried on the Ark’s surface. Only a small fraction of its grandeur remains, and even that is distorted and tarnished by the Flood trapped within its halls after the Gravemind was defeated by the Master Chief. 

Decimated—but not eradicated—the parasite has marshalled what remains of its strength in the years since. This diseased cluster could have been cleansed if the installation’s monitor was still active, but the Ark’s fallback defense protocols can only contain the Flood inside High Charity with armored walls and patrolling Sentinels, a half-measure that allows the parasite to fester and plan within the ruins.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODHISTORY.BODY.INFECTIONFORM">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;A nightmare tide rises.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Flood infection forms are nightmarish homunculi spawned in massive numbers for the singular purpose of converting all living creatures into carriers, tools, and food for the parasite. The most commonly encountered infection forms have soft, pod-like bodies with numerous tentacle-like appendages and a frond-like array which acts as the creature’s sensory system. Their tendrils are multi-purpose locomotion systems and insidious methods of control. 

Each tendril ends in nano-scale barbs which can latch onto the target’s body and cut through armor or environmental suits. Once the target is compromised, infection forms inject Flood cells to hijack the victim’s nervous system. Even if the infection form is quickly removed, Flood cells in the wounds will slowly consume the victim and turn them into quivering, spore-packed blisters. Against unprepared victims the infection form bores into the body, quickly mutating it into a combat form.

Though barely intelligent on their own, once an infection form infiltrates a sentient creature they turn the victim’s cognitive power to the furtherance of Flood goals. Each is an insidious puppeteer, able to sift through memories of any sentient creature to learn of military countermeasures, security access codes, and the location of population centers. This information is then shared with other Flood through their connection with the key minds.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODHISTORY.BODY.KEYMINDS">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fonts of malign intelligence.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

After an infestation is established the parasite transitions from feral aggression to coordinated conversion by creating specialized Flood organisms that network their individual intelligences. These &lt;b&gt;key minds&lt;/b&gt; act as coordinators for nearby Flood, leveraging wisdom harvested from the parasites’ hosts to expand, outwit, overwhelm, and consume other life. 

As the Flood grow in number these key minds combine and expand into larger, exponentially more intelligent networks. The appearance of these vile collectives typically indicate most local animal life and sentient hosts have been infected or consumed. Once a critical mass of key minds have combined the Flood’s centralized intelligence can begin to emerge in their seething mass of corrupted flesh: a &lt;b&gt;Proto-Gravemind&lt;/b&gt; that sifts through and feeds on the memories of every Flood-infected victim.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODHISTORY.BODY.PUREFORMS">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Bone and bile.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

As the parasite grows in strength the key minds begin to cultivate tumorous masses and mucus-like lakes of pure Flood cells using nonessential biomass as food. Most of these Flood cells are used to form hives and blightlands, but some is harvested to create deadly &lt;b&gt;war-forms&lt;/b&gt;. With the sound of breaking bones and ripping flesh these creatures transform themselves to best confront the threats they encounter, contorting and reshaping their anatomy into grotesque but lethal shapes as they lead hordes of lesser combat forms into battle.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODHISTORY.BODY.THEFLOOD">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;The great devourer.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

The Flood is a voracious hive-mind parasite that seizes, converts, and controls sentient hosts to perpetuate itself. Infected individuals have their nervous systems suborned by the parasite, turning their bodies into puppets while their memories and flesh are assimilated and exploited to further the infestation. 

Each infected host is linked to a distributed intelligence, allowing for interstellar coordination and the formation of increasingly sophisticated consciousness nodes. If the Flood is not stopped it will eventually manifest a malevolent meta-intelligence known as &lt;b&gt;Gravemind&lt;/b&gt;.

Flood are composed of a highly adaptable and resilient neuron-like “super cell” that has no analogous structures with other life in the galaxy. These protean cells are the building blocks of all Flood and can be configured into any shape or pseudo-organ necessary to sustain the biological and organizational growth of the parasite. 

Encysted Flood cells form spores which can parasitize both sentient and non-sentient species, rapidly consuming the host and transforming their biomass into an incubator for larger, more mobile Flood combat and infection forms. There is no inoculation against infection, no treatment to slow the parasites’ growth, no reversal of its transformation. The &lt;b&gt;only&lt;/b&gt; effective countermeasure is containment and incineration.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODHISTORY.TITLE.BLIGHTLANDS">Blightlands</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODHISTORY.TITLE.COMBATFORMS">Combat Forms</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODHISTORY.TITLE.FLOODHIVES">Flood Hives</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODHISTORY.TITLE.GRAVEMIND">Gravemind</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODHISTORY.TITLE.HIGHCHARITY">High Charity</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODHISTORY.TITLE.INFECTIONFORM">Infection Forms</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODHISTORY.TITLE.KEYMINDS">Keyminds</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODHISTORY.TITLE.PUREFORMS">Pure Forms</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODHISTORY.TITLE.THEFLOOD">The Flood</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.BODY.COCOONEDBASES">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fallen citadels.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

The parasite does not build what it can instead repurpose.  UNSC and Banished bases within High Charity’s blightlands have been converted into hives of the Flood. They are a hideous sight that barely resemble the structures they once were. There are no survivors or salvage worth recovering in these hideous warrens. These facilities’ defenses are also now under Flood control.

Cocooned Bases are a major threat and priority target, but are surrounded by blightland and located deep in Flood territory. They continually spawn Flood units until eliminated, and even when the base is destroyed there are hordes of twisted creatures who will pour out the wreckage. Regardless of the risks, the only way to deal with Flood-infested bases is to burn them to the ground, preferably from orbit. The base slot of the Cocooned Base is freed when the Flood buildings are razed.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.BODY.EGG">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Incubation chambers.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Non-sentient animals or corpses not harnessed for combat forms are seeded with Flood cells and transformed into infection form-filled sacs. These diseased growths are one of the most pernicious aspects of the Flood, and a single spore could potentially transform an entire planet’s biosphere into quivering masses of diseased mucus and bile if left unchecked.

Blisters “hatch” infection forms when disturbed. Destroying them at a distance is almost always the best option.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.BODY.HIVE">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Infected wounds.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Spore Mounds are an agglomeration of lesser Flood forms and secretions that conceal and protect the foul nests of the parasite. Though mere hills compared to what is to come, the Spore Mounds which have sprouted on the Ark and survived Sentinel cleansing efforts are incredibly dangerous.

Spore Mounds act as an Abomination leader for nearby Flood, in addition to producing new units.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.BODY.HIVECOMMANDER">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Hive commanders.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

A massive key mind war-form, the Abomination brings order and direction to the lesser Flood, turning feral parasites into a cunning and efficient collective. An evolved form of the Juggernaut command form, these towering nightmares are used when standard hives cannot be established and the Flood must stay mobile to avoid detection and destruction.

Abominations increase the speed and health of all nearby Flood units. As the parasite grows in strength, it will construct attack waves around these “generals.” Blunting their onslaught requires making a difficult choice between attacking the Abomination or prioritizing the smaller, more immediate threats.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.BODY.INFECTED">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;The lost and the damned.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Flood-infected sentients serve the parasite as tools and weapons while simpler creatures are twisted into foul abominations that seek only to devour and fuel the parasite’s growth. There is no cure or treatment that can save these victims, and even death may not save their consciousness from being absorbed into the Flood collective for later use. 

Though their bodies are bent to the Flood’s will, occasionally the victim can still whisper for mercy or cry out in pain from ruined lips and half-consumed throats. Or worse, the parasite will speak on their behalf, using stolen thoughts and memories as a psychological weapon.

Most infantry and vehicles with a living crew who take lethal damage from the Flood are converted into &lt;b&gt;Infected&lt;/b&gt; units. Exceptions include non-organic units (Sentinels), Huragok living machines (Engineers), the enigmatic Lekgolo (Hunters), and Super units (who self-destruct when compromised). Heroes also ensure they are not taken by the Flood.

&lt;b&gt;Infected vehicles&lt;/b&gt; are hideously warped versions of their former selves, their crew having been converted into spore-packed pustules and mucus-like growths which hold the damaged vehicle together. Infected vehicles are weaker than their uninfected counterparts, but when they are destroyed infection forms have a chance of bursting from the wreckage.

&lt;b&gt;Infected infantry&lt;/b&gt; mutate into combat forms that retain the weaponry they had before conversion. Infected infantry gain a powerful tentacle-scythe melee attack and the ability to leap short distances.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.BODY.PODINFECTORS">Once the parasite can establish a hive it can begin to produce massive numbers of infection forms that spread out in search of new sentients to infect, and non-sapient animals on which to feed. Both ground and airborne infection forms are used as living weapons, hurling themselves at the enemy to overwhelm defenses and assimilate the unprepared.

&lt;b&gt;Pods&lt;/b&gt; hurl themselves at infantry units, bursting and dealing damage. If Pods gets the killing blow their victim becomes Infected and falls under Flood control. Though individually weak and easily killed, pod infectors strike in vast numbers and can move over cliffs.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.BODY.PROTOGRAVEMIND">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;High Charity’s Bane.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

The Proto-Gravemind within High Charity is the shadow of a far greater threat, one that will unleash damnation upon the stars should it grow unchecked. High Charity’s proto-Gravemind is a perverse mockery of a living thing, a gluttonous stump of Flood cells that remained behind when Halo’s cleansing energies burned away the corrupted biomass which once supported the Gravemind. 

A measure of Gravemind’s intellect remains, though its new vessel must feed and spread in order for it to manifest fully once again. With every Banished soldier that succumbs to its embrace, the Gravemind’s re-emergence grows closer. The mountain of half-dead flesh quivers in anticipation, and the echo of timeless laughter rises from somewhere deep below.

High Charity’s Proto-Gravemind is a massive, highly adaptable biological weapon. It is a horrifying enemy, protected by every Flood beast on the Ark. Only fools and madmen dare to attack it without overwhelming force.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.BODY.RUPTURE">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Underground lurkers.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Bursters are carrier forms that erupt from the ground, simultaneously releasing their cache of parasites and spores.

Bursters guard Flood blightlands, and will attack any interlopers within the parasite’s twisted domain.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.BODY.SEEDERINFECTORS">Once the parasite can establish a hive it can begin to produce massive numbers of infection forms that spread out in search of new sentients to infect, and non-sapient animals on which to feed. Both ground and airborne infection forms are used as living weapons, hurling themselves at the enemy to overwhelm defenses and assimilate the unprepared.

&lt;b&gt;Seeders&lt;/b&gt; are lighter-than-air Flood units that swim through the sky and attack aerial units. If a Seeder gets the killing blow, the crew are overwhelmed and the aircraft becomes Infected. Seeders only infect aircraft, but will “spit” shards of bone at ground targets.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.BODY.SPAWNER">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Nightmare birthing chambers.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Spawners are pure forms that gestate new infection forms in their diseased brood sacs, releasing swarms of new parasites. Spawners are an example of Flood adaptation, a war-form created specifically to counter the defensive measures of the Ark and Banished. 

Highly mobile and capable of independent action, these creatures venture out from High Charity to spread the Flood deep into nearby refugia. Most pockets of Flood infestation Spawners establish will be detected and quickly destroyed, but time and probability is on the parasite’s side.

The Spawner lurks at the rear of Flood assaults, spawning waves of infection forms. Spawners must be quickly dealt with, or they will continue to create Flood attack forces just outside the range of base defenses</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.BODY.VEHICLEINFECTOR">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Anti-vehicle war-forms.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

The Infester is a pure form that specializes in cracking open vehicles and converting their crew into Flood-controlled puppets. A purpose-built biological weapon, Infesters expend all of their energy on their attack, collapsing in a dying heap and spreading spores upon the completion of their singular task.

The Infester is adapted to the task of countering and subverting armored vehicles used by the UNSC and Banished. Though they can attack infantry and structures with barbed tentacles, their goal is to hunt manned vehicles. When they detect mechanized prey, the Infester grabs onto it with their tentacles and bores into the hull to reach the crew. This process can be interrupted, similar to the Hijack ability. If the infestation is successful, however, the vehicle is infected and the Infester dies.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.TITLE.COCOONEDBASES">Cocooned Bases</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.TITLE.EGG">Blisters</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.TITLE.HIVE">Spore Mound</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.TITLE.HIVECOMMANDER">Abomination</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.TITLE.INFECTED">Infected</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.TITLE.PODINFECTORS">Pod Infectors</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.TITLE.PROTOGRAVEMIND">Proto-Gravemind</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.TITLE.RUPTURE">Bursters</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.TITLE.SEEDERINFECTORS">Seeder Infectors</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.TITLE.SPAWNER">Spawners</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.FLOODUNITS.TITLE.VEHICLEINFECTOR">Infester</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.M01.COLLECT.UNLOCKCONDITION">Unlocked by finding a collectable in 'What Could Go Wrong?'.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.M01LOGS.UNLOCKCONDITION">Unlocked by completing 'What Could Go Wrong?'.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.M02.COLLECT.UNLOCKCONDITION">Unlocked by finding a collectable in 'Fighting Retreat'.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.M02LOGS.UNLOCKCONDITION">Unlocked by completing 'Fighting Retreat'.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.M03.COLLECT.UNLOCKCONDITION">Unlocked by finding a collectable in 'Light the Fuse'.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.M03LOGS.UNLOCKCONDITION">Unlocked by completing 'Light the Fuse'.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.M04.COLLECT.UNLOCKCONDITION">Unlocked by finding a collectable in 'The Archive'.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.M04LOGS.UNLOCKCONDITION">Unlocked by completing 'The Archive'.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.M05.COLLECT.UNLOCKCONDITION">Unlocked by finding a collectable in 'Manifestation'.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.M05LOGS.UNLOCKCONDITION">Unlocked by completing 'Manifestation'.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.MPMAPS.BODY.FISSURES">Volatile liquid churns and boils beneath the uncertain amber surface.

Scorched cracks and violent crystal protrusions scar and pock this rocky amber terrain, torn by eruptions from the explosive molten fluid energy that bubbles and smolders beneath the surface. Pressure forces up huge bursts of the liquid, quickly solidifying into huge crystals and trapping invaluable volatile raw power inside. Nearby, an elegant Forerunner structure stretches out over the precipice overlooking endless desert dunes, housing a lift that drops deep to the solemn Archive below.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.MPMAPS.BODY.MIRAGE">Rolling sands hide the ghosts of fallen warriors in these arid wilds.

The weight of Forerunner history lays heavy upon this beautiful but wild environment.  Desert winds moan at the edge of a vast Forerunner gate that protects a long-forgotten secret; the ship-seed of an ancient Forerunner Despair-class fighter, dormant for a hundred millennia.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.MPMAPS.BODY.TERMINUS">This Forerunner structure is a vital node in the Ark’s defences and must be preserved at all costs.

After the Halo Array eradicated the Flood threat and the Forerunners disappeared, the Ark lay dormant and untouched for millennia.

When the Human-Covenant war spilled over onto the Ark, the installation’s threat assessment systems began an exhaustive recording and indexing of events in an effort to anticipate dangers and prepare adequate countermeasures to deal with similar challenges in the future.

These threat assessments compare modern battle records against all catalogued historical conflicts, cross-referencing them with updated information and calculating probable outcomes. The systems performing these assessments are powered by Terminus structures, the loss of which could result in the corruption of centuries of analysis, compromising the Ark’s long-term ability to defend itself.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.MPMAPS.TITLE.FISSURES">Fissures</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.MPMAPS.TITLE.MIRAGE">Mirage</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.MPMAPS.TITLE.TERMINUS">Terminus</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.MPMAPS.UNLOCKCONDITIONTERMINUS">Unlocked by playing Terminus Firefight.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.BODY.BRUTEGRENADIER">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Destroyers and despoilers.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Brute Grenadiers are a special infantry unit available to Voridus. Their &lt;b&gt;Gel Siphon&lt;/b&gt; ability allows them to absorb nearby infusion pools and harness that energy to overcharge their &lt;b&gt;iatrochemically-enhanced armor&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;grenade launchers&lt;/b&gt;. 

On death, their equipment explodes, doing damage to nearby units and leaving behind an infusion pool. Their weapons can be upgraded with &lt;b&gt;Hard-Target Detonators&lt;/b&gt; to cause additional damage against vehicles and structures, and &lt;b&gt;Infused Grenades&lt;/b&gt; which increases grenade attack range and creates short-lived energy pools at the point of impact.

The Brutes Grenadiers are madmen and savages who are too unstable and crude to advance in the Banished hierarchy. With few other options to seek glory, they have turned to Voridus, who offers a place in the vanguard of his pack for any willing to test his latest inventions. Glory they will have, even as their bodies rot from the inside out from exposure to the unspeakably toxic by-products of the power they abuse.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.BODY.INFUSEDENGINEER">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Aberrant Huragok.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Infused Engineers replace standard Engineers in Voridus’ army. They retain the Huragok &lt;b&gt;reconstitution beam&lt;/b&gt; but channel large &lt;b&gt;infused gel pools&lt;/b&gt; instead of creating overshield bubbles with their special ability.

Extended exposure to the toxic residue of Voridus’ experiments with infusion gel has altered his Huragok assistants, causing some to simply fall apart while the rest have been changed in other—more subtle—ways. These “damaged” Engineers are shunned by their healthy companions and display distinctly non-Huragok behaviors, such as a lack of interest in repairing Forerunner machinery and sabotaging equipment of Banished who have annoyed them in the past. As long as the Infused Engineers continue to perform their duties for him, however, Voridus has little interest in their long-term health or new behaviors.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.BODY.PAVIUM">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Unyielding tyrant.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Warlord Pavium is an architect and siegemaster, making and unmaking fortifications at Atriox’s command. Given the epithet “The Unbreakable” for his implacable discipline and prowess in combat engineering, Pavium’s skill is unimpeachable, but conflicting ties of loyalty to his clan and brother has slowed advancement in the Banished. Eager to prove his worth, Pavium has redoubled the efforts of his pack since their setback on the Halo ring. His efforts have not gone without notice, and Atriox has tasked Pavium and his brother with a mission to judge their worthiness as members of the warmaster’s inner circle.

Pavium is a traditional Jiralhanae combat engineer, taking to the field of battle as an engine of destruction, smashing enemy lines as part of the pack’s vanguard. His panoply of war always includes his custom warplate gifted to him by Decimus. On the battlefield, Pavium is a walking tank armed with a &lt;b&gt;Heavy Mortar System&lt;/b&gt; for direct bombardment and a &lt;b&gt;Target Designator&lt;/b&gt; for calling out high-value targets for combined fire. Targets &lt;i&gt;painted&lt;/i&gt; by Pavium’s designator can not benefit from stealth and take additional damage. This effect continues until the painted unit dies, moves out of range, or Pavium cancels the ability. Upgrades include &lt;b&gt;Designator Shells&lt;/b&gt;, which temporarily paints targets hit by his mortar and an &lt;b&gt;Advanced Designator&lt;/b&gt;, which also paints the enemies close to the main target.

Pavium specializes in a defensive strategy which combines &lt;b&gt;Mega Turrets&lt;/b&gt;, powerful &lt;b&gt;Ultra Mines&lt;b&gt;, and orbital &lt;b&gt;Rain of Fire&lt;/b&gt; to secure basing sites. Once established, he increases the output of buildings with &lt;b&gt;Burnout&lt;/b&gt; and tears down damaged or inefficient structures with &lt;b&gt;Full Salvage&lt;/b&gt; recycling. During grueling attrition battles he outlasts the enemy with &lt;b&gt;Enduring Will&lt;/b&gt; to create a long-lasting healing zone while simultaneously striking deep behind their lines with &lt;b&gt;Wraith Invader&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Lich Vanguard&lt;/b&gt;. All of this is monitored using his &lt;b&gt;Orbital Designator&lt;/b&gt;.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.BODY.PAVIUMUNIT">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Unyielding tyrant.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Pavium is a traditional Jiralhanae combat engineer, taking to the field of battle as an engine of destruction, smashing enemy lines as part of the pack’s vanguard. His panoply of war always includes his custom warplate gifted to him by Decimus. 

On the battlefield, Pavium is a walking tank armed with a &lt;b&gt;Heavy Mortar System&lt;/b&gt; for direct bombardment and a &lt;b&gt;Target Designator&lt;/b&gt; for calling out high-value targets for combined fire. Targets &lt;i&gt;painted&lt;/i&gt; by Pavium’s designator cannot benefit from stealth and take additional damage. This effect continues until the painted unit dies, moves out of range, or Pavium cancels the ability. Upgrades include &lt;b&gt;Designator Shells&lt;/b&gt;, which temporarily paints targets hit by his mortar and an &lt;b&gt;Advanced Designator&lt;/b&gt;, which also paints the enemies close to the main target.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.BODY.VOLATILESCARAB">Overcharged weapons systems make this modified assault platform even more deadly for both enemies and for the Scarab’s own crew.

Never one to leave a good weapon alone, once Voridus learned how to harness the power of infused gel he immediately started testing its application to all available Banished systems. Not all vehicles could accommodate the large containment systems required to weaponized the gel, but in the case of the Scarab that extra bulk was a trivial addition. The Infused Scarabs fielded by Voridus are capable of spreading massive pools of the damaging energy gel across the battlefield while retaining the Scarab’s base resilience and ability to traverse even the largest combat obstacles.

Voridus enjoys taking personal command of his Infused Scarabs whenever possible but retains a small cadre of specially selected pilots ready to take over for him when he is otherwise occupied. The prospect of charging into withering enemy fire while riding atop massive tanks of the most volatile liquid known to Banished armorers takes a special kind of crazy, which Voridus knows all too well how to engender in his troops.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.BODY.VORIDUS">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;The corrupter.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Voridus is many things that his elder brother is not: glory-seeking, vicious, curious, and spontaneous. Gifted with an intuitive understanding of Forerunner systems, he has ruthlessly exploited the Ark for new resources and knowledge since the Banished arrived, culminating in his recent harnessing of &lt;g&gt;infusion gel&lt;/b&gt;. 

Infusion gel is a perfected form of the energetic meta-materials and strained-bond lattices used in Covenant fuel rods, and is one of the materials pumped throughout the Ark in great rivers to keep the installation functioning. Unfortunately, the prototype infusion technology Voridus created produces corrosive and mutagenic sludge during operation. Not that this has stopped Voridus from field testing new weapons that actually harness these dangerous by-products.

As a leader, Voridus has bent his considerable intellect to perfecting the military uses of infusion gel, utilizing it in powerful &lt;b&gt;Infused Mine&lt;/b&gt; explosives and creating an &lt;b&gt;Infusion Wake&lt;/b&gt; of corrupting energy with targeted bombing runs. With &lt;b&gt;Salt the Earth&lt;/b&gt; he spreads energy pools, while the &lt;b&gt;Invigorating Frenzy&lt;/b&gt; leader ability heals allies that are in energy pools. &lt;b&gt;Cataclysm&lt;/b&gt; triggers the energy pools latent potential, resetting their duration and significantly increasing the damage they cause to enemy units (even those in the air). When not manipulating gel, his &lt;b&gt;Combat Spoils&lt;/b&gt; leader ability orders his units to salvage a small amount of resources when dealing damage to enemy buildings.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.BODY.VORIDUSUNIT">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;The corrupter.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Voridus takes to the field in &lt;b&gt;iatrochemically-enhanced armor&lt;/n&gt; powered by tanks of infusion gel. Voridus can drop this gel from his tanks, leaving long-lasting toxic &lt;b&gt;energy pools&lt;/b&gt; in his wake which damage enemy units but which can be harnessed by his allies. 

Though he takes to the field with a standard gravity hammer, once he acquires enough resources he replaces it with an &lt;b&gt;Infused Hammer&lt;/n&gt;, which creates energy pools with each strike and synergizes with his armor. Voridus can also intentionally release the gel from his tanks when he activates his &lt;b&gt;Salt the Earth&lt;/b&gt; ability, leaving wide energy pools in his wake.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.BODY.WRAITHAPC">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Assault transport.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

The Wraith Invader is an infantry fighting vehicle available to Warlord Pavium. It is armed with a siphoning beam, which repairs the transport, and can carry two units of infantry. Each of the infantry units can fire out of the Wraith Invader. In addition to standard vehicle upgrades the gravity propulsion system of the Wraith Invader can be boosted with &lt;b&gt;Carrier Overdrive&lt;/b&gt;, significantly increasing its shield strength and damage.

In the Covenant, ecclesiastical authorities ultimately oversaw even the most trivial modifications to existing designs. Improvements or alterations required layers of bureaucracy to navigate, and often took decades to gain approval from the Prophets. The Banished approval process is much simpler: if there is a demonstrated need and materials available a pack leader can make any changes that he or she wishes. The Wraith Invader is an example of this freedom, with Pavium taking damaged mortar tank hulls and repurposing them into heavy troop carriers.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.TITLE.BRUTEGRENADIER">Brute Grenadier</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.TITLE.INFUSEDENGINEER">Infused Engineer</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.TITLE.PAVIUM">Pavium</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.TITLE.PAVIUMUNIT">Pavium</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.TITLE.VOLATILESCARAB">Volatile Scarab</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.TITLE.VORIDUS">Voridus</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.TITLE.VORIDUSUNIT">Voridus</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.CODEX.UNITSBAN.TITLE.WRAITHAPC">Wraith Invader</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.DIFFICULTY.RANDOMDESCRIPTION">Press @RandDiff@ to matchmake with any difficulty</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.FIREFIGHT.FINDMATCH">MAIN MENU/ FIREFIGHT/ FIND MATCH</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.FIREFIGHT.POSTMATCH.HISCORE.TITLE">You've posted a new high score</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.FIREFIGHT.POSTMATCH.PREVSCORE">Previous score&lt;br&gt;%1</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.FIREFIGHTDIALOG.HEADER">Terminus Firefight</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.FIREFIGHTDIALOG.STORE">@Y_Button@ Go to Store</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.FIREFIGHTDIALOG.TEXT">The new Terminus Firefight mode is part of the 'Awakening the Nightmare' download.
Please go to the store to purchase...</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.FIREFIGHTDIALOG.TITLE">New Terminus Firefight mode available.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.FIREFIGHTHUD.MULTIPLIER.LABEL">SCORE(&lt;font color='#00c8f7'&gt;X%1&lt;/font&gt;)</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.LEADERSELECT.ROLE01.CORRUPTED">Desolator</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.LEADERSELECT.ROLE01.UNBREAKABLE">Indestructible</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.LEADERSELECT.ROLE02.CORRUPTED">Stormtrooper</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.LEADERSELECT.ROLE02.UNBREAKABLE">Vanguard</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.LEADERSELECT.ROLE03.CORRUPTED">Scourge</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.LEADERSELECT.ROLE03.UNBREAKABLE">Grand Cannon</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.LEADERSELECT.ROLE3.CORRUPTED">Wakey Wakey</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.LEADERSELECT.SHORTDESCR.CORRUPTED">Voridus focuses on aggressive rush attacks and uses his unique incendiary gel weapons to create damaging pools of toxic liquid.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.LEADERSELECT.SHORTDESCR.CORRUPTED.BLITZ">Voridus focuses on aggressive rush attacks and uses his unique incendiary gel weapons to create damaging pools of toxic liquid.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.LEADERSELECT.SHORTDESCR.UNBREAKABLE">Pavium's ephitet of 'The Unbreakable' comes from his mastery of defensive and economic tactics.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.LEADERSELECT.SHORTDESCR.UNBREAKABLE.BLITZ">Pavium's ephitet of 'The Unbreakable' comes from his mastery of defensive and economic tactics.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.LEADERSELECT.TITLE.CORRUPTED">Voridus</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.LEADERSELECT.TITLE.UNBREAKABLE">Pavium</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.MISSIONBRIEFSCREEN.LOCATION.M01">HIGH CHARITY CRASH SITE</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.MISSIONBRIEFSCREEN.LOCATION.M02">HIGH CHARITY SALVAGE OPERATION</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.MISSIONBRIEFSCREEN.LOCATION.M03">BANISHED SALVAGE DRILLS</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.MISSIONBRIEFSCREEN.LOCATION.M04">FORERUNNER ARCHIVE</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.MISSIONBRIEFSCREEN.LOCATION.M05">HIGH CHARITY CRASH SITE</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.MISSIONBRIEFSCREEN.TITLE.M01">WHAT COULD GO WRONG?</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.MISSIONBRIEFSCREEN.TITLE.M02">FIGHTING RETREAT</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.MISSIONBRIEFSCREEN.TITLE.M03">LIGHT THE FUSE</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.MISSIONBRIEFSCREEN.TITLE.M04">THE ARCHIVE</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.MISSIONBRIEFSCREEN.TITLE.M05">MANIFESTATION</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.MISSIONSPAGE.SHORTDESCR.M01">Voridus launches a Scarab assault through Sentinel-heavy territory to break into High Charity.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.MISSIONSPAGE.SHORTDESCR.M02">Pavium and his troops prepare an exit route to extract High Charity salvage.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.MISSIONSPAGE.SHORTDESCR.M03">Pavium must rescue Voridus and clear a path to the Forerunner structure nearby.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.MISSIONSPAGE.SHORTDESCR.M04">Voridus desperately seeks a way to reactivate the Ark’s sentinel defenses in an effort to stop the spread of the Flood.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.MISSIONSPAGE.SHORTDESCR.M05">Voridus and Pavium must assist the Ark’s defenses in a final push to contain the Flood threat.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.PAUSESCREEN.SHORTDESCR.EP2M01">Voridus launches a Scarab assault through Sentinel-heavy territory to break into High Charity.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.PAUSESCREEN.SHORTDESCR.EP2M02">Pavium and his troops prepare an exit route to extract High Charity salvage.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.PAUSESCREEN.SHORTDESCR.EP2M03">Pavium must rescue Voridus and clear a path to the Forerunner structure nearby.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.PAUSESCREEN.SHORTDESCR.EP2M04">Voridus desperately seeks a way to reactivate the Ark’s sentinel defenses in an effort to stop the spread of the Flood.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.PAUSESCREEN.SHORTDESCR.EP2M05">Voridus and Pavium must assist the Ark’s defenses in a final push to contain the Flood threat.</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.PAUSESCREEN.TITLE.EP2M01">What Could Go Wrong?</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.PAUSESCREEN.TITLE.EP2M02">Fighting Retreat</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.PAUSESCREEN.TITLE.EP2M03">Light the Fuse</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.PAUSESCREEN.TITLE.EP2M04">The Archive</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.PAUSESCREEN.TITLE.EP2M05">Manifestation</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.RICHPRESENCE.MISSIONNAMES.M01">What Could Go Wrong?</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.RICHPRESENCE.MISSIONNAMES.M02">Fighting Retreat</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.RICHPRESENCE.MISSIONNAMES.M03">Light the Fuse</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.RICHPRESENCE.MISSIONNAMES.M04">The Archive</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.RICHPRESENCE.MISSIONNAMES.M05">Manifestation</str>
	<str id="UIEP2.STATUSBAR.RANDOMDIFFICULTY">@RandDiff@ No preferred difficulty</str>
</string_table>